<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Console Wars</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Console Wars by Blake J. Harris and I really enjoyed the trip down memory lane. I grew up in the 1980s and 1990s and played on video game systems by Nintendo, Sega, Sony, and Atari. This is my reflection on this gaming era after reading this book.
Console Wars tells the story of Tom Kalinske, an American business man and CEO behind Sega of America during its meteoric rise and fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed reading Andy Weir&amp;rsquo;s book, The Martian. It reads mostly like a series of journal entries of the protagonist, Mark Watney who&amp;rsquo;s stuck on Mars. If you are a science buff, there&amp;rsquo;s some interesting things that occur in terms of problem solving which Mythbuster Adam Savage, has said he would love to try at his Comic Con panel.
It&amp;rsquo;s also a quick read, as you may find yourself flying through the chapters as they are a bit short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Armada</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I read Ernest Cline&amp;rsquo;s book, Ready Player One. I blogged about my love for the book and how excited I was that a movie was being made. Quick update, it&amp;rsquo;s getting a release date of December 15, 2017! However, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I liked his second book, Armada, nearly as much.
In a nutshell the book is The Last Starfigther meets Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game. It&amp;rsquo;s a coming of age story of a teenager that plays video games, struggles with his place in the world, and has pop culture knowledge of things from the 80s forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated with Elon Musk and his companies: Tesla Motors and SpaceX. I recently read, Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future by Ashlee Vance just to learn a bit more about him.
I like to read books on some of the best entrepreneurs and companies in modern times. Everyone from Bill Gates, Michael Dell, Jeff Bezos, Tony Hsieh, Jason Fried, Larry Page, Sergey Brin, to Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</guid>
      <description>I own several copies of the book, Ready Player One, by Ernest Cline. I have it in hardcover, softcover, and digitally on Amazon Kindle. I only do this for a few books&amp;ndash; the ones I really enjoy. Off the top of my head, another is Jurassic Park by Michael Crichton.
This post is spoiler-free. Read it knowing that you can still fully enjoy the book and upcoming movie.
The Book The book paints a picture of a dystopian future, the year 2044, where people are plugged away in a virtual reality based world, OASIS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, I finished the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson and I wrote a blog post too. For the time it was released, I would say the published book collected the most information on Steve Jobs out there. Isaacson generally gives a negative review of Jobs with multiple repetitions of reality distortion field throughout the book. The book focuses a little more on the bad relationships than the good ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y: The Last Man Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</guid>
      <description>For the past seven months I&amp;rsquo;ve jumped back into reading comics and graphic novels. I used to read them a lot when I was a teenager, but just lost interest by the mid/late 1990s. I find myself struggling to enjoy reading monthly issues and going to the comic book shop every week&amp;ndash; or even getting them online via Comixology.
The problem I have is that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reading them month to month&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s too little to read bit by bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Design of Everyday Things</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 16:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</guid>
      <description>The Design of Everyday Things comes highly recommended on Coding Horror&amp;rsquo;s recommended reading list as well as many other software developers. After giving it a read, I thought it was good, relevant today, but slightly dated with their examples.
After reading the book, I am reminded of the light switch to my bathroom in my current apartment in Los Angeles. See below.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a horrible design! The left-most button, which is red, is for off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</guid>
      <description>As a foodie and photography enthusiast, I found Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots to be a good read, mostly. Although, I did find myself skimming the later chapters as they deal with post-processing using Adobe Photoshop.
The first three chapters on fundamentals, equipment, and lighting I thought were the best for foodies interested in improving their skills as a photographer. The chapter on framing and composition is good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished reading: In The Plex</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/finished-reading-in-the-plex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/finished-reading-in-the-plex/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading In The Plex: How Google Thinks, Works, and Shapes Our Lives on my Kindle Fire.
Overall it was a good book with some insight into Google, but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say that the book was well-written. It does jump around a lot and the material wasn&amp;rsquo;t presented chronologically in story-fashion. It&amp;rsquo;s currently the most up to date book on Google as it includes recent stuff such as Android, Eric Schmidt&amp;rsquo;s stepping down as CEO in 2010, and it&amp;rsquo;s failures to enter as a social network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs biography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoyed reading the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson. I bought both the hardcover and the Kindle book version. Isaacson&amp;rsquo;s writing is superb and flows very well. However, if you read articles or even watched some Steve Jobs documentaries, it covers a lot of similar ground. I am reminded of the TV movie, Pirates of Silicon Valley. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, I highly recommend it.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair for people to compare him to Thomas Edison, as Jobs was our modern day inventor and businessman&amp;ndash; a visionary if you will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List for Summer 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/reading-list-for-summer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 20:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/reading-list-for-summer-2011/</guid>
      <description>I have selected the books I&amp;rsquo;d like to complete before the end of Summer/Fall season. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a nice set and variety of books.
 The 4-Hour Workweek by Timothy Ferriss Confessions of a Public Speaker by Scott Berkun Peopleware: Productive Projects and Teams by Tom DeMarco and Timothy Lister Eloquent Ruby by Russ Olsen Four Steps to Epiphany by Steven Gary Blank The Camera by Ansel Adams Joel on Software by Joel Spolsky  The Green Lantern: Blackest Night graphic novels below I already finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Happiness by Tony Hsieh</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago, Tony Hsieh, the CEO of Zappos, offered free copies of his new book, Delivering Happiness: A Path to Profits, Passion, and Purposevia his twitter. I hopped on it right away and got myself two copies of it by using two different email addresses. I gave one away to a friend and kept the remaining copy to myself to keep and read.
I really enjoyed this book. It&amp;rsquo;s inspirational how Tony Hsieh started his company out, taking the big risks he did, despite the economic conditions of the Dot Com bubble burst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rework by Jason Fried and David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 14:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Rework by the founders of 37Signals. I really really enjoyed the book. The chapters were concise and to the point.
Here are my favorite chapters:
 Learning from mistakes is overrated Planning is guessing No time is no excuse Outside money is Plan Z Embrace constraints Focus on won&#39;t change Interruption is the enemy of productivity Meetings are toxic Your estimates suck Underdo your competition Say no by default Emulate chefs Drug dealers get it right Do it yourself first Everybody works They&#39;re not thirteen Don&#39;t scar on the first cut  I highly recommend people to pick up a copy if you are at all interested in how a great business should be run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coders at Work and Duct Tape Programming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 21:25:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Coders at Work! I really enjoyed the interviews with Jamie Zawinksi, Douglas Crockford, Brendan Eich, and Ken Thompson. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too interested in compilers and the much older systems some of the programmers once developed in. I must admit, I had a short attention span reading over those sections.
Anyway, the reason I picked this book up was because back in late September to early October 2009, I remember reading several blog posts on duct tape programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished reading the Groundswell</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 03:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading Groundswell: Winning in a World Transformed by Social Technologies. Probably one of the best books I&amp;rsquo;ve read this year thus far.
 What Is Groundswell? It&#39;s a book by two Forrester analysts with practical, data-based strategies for companies that want to harness the power of social technologies like blogs, social networks, and YouTube. (source: Forrester) I absolutely love reading case studies in these IT Business books. I finished my MS in Information Systems 2 years ago last month.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>