<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Travel on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Travel on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 11:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Road Trip From LA to Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Last week I drove from Los Angeles back to my hometown of Chicago. I&amp;rsquo;ve moved back home for personal reasons. It took my sister and I nine days to get across the US&amp;ndash; mostly just eating, driving, sleeping, and taking pictures.
The states I drove through were (in order):
 California Arizona Utah Colorado Kansas Missouri Illinois  
The first half of the trip from California to Colorado was rather scenic and interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Considerate of Other Photographers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in the Bahamas for a friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding. The people, the scenery, and weather was beautiful up and through the wedding. The day after&amp;hellip; not so much. We had a bit of a tropical storm, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t last too long. Thank goodness the wedding day had clear skies.
Naturally, I brought my camera with me on the trip. I do have a post on what&amp;rsquo;s in my camera bag, typically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Traveling</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 13:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</guid>
      <description>In July of 2010, I quit my full time job as a software developer. I wanted to break away from the nine-to-five, travel a bit, have fun, and teach myself new things in the process. I was able to visit San Diego, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Boston, New York City, Denver, Bangkok, Chiang Mai, and Pattaya.

In 2011, I kept traveling, I visited Hua Hin, Phuket, Phang Nga, Singapore, Las Vegas, and Baltimore, before returning to Chicago for a time period greater than one week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting ready to Jet Blue with Blue Pass</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2010, I took off with JetBlue with my All-You-Can-Jet (AYCJ) pass during the month of September/October. I visited Boston, New York City, Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Denver. Five cities! Friends, food, and fun! It was such a fantastic journey!
On my plane rides, I met many other jet-setters flying around the US. I remember having interesting conversations with them, and even on one flight, sitting next to a dog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Baltimore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/trip-to-baltimore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/trip-to-baltimore/</guid>
      <description>I was out in Baltimore, Maryland for RailsConf last week. The conference was great, but this was also the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Baltimore other than for a flight layover. For the most part I was there for the 4 day conference and eating.
I must say that some of the neighborhoods in the evening/night didn&amp;rsquo;t feel to safe to walk through. Also, the taxis there are so very expensive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Singapore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 16:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</guid>
      <description>I went to Singapore over the weekend (April 21-25) for Red Dot Ruby Conf. It was my first time to Singapore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t travel around too much, as I was in a conference for two full days (Friday and Saturday).
Some things I noticed about Singapore:
 No mosquitoes Hot and humid like Bangkok, but more pleasant Plenty of jay-walkers Seems the major things to do are shop and eat 3G is everywhere, generally very good Singlish takes some getting used to Singapore is full of folks from everywhere Super clean everywhere No traffic-- seems well managed  I ate out often at hawker centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APN Info for Singtel&#39;s 3G in Singapore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/apn-info-for-singtels-3g-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 06:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/apn-info-for-singtels-3g-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write a quick post on my experience with getting a SIM card in Singapore.
When I arrived to Changi Airport, I immediately went to get a SIM card from a money exchange booth. They seemed to only offer prepaid SIM cards in $50, $100, and $150 SGD if I&amp;rsquo;m not mistaken. Since I was only staying for 4 days, I chose the smallest one: $50 SGD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Dot Ruby Conf 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/red-dot-ruby-conf-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 21:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/red-dot-ruby-conf-2011/</guid>
      <description>As part of my trip back to the US, I attended Red Dot Ruby Conf 2011 on April 22-23, 2011. This event takes place in Singapore, at the Singapore Management University (SMU).
I had an awesome time. I enjoy going to these social technology events. Got a chance to talk and hang out with a lot of smart folks. I really enjoy the Ruby/Rails community
Quick summary of the talks from the two days:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow Meetup in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 20:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>On the Stackoverflow blog, it was announced that April 6, 2011 would be Worldwide Stack Overflow Meetup. They created a meetup page at: Stackoverflow Meetup.
BKK Web Meetup also hosted a meetup on IDEs and other dev tools. Presentations were given on Eclipse (by @nadam9) and Vim (by @ches). Our gracious host was, as always, Web Courses Bangkok. Afterwards, we had the usual beer/food meetup at Singha Beer Park not too far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from the March BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 03:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>The BKK Web Meetup last night was pretty awesome. It was the biggest turnout I&amp;rsquo;ve seen yet, and it was also very interactive. Plenty of discussion, questions, and even stories came from the attendees.
The topic was: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about hiring and training developers. Benjamin Scherrey was the presenter. Some bullet points that I took away:
 There are some cultural barriers to understand in hiring a Thai/Asian software developer. There are some cultural barriers dealing with Thai clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 2 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of 2 of my story from 2010. You can view part 1 at: My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)
So where I last left off, I was leaving Chicago, destination: Thailand. Below, the bags I packed at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.

I was flying Korea Air for the first time. On my way to Bangkok, Thailand, I had a layover at S. Korea. Some pictures I took at the airport:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</guid>
      <description>Just want to give a quick overview of my life since mid 2010 to present, early 2011. This is part 1 of 2.
For several years I was a software developer/consultant at a few companies and organizations. I mostly used .Net and Microsoft technologies as my tools for solving problems. In July of 2010, I decided to quit my 9-5 job and try new things out. I bought a Macbook Pro and decided that I wanted to get away from .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDxBKK Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, on March 3 2011, I attended TEDxBKK over at TCDC at the top floor at Emporium in Bangkok, Thailand. You can also follow them on twitter at @tedxbkk. Overall it was a good turnout, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too enthusiastic about most of the talks though. The one that stuck out the most for me was David Christian&amp;rsquo;s talk in the Knowledge Revolution session.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from February 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 21:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures from last night&amp;rsquo;s BKK Web Meetup session on Ruby on Rails. The presentation was by Ches Martin. Our gracious host was Web Courses Bangkok. I like how everyone who brought a laptop, brought a Macbook, as you can see from the pictures.






Full album here.
Afterwards was the usual beer meetup at Singha Beer Park a few blocks away (towards Asok BTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from January 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 01:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>A recent group I started to attend is BKK Web Meetup (short for Web Design, UX Design and Web Development Meetup Group in Bangkok).
Below are the pictures I took from the January Meetup: Computer Vision with Android. The presentation is by Andrea Gagliardi La Gala.







Full album here.
Some video links Andrea provided for those who couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend:  Optical recognition of ID documents with Android phone Indoor monitoring with Android phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech communities in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 13:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Thailand now for a little over two months now. Although I miss the US a lot, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot of new things, and meeting a lot of wonderful people here in Bangkok. In other words, I&amp;rsquo;m having a blast out here.
The day after I arrived, November 9 2010, I attended a Bangkok Hackerspace meetup at True Coffee (Siam Soi 2). I walked in thinking it was going to be something akin to Jelly Chicago and community building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling with eBags</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</guid>
      <description>As many of you may or may not know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling a lot lately. From July&amp;rsquo;s trip to the San Diego Comic-Con, to September&amp;rsquo;s All-You-Can-Jet pass, to even now, Thailand! It&amp;rsquo;s been awesome, but there&amp;rsquo;s a special shout-out I need to give recognition to: eBags.com
On October 5, 2010, at the end of my All-You-Can-Jet vacationing, after hitting up 5 cities in one month, my main traveling bag: the Mother Lode eTech Junior 25 Wheeled Duffel, had ripped at the baggage claim at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>