<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>San Diego Comic Con on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/san-diego-comic-con/</link>
    <description>Recent content in San Diego Comic Con on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/san-diego-comic-con/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/san-diego-comic-con-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/san-diego-comic-con-2018/</guid>
      <description>Another year, another Comic Con (SDCC) in the bag!
The programming for this year&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con was different than other years as some of the big studios were not there&amp;ndash; namely Marvel Studios and HBO. I can understand Marvel Studios not being there this year, as they are between the Infinity War movies. They don&amp;rsquo;t want to give much information away in regards to how things are going to be in the coming movies and the next phase of their movie/storytelling development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/san-diego-comic-con-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/san-diego-comic-con-2017/</guid>
      <description>San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) has come and gone. This year marks my seventh year going to SDCC! Each year I have a good time, but every year it becomes less about the convention floor, offsite experiences, and buying stuff. Going to the con is now more about taking photos and attending panels.
Cosplay I love taking photos of cosplayers, but it&amp;rsquo;s really difficult to be at the right place at the right time to catch some of the awesome cosplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/07/san-diego-comic-con-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/07/san-diego-comic-con-2016/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from San Diego Comic Con and I&amp;rsquo;m super exhausted! My sisters and I were lucky this year and we got rooms at the Manchester Grand Hyatt, just a few blocks away from the convention center. I even nabbed myself a Superman Conan FunkoPop that was being raffled away in the very same hotel we were staying at!
The weather was hot as the sun was unforgiving most of the time during the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Photos in Cosplay Culture Magazine</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Halloween edition of Cosplay Culture magazine came out on newsstands. There is an article on San Diego Comic Con that features my photos in it. The article is a ten whopping page spread! This all started from a simple comment on an instagram photo.
You can find this magazine at Barnes and Noble, Target, Walmart, Ralph&amp;rsquo;s, Walgreens, CVS, and other major newsstands and comic shops. I found my copies at B&amp;amp;N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/san-diego-comic-con-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/san-diego-comic-con-2015/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in San Diego for Comic Con. This year marks my fifth time that I&amp;rsquo;ve been to San Diego Comic Con.
This month of July also marks twenty years since I attended my first comic convention in Chicago, when it was then known as Chicago Comic Con (it was bought by Wizard World in 1997).
The Good As usual, it&amp;rsquo;s always fun to go to the biggest geek party in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Museum of California&#39;s SDCC Exhibit</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</guid>
      <description>The Oakland Museum of California has one of my photos from San Diego Comic Con on display in their exhibit: Sunshine and Superheroes: San Diego Comic-Con. A few days ago I had the opportunity to visit and took some photos.
The exhibit runs from May 23, 2014 to May 31, 2015.
Below is the photo I took at SDCC in 2013 that they used. It&amp;rsquo;s taken on the escalators leading up to the ticket booths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/san-diego-comic-con-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/san-diego-comic-con-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last week I as in San Diego for Comic Con (SDCC). This visit marks my fourth visit to San Diego&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con, with next year (2015) marking twenty years since I attended my first comic con in Chicago. I cannot believe it&amp;rsquo;s been that long since I first ventured into a convention

This year I didn&amp;rsquo;t take as many pictures as I did in previous years. I think it&amp;rsquo;s mostly because I&amp;rsquo;m more interested in attending panels and enjoying myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/san-diego-comic-con-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/san-diego-comic-con-2013/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in San Diego for Comic-Con. This was my third time at SDCC and I had a great time as usual. I took pictures as usual, but unlike previous years, I went to more panels than any other year.
Here are my albums on G+ (and Facebook&amp;ndash; FB):
 SDCC 2013 - Valiant Panel SDCC 2013 - Panels SDCC 2013 - General  Pictures The San Diego Convention Center from the East side Teen Titans Go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 16:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</guid>
      <description>Last week I went to the San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) and had a blast. The last time I went was back in 2010, which I blogged about here. I took quite a few photos, but only post-processed a fraction of them. I may choose to post-process more of them at a later date. You can view the full album here.
I attended SDCC with a 4-day pass along with preview night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2010</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/san-diego-comic-con-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/san-diego-comic-con-2010/</guid>
      <description>Went to the San Diego Comic Con this year. First time. Awesome.
Preview Night (July 21, 2010) Arrived and checked out the exhibit hall.






SDCC 2010 Preview Night album
Day 1 (July 22, 2010) First official day of Comic Con. Attended the OneRing.net panel and the BSG/Caprica panel.









SDCC 2010 Day 1 album
Day 2 (July 23, 2010) This day was Star Wars day.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>