<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apple on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/apple/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apple on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Format your Hard Drive into exFAT</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/how-to-format-your-hard-drive-into-exfat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/how-to-format-your-hard-drive-into-exfat/</guid>
      <description>With Black Friday and Cyber Monday behind us and the upcoming holidays upon us, some of you may be getting a new external hard drive(s) for your Mac or Windows system(s). I wanted to write up a guide on how to format your drive into exFAT, the format that is well supported and ideal for many cases.
The Benefits of exFAT A few years ago, I wrote about how hard drives marketed to Apple devices are over-priced and are functionally the same as their Windows counterpart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Apple&#39;s Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/thoughts-on-apples-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/thoughts-on-apples-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, Apple had their livestream event (September 9, 2015) announcing a bunch of new things. As usual, I live tweeted some of my thoughts during the keynote. For the most part, my tweets are meant to poke fun at everything and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be taken in the most serious context. I say this because some contacts I have take great personal insult whenever I poke fun of big successful companies like Apple&amp;ndash; that are named Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, I finished the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson and I wrote a blog post too. For the time it was released, I would say the published book collected the most information on Steve Jobs out there. Isaacson generally gives a negative review of Jobs with multiple repetitions of reality distortion field throughout the book. The book focuses a little more on the bad relationships than the good ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Compatible External Hard Drives Are Over-Priced</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</guid>
      <description>Buying any technology related products online is still by far the best way to save money over buying from traditional brick and mortar stores. The likely products you would buy for your PC/Mac are keyboards, mice, external hard drive, and headphones.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the external hard drives, since they are currently priced differently between the PC and Mac market. For all intents and purposes of these drives are to backup data of a machine running either Windows or Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading my 2010 Macbook Pro to SSD</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/upgrading-my-2010-macbook-pro-to-ssd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/upgrading-my-2010-macbook-pro-to-ssd/</guid>
      <description>I recently upgraded my 15&amp;rdquo; 2010 Macbook Pro&amp;rsquo;s 500GB HDD to a 512GB SSD. The directions you find in this blog post, you should easily be able to find using a search engine. I just want to document what I did, hoping to help fill the Internet with something useful, maybe.
The didn&amp;rsquo;t have a problem with the CPU or even memory. Well, I do constantly run out of HDD space every two-three months, but I do regular backups to an external USB 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs biography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoyed reading the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson. I bought both the hardcover and the Kindle book version. Isaacson&amp;rsquo;s writing is superb and flows very well. However, if you read articles or even watched some Steve Jobs documentaries, it covers a lot of similar ground. I am reminded of the TV movie, Pirates of Silicon Valley. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, I highly recommend it.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair for people to compare him to Thomas Edison, as Jobs was our modern day inventor and businessman&amp;ndash; a visionary if you will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey from Windows to Mac</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/my-journey-from-windows-to-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/my-journey-from-windows-to-mac/</guid>
      <description>So back in May of 2010, I bought myself a Macbook Pro. I bought it for several reasons:
 I wanted a new toy/gadget to play with. I wanted to try the only other operating system (OS) I haven&#39;t really spent much time on (OS X). I wanted to get away from Microsoft technologies  Those were and are the 3 main reasons.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over 8 months of usage and I absolutely love it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>