<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 05:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a Meetup Junkie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve become a Meetup Junkie. Every month I attend several meetups related to technology and food. I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get enough of following these interests with other like-minded individuals, in the real world.

I primarily use Meetup to find interesting groups by city. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it in Chicago, Bangkok, San Francisco, and now Los Angeles. It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic and addicting!
But for those who haven&amp;rsquo;t used such a service, it may be somewhat scary&amp;ndash; especially if you are an introvert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye 2011, Hello 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/goodbye-2011-hello-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 04:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/goodbye-2011-hello-2012/</guid>
      <description>The new year has come. Time to say goodbye the past year, and hello to the upcoming one. 2011 was an amazing year for me in terms of travel, photography, and trying out new things.
I spent four months living in Thailand up until the end of April. I was able to celebrate Thai new year, songkran, among other Thai/Chinese holidays. I traveled in September through November using the JetBlue Bluepass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Traveling</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 13:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</guid>
      <description>In July of 2010, I quit my full time job as a software developer. I wanted to break away from the nine-to-five, travel a bit, have fun, and teach myself new things in the process. I was able to visit San Diego, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Boston, New York City, Denver, Bangkok, Chiang Mai, and Pattaya.

In 2011, I kept traveling, I visited Hua Hin, Phuket, Phang Nga, Singapore, Las Vegas, and Baltimore, before returning to Chicago for a time period greater than one week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting ready to Jet Blue with Blue Pass</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2010, I took off with JetBlue with my All-You-Can-Jet (AYCJ) pass during the month of September/October. I visited Boston, New York City, Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Denver. Five cities! Friends, food, and fun! It was such a fantastic journey!
On my plane rides, I met many other jet-setters flying around the US. I remember having interesting conversations with them, and even on one flight, sitting next to a dog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purchased a Herman Miller Aeron Chair</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I purchased a Herman Miller Aeron chair from Home and Office Solutions up in Northbrook, Illinois. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an Aeron for the longest time, but just never felt comfortable spending a thousand dollars on an office chair. My seven-year old Ikea chair was falling apart and wasn&amp;rsquo;t comfortable anymore. To be honest, it started to fall apart after two years. I really needed to get a new chair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Singapore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 16:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</guid>
      <description>I went to Singapore over the weekend (April 21-25) for Red Dot Ruby Conf. It was my first time to Singapore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t travel around too much, as I was in a conference for two full days (Friday and Saturday).
Some things I noticed about Singapore:
 No mosquitoes Hot and humid like Bangkok, but more pleasant Plenty of jay-walkers Seems the major things to do are shop and eat 3G is everywhere, generally very good Singlish takes some getting used to Singapore is full of folks from everywhere Super clean everywhere No traffic-- seems well managed  I ate out often at hawker centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from the March BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 03:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>The BKK Web Meetup last night was pretty awesome. It was the biggest turnout I&amp;rsquo;ve seen yet, and it was also very interactive. Plenty of discussion, questions, and even stories came from the attendees.
The topic was: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about hiring and training developers. Benjamin Scherrey was the presenter. Some bullet points that I took away:
 There are some cultural barriers to understand in hiring a Thai/Asian software developer. There are some cultural barriers dealing with Thai clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 2 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of 2 of my story from 2010. You can view part 1 at: My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)
So where I last left off, I was leaving Chicago, destination: Thailand. Below, the bags I packed at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.

I was flying Korea Air for the first time. On my way to Bangkok, Thailand, I had a layover at S. Korea. Some pictures I took at the airport:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</guid>
      <description>Just want to give a quick overview of my life since mid 2010 to present, early 2011. This is part 1 of 2.
For several years I was a software developer/consultant at a few companies and organizations. I mostly used .Net and Microsoft technologies as my tools for solving problems. In July of 2010, I decided to quit my 9-5 job and try new things out. I bought a Macbook Pro and decided that I wanted to get away from .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDxBKK Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, on March 3 2011, I attended TEDxBKK over at TCDC at the top floor at Emporium in Bangkok, Thailand. You can also follow them on twitter at @tedxbkk. Overall it was a good turnout, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too enthusiastic about most of the talks though. The one that stuck out the most for me was David Christian&amp;rsquo;s talk in the Knowledge Revolution session.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Is Happiness</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/food-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/food-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>I started a new blog/website over at foodishappiness.com. I exported all my food posts from this site as well as from bestburgerintown.blogspot.com (which I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned) and imported them into the new site. It&amp;rsquo;s just something new I wanted to try out, to see if I could generate content from my food/eating passion. I&amp;rsquo;m still on an &amp;ldquo;eating tour&amp;rdquo; of Bangkok, Thailand so to speak.

I know many say that blogs are dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from February 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 21:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures from last night&amp;rsquo;s BKK Web Meetup session on Ruby on Rails. The presentation was by Ches Martin. Our gracious host was Web Courses Bangkok. I like how everyone who brought a laptop, brought a Macbook, as you can see from the pictures.






Full album here.
Afterwards was the usual beer meetup at Singha Beer Park a few blocks away (towards Asok BTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech communities in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 13:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Thailand now for a little over two months now. Although I miss the US a lot, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot of new things, and meeting a lot of wonderful people here in Bangkok. In other words, I&amp;rsquo;m having a blast out here.
The day after I arrived, November 9 2010, I attended a Bangkok Hackerspace meetup at True Coffee (Siam Soi 2). I walked in thinking it was going to be something akin to Jelly Chicago and community building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling with eBags</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</guid>
      <description>As many of you may or may not know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling a lot lately. From July&amp;rsquo;s trip to the San Diego Comic-Con, to September&amp;rsquo;s All-You-Can-Jet pass, to even now, Thailand! It&amp;rsquo;s been awesome, but there&amp;rsquo;s a special shout-out I need to give recognition to: eBags.com
On October 5, 2010, at the end of my All-You-Can-Jet vacationing, after hitting up 5 cities in one month, my main traveling bag: the Mother Lode eTech Junior 25 Wheeled Duffel, had ripped at the baggage claim at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My visit to Blizzard Entertainment HQ</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/my-visit-to-blizzard-entertainment-hq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 10:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/my-visit-to-blizzard-entertainment-hq/</guid>
      <description>On my way to Los Angeles from San Diego, I had the opportunity to stop by the Blizzard Entertainment HQ in Irvine, California. I must say that they have an awesome campus with very developer/designer friendly offices. Toys and models everywhere!
Here some pictures, full set of pictures can be found here.










For more pictures, check out: Inside Blizzard Headquarters [PICS]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vending Machine at Work</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 22:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</guid>
      <description>This is my vending machine at work. I happen to like Reeses Peanut Butter Cups. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a sweet tooth, but it&amp;rsquo;s the only snack in the entire machine I would buy.
Can you see what&amp;rsquo;s wrong?

It&amp;rsquo;s behind a 100 Grand, one of the worst pieces of candy in the entire machine. I haven&amp;rsquo;t enjoyed a 100 Grand since I was a kid, which is probably the age of the candy since everybody knows it&amp;rsquo;s stale and gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got  a Roomba for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/i-got-a-roomba-for-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2009 23:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/i-got-a-roomba-for-christmas/</guid>
      <description>For Christmas 2008, I got a iRobot 560 Roomba Vacuuming Robot, Black and Silveras a combined gift from my sisters and their boyfriends. I must say, that this is the best Xmas gift I&amp;rsquo;ve ever received other than the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES), around 1988-1989. Which was 20 years ago&amp;hellip; wow.

The Roomba actually does a pretty decent job of cleaning my apartment. My apartment is about 620 sq ft and mostly carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signed up for the 2009 Shamrock Shuffle 8k run</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 22:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</guid>
      <description>After hearing that several friends will be doing the Shamrock Shuffle this year, I decided I wanted to challenge myself to it again. I did it two years ago, in 2007. I did little to no training for that, and ran at about a 13min/mile pace. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to bring that down to a 10min/mile pace with some proper training.
I look at this as a way to start out 2009 and hopefully, the rest of my life: As a fresh start to making a better me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday is just Stupid</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/black-friday-is-just-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 11:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/black-friday-is-just-stupid/</guid>
      <description>To my recollection, I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever participated in a Black Friday event back in 2006. And it was really really tough. In a nutshell, I went shopping at midnight, went home to nap, then went out again to shop during the day, totally 15 some hours of shopping by day&amp;rsquo;s end. It&amp;rsquo;s something that I hope to never do again in my life. (Note: I only did this because some girls wanted to do some shopping).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Went to the Obama Rally in Grant Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 01:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</guid>
      <description>I witnessed history in the making last night by attending Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s Election Night in Grant Park.
How I got the ticket: Sheer Luck
It all started after I got my lunch and was heading back to the office. A lady one floor beneath mine hopped on the elevator early (she wanted to go down, I was going up, but a co-worker of hers just got off), and she mentioned to her co-worker that if got his ticket yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 9</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</guid>
      <description>Another digerati networking event coming up in November! Last time I went I had a pretty good time talking with various people in the Chicago tech community. Only wish my company would sport me with actual up-to-date business cards!

When: Thursday, November 6, 2008 - 6:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST Where: John Barleycorn Wrigleyville Tech Cocktail Chicago 9
I also recently joined the community: iam.techcocktail.com
You can see my personal blog&amp;rsquo;s previous posting on Tech Cocktail 8 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Man Bags</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/03/my-man-bags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 21:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/03/my-man-bags/</guid>
      <description>I went on an online shopping spree earlier this week and bought some Man bags for myself. I only bought 2, but from the set below, I&amp;rsquo;m showing 2 because I ordered the one on the left (the more green/olive color), but I received the one on the right (brownish/dark-green). At first I was going to send it back, but I grew attached to the color and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go through the hassle of sending it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking forward to 2008</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/looking-forward-to-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 19:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/looking-forward-to-2008/</guid>
      <description>As 2007 comes to a close, it marks the end of one year, and the beginning of another. So too does it bring an end more or less of my blogging on spong.org. It was a personal side project of I started 9 years ago before blogs and other free services were available. Now I&amp;rsquo;m reading to officially say that I&amp;rsquo;m stopping development on it as I have other things in my life I wish to focus on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>