<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photowalk on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/photowalk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photowalk on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/photowalk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Open House Chicago 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Sunday I went to checkout Open House Chicago and did a little photowalk of my own. I actually had no plan to go until my sister gave me her priority pass the morning of. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did as it was not only had some good photops, but was a nice steps in too since I use FitBit.
The places I visited:
 The Oriental Theatre Joffrey Ballet Aon Center Continental Illinois Bank Building The Rookery  My favorite spot was the Aon Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went to Trey Ratcliff&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Photowalk. I had fun walking from the Adler Planetarium toward the Bean. As usual on my many photowalks, I tend to stray from the large groups and do my own thing. I just find it difficult to get shots I want around dozens or in this case hundreds of other photographers.
This event was actually my second time that I met Trey. The first time was a few years ago at a Santa Monica Photowalk along with MySpace Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink and Click LA Downtown Artwalk</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my second Drink and Click LA meetup in downtown Artwalk. Specifically we checked out The Last Bookstore, which is an amazing place to walk around and take photos if you are into books and little trinkets. Generally they ask you to check your bag at what I think is their main entrance, but the other entrance they do not in case you want to bring your camera bag in, which is what we all did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Drink and Click LA Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended my first Drink and Click LA event. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of the group for a while, but just never got around to attending one of their get-togethers. I really had fun talking shop with other photography enthusiasts from beginner to professionals levels. There was time to do some street photos, a little drinking, some eating, and lots of talking.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I attended a photography meetup of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus Photographer&#39;s Photowalk at Golden Gate Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was up in San Francisco May 21-23 for the Google+ Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Conference. On Monday, there was an optional photowalk at about ten locations. I attended the one led by Scott Kelby at Golden Gate Park.
The photowalk was pretty fun. It&amp;rsquo;s the third photowalk I&amp;rsquo;ve been on so far, and in general I like to stray from the group, go at my own pace, and take shots of everything I find interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Last night I attended the Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown meetup. I arrived early and walked to the Walt Disney Concert Hall to do some HDR shots. Upon arriving there, I immediately regretted not bringing my 16-35mm f/2.8 L lens. So made due with my recently purchased 24-105 f/4 L lens, which I really haven&amp;rsquo;t used that much yet.
I spent most of the evening on my own going at my own pace to take pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</guid>
      <description>Over this past weekend, on Sunday, the evening of the NBA All-Star game and Academy Awards, I went to check out a Google+ LA Photowalk in Santa Monica hosted by Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson (aka mySpace Tom).
I had a great time seeing and learning how other photography enthusiasts and professionals see things. I brought my Canon 60D, Canon 16-35mm L lens, and tripod. I regret not bringing another lens with me for some more flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>