<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Movies on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/movies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Movies on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/movies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadpool 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</guid>
      <description>I watched Deadpool 2 over the weekend and I thought the movie was just okay. The movie was done in a Deadpool way, which is both good and bad. This is my review.
Spoilers below of course.
The Good The movie is made for comic fans and those familiar with comic book pop culture. Deadpool&amp;rsquo;s character in the comics and movies is very meta in it&amp;rsquo;s commentary of comics, pop culture, current events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avengers Infinity War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</guid>
      <description>Destiny has arrived. I watched the Avengers: Infinity War twice already and I loved it. The first time was the most emotional and suprising, the second time I caught some dialogue I missed and was more relaxed.
It&amp;rsquo;s been over three years since Kevin Feige announced the plans for MCU Phase 3, and ten years since the first movie. This is the culmination of everthing that has come before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Panther</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed the Black Panther movie. The story, the characters, and especially the villain was well balanced and defined in this Marvel movie. This is my spoilery review.
The Good The characters were really solid. It&amp;rsquo;s an all-star cast!
Letitia Wright is amazing as Black Panther&amp;rsquo;s sister, Shuri. She was having fun and it really showed. She&amp;rsquo;s also starred in an episode of Black Mirror: Black Museum.
Michael B. Jordan knocked it out of the park as Erik Killmonger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies of 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>This looks like a good year for not just comic book fans, but fans of books and other franchises because there are so many sequels coming out. This is why I dropped doing comic book only movies for my posts and opened it up to all movies.
Here are my top 8 movies that I think will be hits:
 Avengers: Infinity War Black Panther Ready Player One Incredibles 2 Ant-Man and The Wasp Deadpool 2 Alita: Battle Angel Venom  Quick Thoughts Black Panther - February 16, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars The Last Jedi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</guid>
      <description>I loved Star Wars The Last Jedi. The movie is brilliant. I&amp;rsquo;ve only watched it once as of this posting and I plan on watching it a few more times to catch all the little things I may have missed.
Spoilers below of course.
Empire and Return The movie has similarities to both Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi.
The dark tones are similar to Empire. The failure of Luke Skywalker and the entire Jedi Order was touched upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice League</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</guid>
      <description>I am pretty disappointed in the Justice League (JL) movie. I went in with low expectations since it is a Zack Snyder movie that was finished by Joss Whedon. I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed Man of Steel and Batman vs Superman where I&amp;rsquo;ve complained about Snyder as a director. Despite Whedon&amp;rsquo;s involvement, JL suffers more of the same&amp;ndash; great visually with unappealing characters and story.
Spoilers below of course.
What I Liked Gal Gadot looks amazing as Wonder Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thor Ragnarok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</guid>
      <description>I really liked Thor: Ragnarok. By far it was the best Thor movie from the MCU and maybe even the best Marvel movie of 2017. There&amp;rsquo;s not much to complain about in the movie. Spoilers ahead.
What I Liked The movie is a blend of Planet Hulk and Ragnarok story from the comics. Since Marvel can&amp;rsquo;t do Hulk movies&amp;ndash; due to movie rights sitting with Universal, they just incorporated one of his best stories in with Thor&amp;rsquo;s to make a buddy space adventure and comedy movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>Spider-Man: Homecoming is a good, coming-of-age movie aimed at younger fans and those young at heart. I liked it on a few levels, but also felt distant because I&amp;rsquo;m older and watched other Spidey and superhero films since the early 1990s.
The Good I like how Tom Holland actually looks like a teenager. I&amp;rsquo;ve always preferred the younger teen Spider-Man that makes quips in battles. Toby Maquire looked too old for high school and Andrew Garfield too handsome/hipster/cool to be Peter Parker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder Woman</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</guid>
      <description>I watched the Wonder Woman movie twice, didn&amp;rsquo;t like it much the first time, but enjoyed it more the second time. My initial reaction after the first viewing was rather harsh on the movie, and I think it had to do with how close I sat and how much my eyes had to travel when looking at the screen. The second time I sat further back in a sweet spot, and my eyes were more relaxed to enjoy the movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed watching Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2, it&amp;rsquo;s what a space adventure movie should be! What I especially love about the movie is that every character has his/her moment in the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s a great sequel to the amazing first movie.
The movie has FIVE post credit scenes, yes 5, so be sure to stay through the entire credit scroll to catch them all. This is my spoiler filled review of the movie, so read no further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched the movie yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</guid>
      <description>I liked the movie, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t love Logan. It was the best Wolverine movie Fox has made, but that bar is rather low to clear. After 17 years of playing the character, it was a good send off for Hugh Jackman. He really made the character his own over the years, despite being different from the comics-Wolverine character.
The Good What I liked about the movie is that it continues to stay true to movie-Wolverine character that Jackman has made in his solo movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Book Movies of 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote a post about Super Hero Movies of 2016. I wanted to do the same for 2017, as it looks to be another amazing year for comic fans.
2017 Rankings This is the ranking, 1-6, ranked from most looking forward to, to least.
 Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 (May 5, 2017) Wonder Woman (June 2, 2017) Thor: Ragnarok (November 3, 2017) Justice League (November 17, 2017) Spiderman: Homecoming (July 7, 2017) Logan (March 3, 2017)  Logan I cannot get excited about Fox&amp;rsquo;s Logan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Strange</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</guid>
      <description>The last MCU movie for 2016, Doctor Strange came out last week. This is my spoilery review which covers some plot points and my thoughts of it&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on the movie universe.
I really enjoyed the movie. It was an origin movie that formally introduced magic and the multiverse into Marvel&amp;rsquo;s cinematic universe. This is a big deal because it opens the door to infinite possibilities for how they wish to expand or even link universes together&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at Fox&amp;rsquo;s Deadpool/X-Men franchise here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</guid>
      <description>My quick non-spoiler-y thoughts on Suicide Squad:
I went in with low expectations, overall, the movie was just okay. I was entertained, but not blown away by anything. If you are expecting what you saw the trailers, you are probably going to be disappointed. It&amp;rsquo;s worth a watch if you want to keep up with the DC movie universe.
Disclaimer: I watched the movie for free with my T-Mobile Tuesday App, which gave me free tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warcraft Movie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is my review for the Warcraft movie, which is based off the video game.
I normally give a spoiler warning, but I won&amp;rsquo;t say enough about the plot of the movie to ruin anyone&amp;rsquo;s experience. But in case you are sensitive to any information and want to go in fresh, then you should stop reading now&amp;ndash; but I doubt that since you&amp;rsquo;ve read this far already.
I do have some background in playing Warcraft III, World of Warcraft (WoW), Hearthstone, and other games from Blizzard Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-Men Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>This is my spoiler filled review for the latest X-Men movie. I also talk about all the previous X-Men movies. It won&amp;rsquo;t be pretty.
I did not care for X-Men: Apocalypse.
I went in with low expectations and came out disappointed with what I saw. This is coming from someone who read some of the X-Men comics as well as watched the 1990s animated TV series.
The problem is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie where things happen, has characters from the X-Men universe, but in name only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain America: Civil War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>This is my Captain America: Civil War review that contains spoilers, so if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the movie yet, please stop reading now! I also provide some insights and predictions on what&amp;rsquo;s to come. I also assume you&amp;rsquo;ve seen all the movies in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) to date.
I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the movie twice now and I really like it. I even enjoyed it more the second time. Not only does it complete a trilogy of the Captain America movies, it also sets up Phase 3 of the MCU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batman v Superman Dawn of Justice Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I saw Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice. In a nutshell, I thought it was okay, but not great&amp;ndash; nor does it match the hype. This post does contain SPOILERS, so don&amp;rsquo;t read any further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it yet or don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned&amp;hellip;.
I reviewed Man of Steel several years ago and gave it a generally positive review for a sci-fi Superman reimagining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Hero Movies of 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year (2016), is looking to be an amazing year for comic book and superhero fans. There are so many movies coming out from both Marvel and DC that it&amp;rsquo;s a stark reminder how great it is to be a fan. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, this post is spoiler free for both the movies (since I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen them nor have they come out yet) and the source materials, the comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man of Steel Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</guid>
      <description>Man of Steel is the best take on Superman movie since Christopher Reeve donned the role. For me, he set the bar as to what Superman was before anything. Immediately after watching the movie, I said I liked it. But after sleeping on it and thinking about it more and more, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to like it less and less.
SPOILERS below. You have been warned.
What I liked: It&amp;rsquo;s a new take on Superman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiro Dreams of Sushi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 01:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from watching a special advanced screening of Jiro Dreams of Sushi at the Landmark. Special thanks to Aisha and Foodspotting for putting me on the list!
The documentary is wonderful! Besides the very appealing video of sushi on the big screen, there is quite a story of Jiro Ono and his sushi restaurant, Sukiyabashi Jiro. There certainly is craftsmanship and art to making sushi&amp;ndash; which Jiro has dedicated his life to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Lantern Movie Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 13:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>Green Lantern was the movie I was looking forward to the most this summer. I watched it last night and wanted to share my thoughts on the movie with other fans and others that may have watched the movie already. I still recommend people to go watch the movie though, to read the comics, and/or then come talk to me.
Please note, DO NOT READ FURTHER IF YOU HAVEN&amp;rsquo;T SEEN THE MOVIE YET.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Transformers 3 Set in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I just realized I never formally made a blog post on all the pictures I took of the Transformers 3 set in Chicago of Summer of 2010. Many of the photos I took weren&amp;rsquo;t that far from the office I was working at.
Here you go, enjoy the albums:  2010 Transformers 3 Set 2010 July 17 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 1 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 19 Transformers Set</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>