<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Media on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/social-media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Media on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/social-media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Epic History</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/game-of-thrones-epic-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/game-of-thrones-epic-history/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of Game of Thrones like I am? Have you checked out Comic Book Girl 19&amp;rsquo;s (CBG19) youTube videos on this book/show?
Well, you should. Her epic history videos cover all the major houses (Baratheon, Stark, Targaryen, and Lannister). She has other videos too.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the books like me, her videos helps me appreciate the TV show immensely. I previously blogged about my Top 5 YouTube Channels for Comic Geeks, and she&amp;rsquo;s listed there as being one of my favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 YouTube Channels for Comic Geeks</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s such an amazing time to be a comic book fan/geek. From movies to TV shows and merchandising, all the way to comic cons, there&amp;rsquo;s just so much content to consume that it can be a bit overwhelming. I don&amp;rsquo;t really watch TV anymore and just rely on my social media feed, websites, and youTube for all my news and entertainment. So there are a few YouTube channels that I absolutely love and would recommend to my friends and comic fans alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram, the Better Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/instagram-the-better-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/instagram-the-better-twitter/</guid>
      <description>I like Twitter for following interesting people and entities. But lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken to Instagram more because it can also be interesting and more visually pleasing since each post has a picture telling a story.
I know Twitter has updated features to display images in web and mobile apps now, but most tweets do not have any picture whatsoever&amp;ndash; even though tweets with pictures have twice the amount of engagements over those that do not have a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Up Old Social Accounts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/cleaning-up-old-social-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/cleaning-up-old-social-accounts/</guid>
      <description>A week ago I deleted my Instagram and Path accounts.
Today I was able to delete an old Facebook account I created in 2006 when I was in graduate school. After graduating, I not only lost access to that email address, but also forgot the password and even the email address! It was one of those school accounts that auto generates an email address based on first letter of first name, followed by however many more characters of the last name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus is for Geeks</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/google-plus-is-for-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 01:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/google-plus-is-for-geeks/</guid>
      <description>Google Plus (G+) is for geeks. It&amp;rsquo;s how it is now, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s going to be going forward, more or less.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using G+ now for about a month. I scored an invite early on, and a few days later invited a good chunk of people from my Gmail contacts. I went through the process of making circles, refining the circles, installing the add-ons into my Chrome browser, and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Social Networks Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/the-history-of-social-networks-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/the-history-of-social-networks-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In The History of Social Networks Part 1, I covered the legacy social networks that I was once a part of. I use the term legacy to mean out-dated, unpopular, and in some cases discontinued.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m going to cover the current social networks that I am active on today. I guess you can say that these are my picks, for now.
Facebook I remember when I first heard about Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Social Networks Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/the-history-of-social-networks-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/the-history-of-social-networks-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Paul Adams has an insightful presentation: The Real Life Social Network. It&amp;rsquo;s a great read, but it is a little long (224 slides)! Basically, he points out that the social network isn&amp;rsquo;t a fad, that it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay, and he goes through to talk about how relationships are, online/offline, behaviors, etcetera. Check it out if you have some time.
Since I started using computers, there&amp;rsquo;s always been a yearning to connect with others online&amp;ndash; through a social network in some way, shape, or form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s next for Social Media?:  GPS-enabled applications</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/whats-next-for-social-media-gps-enabled-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 19:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/whats-next-for-social-media-gps-enabled-applications/</guid>
      <description>There are some really cool GPS applications out there that are about to push the boundaries of technology and social media as we know it. I remember years ago when I shared a link to Loopt with friends, pretty much everyone didn&amp;rsquo;t like the idea of sharing that much information with each other. Today, I already have a few friends jumping onto to use such an app. Google has now also released a similar application out called Google Latitude, but based on their Google login system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook to become the new AOL?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/facebook-to-become-the-new-aol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/facebook-to-become-the-new-aol/</guid>
      <description>I used to use Prodigy as my Internet Service Provider (ISP) back in the 1990s. It was fun to post to bulletin boards and participate in various discussions. I then jumped over to use America Online (AOL) because of it&amp;rsquo;s nicer interface, live chat rooms, email, instant messaging, buddy lists, and overall better features. To be honest, back then I used the Internet for two things: to talk about wrestling and find Dragonball Z pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>