<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Los Angeles on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/los-angeles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Los Angeles on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/los-angeles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was at Anime Expo (AX). In general it was super fun to be taking photos of cosplayers there again. But it was a crazy hot weekend. It was 100+ &amp;#176; F every day there!
It&amp;rsquo;s been three years (2015) since I was at AX. I mostly hung out inside the South hall again. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see as many cosplayers as I thought I would, and I think that may be because of the heat, and that many notable cosplayers/photographers set up near the Staples Center out West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in California. This past week was Anime Expo in Los Angeles, and this coming week will be San Diego Comic Con in well, San Diego.
Like previous years, I attend AX mostly to take pictures of cosplays in the South Hall. Not many people realize that the lighting from the windows and structure of the building acts like a diffuser for most of the day. In other words, it makes LA&amp;rsquo;s harsh light into something fun to work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Photos of 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2014 was a good year for my photography. I did quite a bit of traveling and pushed myself to try some new things. Now that it&amp;rsquo;s 2015, I hope to take more photographs and try some new things out too!
Some goals:  I recently upgraded my SLR Lounge Presets to V6 and look forward to using their system in upcoming projects. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago, I hope to do some more street photos of the great city!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>I attended my third Comikaze Expo (CE) over the weekend, October 31st through November 2nd. I had a great time again. I say this every year&amp;ndash; Comikaze keeps getting bigger and better. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the numbers are, but the attendance on Saturday was pretty big&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;d say probably a 30% increase from last year.
I only went on Friday and Saturday. I did go on Thursday to do an early pick up of my badge&amp;ndash; which is where and when I took the shot below of the Los Angeles Convention Center with the Comikaze Expo sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>Day-0.jpg blogger_id: tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6841384.post-5261524371800133363 blogger_orig_url: http://www.sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html redirect_from: /2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html
headerimage: /images/headers/anime_expo.jpg This year&amp;rsquo;s Anime Expo (AX) has come and gone now. Just like the previous years, I went again to take photos of the cosplayers. For me, AX, has the best collective gatherings of cosplayers I&amp;rsquo;ve ever come across&amp;ndash; although one day I&amp;rsquo;d like to check out DragonCon, which I hear is amazing.
If you just want to see my sets of pictures see below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brief Appearance on Heroes of Cosplay</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</guid>
      <description>In a last week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Heroes of Cosplay, I had a brief appearance in Season 1 - Episode 7!
The episode covered part of the cosplay competition at Stan Lee&amp;rsquo;s Comikaze Expo. I was there in attendance checking out the event and taking photos of many cosplayers and panels.
I appear at about the 2:34 mark as the opening credits are still rolling.
That&amp;rsquo;s me in the Valiant t-shirt behind the DSLR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from 6th St Bridge</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 11:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The 6th St. bridge has a magnificent view of the Los Angeles skyline. There&amp;rsquo;s only a two problems about getting the photo at this location.
First, the area in the Arts district isn&amp;rsquo;t so good. There&amp;rsquo;s little foot traffic and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable bringing expensive equipment to set up there. Second, there are telephone wires running across in the view. I had to use Photoshop to clean that all up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Project Hearts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</guid>
      <description>One evening I took my DSLR and a bokeh kit with a heart-shaped cut out and took a walk down Miracle Mile. I started at LACMA and just walked east on Wilshire and snapped away at all the lights and traffic. I didn&amp;rsquo;t care so much about ISO as I needed to take fast shots of varying lighting situations that came up on the street&amp;ndash; so I just stayed in auto-ISO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Griffith Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</guid>
      <description>I use 500px to do research on where I want to go take pictures and what kind of shots to do. One in particular compelled me to go to Griffith Park to get a shot of the Griffith Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline.
Griffith Observatory Before Sunrise Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59933986 Griffith Observatory (After Sunrise) Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59957370 I went on a different day and night to get a night shot of the Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline (see below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Downtown Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Los Angeles now from traveling to cities like Toronto, San Francisco, and Chicago the past few months. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using 500px to research nice locations for these photos and it&amp;rsquo;s really paid off&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m very happy.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pushing my 500px account for my photos. I&amp;rsquo;ll have a separate blog post on that soon too, once a print I ordered arrives so I can give it a more thorough review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 18:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to Comikaze Expo at the Los Angeles Convention Center. Last year I blogged about my experience and I must say that this year is a huge improvement. I want to share with everyone my thoughts and pictures I took of the convention.
But first I want to say that what Comikaze is doing is important. San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) is getting so big now that many comics/sci-fi/horror fans can&amp;rsquo;t even get tickets or housing to the huge event&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s such a hassle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink and Click LA Downtown Artwalk</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my second Drink and Click LA meetup in downtown Artwalk. Specifically we checked out The Last Bookstore, which is an amazing place to walk around and take photos if you are into books and little trinkets. Generally they ask you to check your bag at what I think is their main entrance, but the other entrance they do not in case you want to bring your camera bag in, which is what we all did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 13:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>Over the Fourth of July week I attended Anime Expo (AX) at the Los Angeles Convention Center (LACC). Last year I went and took over 1500 photos. This year I took over 1700 photos.
Full albums can be found here on G+ (and Facebook&amp;ndash; FB):  Anime Expo 2013 Day 0 Anime Expo 2013 Day 1 Anime Expo 2013 Day 2 Anime Expo 2013 Day 3 
I did not go on Day 4, on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Drink and Click LA Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended my first Drink and Click LA event. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of the group for a while, but just never got around to attending one of their get-togethers. I really had fun talking shop with other photography enthusiasts from beginner to professionals levels. There was time to do some street photos, a little drinking, some eating, and lots of talking.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I attended a photography meetup of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from UnCubed LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/02/pictures-from-uncubed-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/02/pictures-from-uncubed-la/</guid>
      <description>I went to the The UnCubed event here in Los Angeles this past Thursday. I wanted to check out what startups are here in LA and see the panels. It was good event that was extremely relaxed for a job fair. It was right by the beach&amp;ndash; LA style no doubt.
I took pictures here and there, but didn&amp;rsquo;t take any of the actual job fair. I got a chance to see what companies and technologies are at play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stanley Kubrick Exhibit at LACMA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/the-stanley-kubrick-exhibit-at-lacma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/the-stanley-kubrick-exhibit-at-lacma/</guid>
      <description>Today I checked out the Stanley Kubrick Exhibit at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA). To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not all too familiar with Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s work. There are only two of his movies that I can say I watched entirely: Eyes Wide Shut and A.I. Artificial Intelligence. The latter being more Spielberg than Kubrick anyway.
I hear that a lot of people either really like Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s films, or really dislike them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Knight Legend Exhibit at LA Live</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/12/dark-knight-legend-exhibit-at-la-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/12/dark-knight-legend-exhibit-at-la-live/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend on Sunday, I went to check out the Dark Knight Legend Exhibit at LA Live. It&amp;rsquo;s a free exhibit there, located on the top of the parking structure just north of LA Live. The exhibit runs until December 14, 2012.
There&amp;rsquo;s artwork, vehicles, models, props, costumes, and behind the scene videos from all the Batman films throughout the exhibit. I really like how close I could get to the props and costumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Camp LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</guid>
      <description>I picked up a free ticket to Mobile Camp LA earlier this week and decided to attend. Overall I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too impressed with the event. It may have very well been the first of it&amp;rsquo;s kind aimed at developers, designers, and business folk. Anyway, I thought the venue was a bit of a mess as many things went wrong.  Earthquake drill at 10:15am (slightly distracting, but out of their control&amp;ndash; I understand) A lot of sessions held in a one big open space separated by cloth dividers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Code Camp at USC</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended SoCal Code Camp held at University of Southern California (USC). Had a good time learning about new stuff as usual. The prizes here are pretty spectacular, but once again I won absolutely nothing. Nothing!
Like the one I went to earlier this year, this one was also a bit heavy on the .Net side of technology with little representation from Android and iOS, and nothing from Ruby/Rails/Java/etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I checked out the Comikaze Expo at the LA Convention Center (LACC). As far as I know, this was the first &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; comic con taking place in Los Angeles. The previous year&amp;rsquo;s I heard took place in a parking structure or something. But this is a comic con for LA made by fans, for fans. That&amp;rsquo;s their slogan more or less anyway.
Anyway, I had fun and took a lot of pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Day in LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/brazilian-day-in-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/brazilian-day-in-la/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I posted about my visit to Greekfest LA. The following day, Saturday I checked out Brazilian Day LA, which was during the super sunny and hot day. What I loved was that the costumes and culture were so colorful and lively. Pretty much everyone was enjoying themselves watching or dancing along to a nice big neighborhood party.
The parade was pretty awesome too. I just wish the sidewalk for it was a bit bigger and less congested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greekfest LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/greekfest-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/greekfest-la/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I love about living in Los Angeles is all the ethnic fairs that go on. Over the weekend I attended two different fairs no so far from where I live.
On Friday there was LA Greekfest. I went during the evening to avoid the crowd and heat during the day. My favorite dish was the dessert, the pastry puffs.
Full set of pictures can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>A little over a week ago I attended Anime Expo (AX) held at the LA Convention Center. I had a four-day pass for June 29 - July 2, 2012. The last time I attended AX was in 2008, quite a long time ago. I recall being the odd one for not dressing up&amp;ndash; as so so very many people dress up in an anime costume!
So a motivation for attending this year was to take pictures of the costumed attendees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB May Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last evening I attended the LA MongDB May Meetup hosted at Factual. Presentations by Tony Tam (@fehguy), CTO of Wordnik and Andrew Hall, Principal Engineer of uSamp. I had a great time hearing about how mongoDB is being used by two different companies.
In N Out Burgers and fries served instead of pizza! 



Tony Tam presenting 





Andrew Hall presenting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coworking at NextSpace LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</guid>
      <description>Jelly LA held a free coworking day at NextSpace in Culver City this past Friday. I got a little tour of the place and was very impressed. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to a few coworking offices in LA already (CoLoft, BlankSpaces, and Kleverdog), and I can honestly say that this is my favorite to cowork in. One, it&amp;rsquo;s conveniently located in Culver City, where I currently live in. Two, it&amp;rsquo;s got a great amount of space, offices, and little nooks to work in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Summer Conventions</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 20:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</guid>
      <description>There are some conferences and conventions coming up soon that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about. So far I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to Anime Expo and Comic-Con, as I purchased tickets for those already. Recently announced is the G+ Photographers Conference, which includes a Photowalk on Monday, May 21st. I will most likely make my way up there for that&amp;ndash; about eighty-percent sure I&amp;rsquo;ll go.
I plan to take my photography gear to take plenty of pictures too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire in Irwindale, California. It&amp;rsquo;s been over almost fifteen years since I attended a Renaissance Fair, the last being the Bristol Renaissance Fair in the Midwest. I was a teenager then and really loved the tasty mushrooms! I also got my older sister to buy me a broad sword!
A selection of photos I took are below. Full set can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET April Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended the LADOTNET April meetup on&amp;nbsp;Building a Rich Web Experience with jQuery, Ajax and .NET&amp;nbsp;presentation by James Johnson. Good meetup with a very decent turnout considering it was a nice day out and NCAA finals was on
For full set of pictures I&amp;rsquo;ve taken at meetups I&amp;rsquo;ve been to this year, click here.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songkran Festival in LA&#39;s Thaitown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend, on Sunday April 1, 2012, I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Thaitown to check out the Songkran (Thai New Year) celebrations along Hollywood Blvd. They closed Hollywood off from Western all the way to Normandie to have a street festival/parade. I arrived around 11am and spent about 30 minutes just trying to find parking. I ran along Hollywood just in time to catch the beginning of the parade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Last night I attended the Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown meetup. I arrived early and walked to the Walt Disney Concert Hall to do some HDR shots. Upon arriving there, I immediately regretted not bringing my 16-35mm f/2.8 L lens. So made due with my recently purchased 24-105 f/4 L lens, which I really haven&amp;rsquo;t used that much yet.
I spent most of the evening on my own going at my own pace to take pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Photography at Baldwin Hills and LACMA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 12:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I took my camera out to take some photos here in LA.
Some HDR photos taken of the sunset near the Baldwin Hills Scenic Overlook:



 
Some photos taken at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA):
Do you know what this is? Hint, it&amp;rsquo;s a dog&amp;rsquo;s butt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</guid>
      <description>Over this past weekend, on Sunday, the evening of the NBA All-Star game and Academy Awards, I went to check out a Google+ LA Photowalk in Santa Monica hosted by Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson (aka mySpace Tom).
I had a great time seeing and learning how other photography enthusiasts and professionals see things. I brought my Canon 60D, Canon 16-35mm L lens, and tripod. I regret not bringing another lens with me for some more flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my first MongoDB meetup. They have a twitter account: @lamongodb. The meetup was hosted at Factual Inc.
Anand &amp;ldquo;Kumi&amp;rdquo; Nandakumar (@kumi360) presented MongoDB + Node.js design decisions for Jumpspoon. Nuri Halperin presented MongoDB vs. RDBMS.
Overall a good group. I look forward to attend future meetups and learn more about how mongodb is being used.
You can find the pictures I took at meetups in 2012 in this album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Web Guide Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to a Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub meetup at Kleverdog. The topic was&amp;nbsp;Kicking Web Butt: Small Business Web Guide. The presenter was Ed Wu (@edwu) from THINKademic.
The room was primarily designers, which is a nice change for me, as I generally go to developer-centric meetups and events. I hope to be more of a dev-signer (developer/designer).
Here are some of the pictures I took. As usual, you can find the album where I dump all my meetups pictures for this year here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiro Dreams of Sushi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 01:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from watching a special advanced screening of Jiro Dreams of Sushi at the Landmark. Special thanks to Aisha and Foodspotting for putting me on the list!
The documentary is wonderful! Besides the very appealing video of sushi on the big screen, there is quite a story of Jiro Ono and his sushi restaurant, Sukiyabashi Jiro. There certainly is craftsmanship and art to making sushi&amp;ndash; which Jiro has dedicated his life to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 11:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I attended the LADOTNET February meetup held at Blankspaces last night. The event topic was: Start ups, Tech and Business Trends with John Shiple. The attendance was pretty massive as this user group is getting bigger and bigger every month. I enjoyed the speaker and presentation a lot. I do notice that it&amp;rsquo;s a trend that there are a lot of startup businesses growing outside of Silicon Valley.
More speaker information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from SoCal Code Camp</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I attended and volunteered at SoCal Code Camp at California State University Fullerton. I had an awesome time, attended quite a few sessions, learned a lot, and met quite a few good people.
Below are some of the pictures. Full set of pictures can be found here.
Pictures 

Mario Harnandez presenting CSS3 for Web Designers- Let&amp;rsquo;s Design a Visually Appealing Website and Grid Systems - Picking the Right CSS Framework for Your Website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designer&#39;s Hub Meet and Greet</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 06:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub Meet and Greet event hosted at Kleverdog, a co-working space located in Chinatown. This was their first event. It was a very nice meetup about essentially building a community of designers. There were a lot of ideas thrown out about what the group could be about. I personally would like to have a community to turn to, in-person, for me to learn more about the tools and techniques in graphics design&amp;ndash; notably Photoshop, Lightroom, and Aperture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA Ruby/Rails January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 03:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night went to the LA Ruby/Rails Meetup hosted at AT&amp;amp;T Interactive. There were two presentations followed by three lightning talks.
Using Ruby with R by Sean Marcia
Rack Middleware as a General Purpose Abstraction by John Bender
Some of the pictures I took are posted below. You can view the picture dump from all pictures I took here.
As a reminder: LA RubyConf is coming up February 2-4, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LADOTNET January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 11:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to the LADOTNET January Meetup. The presentation was: Unit Testing/Architecting Apps for Testing with Paul Sheriff.
The turn-out for the meetup was pretty big, maybe fifty to sixty people, with a fair amount of recruiters. The LADOTNET meetup was held at Blankspaces. There is an upcoming SoCal Code Camp coming up on the weekend of January 28 and 29, 2012.
I have a new album where I will dump all pictures I take from Meetups for this upcoming year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA DotNet December Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 15:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in living in Los Angeles for two months now. About a month ago I finally bought a car to get around in. On Monday, December 5, 2011, I was able to attend my first the Los Angeles .Net Developer&amp;rsquo;s Group hosted at Blankspaces.
There were two presentations:
 Daniel Egan presented on Diving into Windows Phone Market: Should I make the jump? Henry Lee presented on Making Money with Windows Phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Los Angeles Ruby/Rails Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last week I used my JetBlue BluePass to head out to Los Angeles to attend the LA Ruby Meetup (@laruby) hosted at CoLoft. I was impressed with the turnout, the speakers and presentation, and the audience participation. The format of the meetup was pretty long though. I&amp;rsquo;m used to maybe thirty minutes to one hour of a presentation. They had four presentations lasting about two hours! All very good of course, but I have to admit that it was a bit tiring.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>