<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Best Stuff on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/best/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Best Stuff on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/best/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Books</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/business-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/business-books/</guid>
      <description>This may be bit more of a weird page. As some of these books aren&amp;rsquo;t exactly business or economics exactly&amp;ndash; or rather purely, but they&amp;rsquo;re books I enjoyed.
Companies and the People I love companies such as Amazon, Zappos, Google, Apple, and the people behind such companies. This list is for these great companies I admire to varying degrees.
 Amazonia: Five Years at the Epicenter of the Dot.Com Juggernaut Delivering Happiness: A Path to Profits, Passion, and Purpose The Search: How Google and Its Rivals Rewrote the Rules of Business and Transformed Our Culture Steve Jobs Becoming Steve Jobs  Business and Economics  Founders at Work: Stories of Startups&amp;rsquo; Early Days Rework Making Great Decisions in Business and Life Freakonomics: A Rogue Economist Explores the Hidden Side of Everything Groundswell, Expanded and Revised Edition: Winning in a World Transformed by Social Technologies Millennial Leaders: Success Stories from Today&amp;rsquo;s Most Brilliant Generation &amp;amp; Leaders Traction: A Startup Guide to Getting Customers  Last updated June 14, 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camera Gear</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/camera-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/camera-gear/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Best Camera Is The One That’s With You&amp;rdquo; - Chase Jarvis
I primarily use and recommend Canon gear, and it&amp;rsquo;s not because I&amp;rsquo;m a Canon fanboy or anti-Nikon&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s simply because I started with a Canon DSLR and just stuck with that since 2007. If I had started with Nikon, I probably would be using their products.
Anyway, people often ask me for camera recommendations and I honestly don&amp;rsquo;t know what their needs or lifestyle is like to give them a single answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comics and Graphic Novels</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/comics-and-graphic-novels/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/comics-and-graphic-novels/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve put together a list of my all time favorite comics and graphic novels. I hope you enjoy this list of books I&amp;rsquo;ve read across twenty plus years! I&amp;rsquo;ve organized them by publisher for a more organized look at stuff. For simplicity, I&amp;rsquo;ve categorized the books by publishers since publishers generally represent their own respective universe.
DC Entertainment Since I was little I&amp;rsquo;ve been a fan of both Superman and Batman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentaries</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/documentaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/documentaries/</guid>
      <description> These are some of the best documentaries/videos on the subjects I enjoy.
Comic Books  How to Draw Comics the Marvel Way (1988) The Image Revolution (2014)  Hollywood  The Death of &amp;ldquo;Superman Lives&amp;rdquo;: What Happened? (2015) Electric Boogaloo: The Wild, Untold Story of Cannon Films (2014) Lost Soul: The Doomed Journey of Richard Stanley&amp;rsquo;s Island of Dr. Moreau (2014) Trekkies (1997)  Technology  Project Code Rush - The Beginnings of Netscape / Mozilla Documentary (youTube link) Revolution OS (2001) The Triumph of the Nerds: The Rise of Accidental Empires (1996) The UNIX System: Making Computers More Productive  Toys  The Toys That Made Us (2017)  Video Games  Atari: Game Over (2014) Tetris: From Russia with Love (2004)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Books</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/financial-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/financial-books/</guid>
      <description>These are some of my favorite financial books.
 The Intelligent Investor The Little Book of Common Sense Investing: The Only Way to Guarantee Your Fair Share of Stock Market Returns Becoming an Investor: Building Wealth by Investing in Stocks, Bonds, and Mutual Funds  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac Software</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/mac-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/mac-software/</guid>
      <description>Mac OS X Mavericks is my main operating system now. I still use Windows and Linux a bit, but by far this is where I do most of my work.
I also have a pages for the Best Windows Software and Best Software Development Tools.
For an always up to date list, check out my Best Software List on Github.
Cloud Storage, Sync, and Backup  Dropbox - Service that keeps your files safe, synced, and easy to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography Books</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/photography-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/photography-books/</guid>
      <description>I fell in love with photography a bit in high school during my junior/senior year. Throughout college I pretty much ignored my artistic side in favore of learning about computers and computer science. In 2010 I started to use my DSLR to once again enjoy the art of photography and story telling.
I put together this list of books I found very influential in my ongoing education on everything regarding photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Tools</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/software-development-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/software-development-tools/</guid>
      <description>I love using great tools to help me get my stuff done. These are my favorite tools I must install on my Mac or Windows for software development.
I also have pages for Best Mac Software and Best Windows Software.
Also see my dotfiles.
For an always up to date list, check out my Best Software List on Github.
Coding and IDE  Android Studio - Android SDK and official IDE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows Software</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/best/windows-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/best/windows-software/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve put together a list of the best software for Windows PCs. These are all free, unless otherwise noted.
I have a pages for Best Mac Software and Best Software Development Tools.
For an always up to date list, check out my Best Software List on Github.
Cloud Storage, Sync, and Backup  Drobo - Get the software, after the hardware. Google Drive - Google&amp;rsquo;s cloud service tied to your Gmail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>