<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 17:07:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Different Screen Resolutions Wallpaper Project</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/different-screen-resolutions-wallpaper-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 17:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/different-screen-resolutions-wallpaper-project/</guid>
      <description>When I design websites and always wonder what the site would look like on different screen resolutions. I don&amp;rsquo;t always have all the devices to test the layout on, so I generally will prefer to resize my browser window. I once had a wallpaper that had different screen resolutions marked out, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it or google it. So I decided to make my own.
I joined Pixelapse.com and made a desktop wallpaper project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Design of Everyday Things</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 16:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</guid>
      <description>The Design of Everyday Things comes highly recommended on Coding Horror&amp;rsquo;s recommended reading list as well as many other software developers. After giving it a read, I thought it was good, relevant today, but slightly dated with their examples.
After reading the book, I am reminded of the light switch to my bathroom in my current apartment in Los Angeles. See below.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a horrible design! The left-most button, which is red, is for off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Web Guide Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to a Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub meetup at Kleverdog. The topic was&amp;nbsp;Kicking Web Butt: Small Business Web Guide. The presenter was Ed Wu (@edwu) from THINKademic.
The room was primarily designers, which is a nice change for me, as I generally go to developer-centric meetups and events. I hope to be more of a dev-signer (developer/designer).
Here are some of the pictures I took. As usual, you can find the album where I dump all my meetups pictures for this year here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tropicana&#39;s New Logo Design</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/tropicanas-new-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/tropicanas-new-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>This morning I had a peanut butter and jelly sandwich, toasted. It was delicious. Along with it I had some orange juice (OJ), but not just any OJ, Minute Maid OJ.

For years I&amp;rsquo;ve been more of a Tropicana OJ kind-of-guy, but with Tropicana&amp;rsquo;s somewhat recent logo switch on their cartons, I just felt compelled to switch.
The reason? I just don&amp;rsquo;t get why they changed their logo.
What they had before made sense (see left carton).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>