<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>M1 Finance</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/10/m1-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 17:00:34 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/10/m1-finance/</guid>
      <description>Lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending a lot of time reading books and watching youTube videos on investing. For years I&amp;rsquo;ve heard a lot about the Robinhood and Acorns apps, but there was nothing about them that made me want to try them out, or move away from my traditional brokerages. It&amp;rsquo;s great that they have mobile apps and free trades for young investors and beginners, but I&amp;rsquo;d rather do my investments carefully on the desktop browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrated Website to Hugo</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/09/migrated-website-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 03:03:14 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/09/migrated-website-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Over the past week I migrated my blog from using static site generator, Jekyll to use Hugo. I also switched hosts from Github Pages to Netlify.
The main reasons for the changes are:
 Jekyll/Ruby is just too slow as a static site generator in development/production. Hugo/Go is fast. Wanted to try out Netlify.  When I wrote new posts with Jekyll, it was painfully slow to build the site after any small set of changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Celebration</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/04/star-wars-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/04/star-wars-celebration/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to Star Wars Celebration in Chicago. This was my first Celebration event I attended so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure what to expect. Overall, I&amp;rsquo;d say it was fun and very doable event for its size. What I mean by this is that larger cons like San Diego Comic Con is super fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also super large where it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to do all the things you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2019</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended C2E2 at Chicago&amp;rsquo;s McCormick Place once again. It&amp;rsquo;a convention I recommend to all my Chicago friends to attend as it&amp;rsquo;s very convenient to attend and is quite affordable since they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to travel far.
If you weren&amp;rsquo;t able to attend, check out SyFy Wire&amp;rsquo;s youTube channel. They have videos of most if not all the panels that happened at C2E2 as well as many other conventions across the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/san-diego-comic-con-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/san-diego-comic-con-2018/</guid>
      <description>Another year, another Comic Con (SDCC) in the bag!
The programming for this year&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con was different than other years as some of the big studios were not there&amp;ndash; namely Marvel Studios and HBO. I can understand Marvel Studios not being there this year, as they are between the Infinity War movies. They don&amp;rsquo;t want to give much information away in regards to how things are going to be in the coming movies and the next phase of their movie/storytelling development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was at Anime Expo (AX). In general it was super fun to be taking photos of cosplayers there again. But it was a crazy hot weekend. It was 100+ &amp;#176; F every day there!
It&amp;rsquo;s been three years (2015) since I was at AX. I mostly hung out inside the South hall again. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see as many cosplayers as I thought I would, and I think that may be because of the heat, and that many notable cosplayers/photographers set up near the Staples Center out West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadpool 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</guid>
      <description>I watched Deadpool 2 over the weekend and I thought the movie was just okay. The movie was done in a Deadpool way, which is both good and bad. This is my review.
Spoilers below of course.
The Good The movie is made for comic fans and those familiar with comic book pop culture. Deadpool&amp;rsquo;s character in the comics and movies is very meta in it&amp;rsquo;s commentary of comics, pop culture, current events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avengers Infinity War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</guid>
      <description>Destiny has arrived. I watched the Avengers: Infinity War twice already and I loved it. The first time was the most emotional and suprising, the second time I caught some dialogue I missed and was more relaxed.
It&amp;rsquo;s been over three years since Kevin Feige announced the plans for MCU Phase 3, and ten years since the first movie. This is the culmination of everthing that has come before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</guid>
      <description>This year&amp;rsquo;s C2E2 was by far the largest and busiest I&amp;rsquo;ve been to. There seemed to be a bigger space rented out for the event over at McCormick Place. I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to apply for a press pass this year and just went ahead and bought a 3-day pass. I&amp;rsquo;ve been denied 2 years in a row now and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like applying&amp;ndash; perhaps next year.
Like many other comic conventions, C2E2 offers mailing of purchased badges if they are bought before a deadline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Panther</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed the Black Panther movie. The story, the characters, and especially the villain was well balanced and defined in this Marvel movie. This is my spoilery review.
The Good The characters were really solid. It&amp;rsquo;s an all-star cast!
Letitia Wright is amazing as Black Panther&amp;rsquo;s sister, Shuri. She was having fun and it really showed. She&amp;rsquo;s also starred in an episode of Black Mirror: Black Museum.
Michael B. Jordan knocked it out of the park as Erik Killmonger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies of 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>This looks like a good year for not just comic book fans, but fans of books and other franchises because there are so many sequels coming out. This is why I dropped doing comic book only movies for my posts and opened it up to all movies.
Here are my top 8 movies that I think will be hits:
 Avengers: Infinity War Black Panther Ready Player One Incredibles 2 Ant-Man and The Wasp Deadpool 2 Alita: Battle Angel Venom  Quick Thoughts Black Panther - February 16, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars The Last Jedi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</guid>
      <description>I loved Star Wars The Last Jedi. The movie is brilliant. I&amp;rsquo;ve only watched it once as of this posting and I plan on watching it a few more times to catch all the little things I may have missed.
Spoilers below of course.
Empire and Return The movie has similarities to both Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi.
The dark tones are similar to Empire. The failure of Luke Skywalker and the entire Jedi Order was touched upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice League</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</guid>
      <description>I am pretty disappointed in the Justice League (JL) movie. I went in with low expectations since it is a Zack Snyder movie that was finished by Joss Whedon. I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed Man of Steel and Batman vs Superman where I&amp;rsquo;ve complained about Snyder as a director. Despite Whedon&amp;rsquo;s involvement, JL suffers more of the same&amp;ndash; great visually with unappealing characters and story.
Spoilers below of course.
What I Liked Gal Gadot looks amazing as Wonder Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thor Ragnarok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</guid>
      <description>I really liked Thor: Ragnarok. By far it was the best Thor movie from the MCU and maybe even the best Marvel movie of 2017. There&amp;rsquo;s not much to complain about in the movie. Spoilers ahead.
What I Liked The movie is a blend of Planet Hulk and Ragnarok story from the comics. Since Marvel can&amp;rsquo;t do Hulk movies&amp;ndash; due to movie rights sitting with Universal, they just incorporated one of his best stories in with Thor&amp;rsquo;s to make a buddy space adventure and comedy movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/san-diego-comic-con-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/san-diego-comic-con-2017/</guid>
      <description>San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) has come and gone. This year marks my seventh year going to SDCC! Each year I have a good time, but every year it becomes less about the convention floor, offsite experiences, and buying stuff. Going to the con is now more about taking photos and attending panels.
Cosplay I love taking photos of cosplayers, but it&amp;rsquo;s really difficult to be at the right place at the right time to catch some of the awesome cosplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>Spider-Man: Homecoming is a good, coming-of-age movie aimed at younger fans and those young at heart. I liked it on a few levels, but also felt distant because I&amp;rsquo;m older and watched other Spidey and superhero films since the early 1990s.
The Good I like how Tom Holland actually looks like a teenager. I&amp;rsquo;ve always preferred the younger teen Spider-Man that makes quips in battles. Toby Maquire looked too old for high school and Andrew Garfield too handsome/hipster/cool to be Peter Parker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder Woman</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</guid>
      <description>I watched the Wonder Woman movie twice, didn&amp;rsquo;t like it much the first time, but enjoyed it more the second time. My initial reaction after the first viewing was rather harsh on the movie, and I think it had to do with how close I sat and how much my eyes had to travel when looking at the screen. The second time I sat further back in a sweet spot, and my eyes were more relaxed to enjoy the movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Central 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/anime-central-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/anime-central-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was at Anime Central (ACen) which was hosted at the Donald E. Stephens Convention Center. This was my second time attending, and I was also given a press pass again.
I stuck around the main entrance hall/lobby for most of the convention hoping to catch cosplayers on their way in or out of the exhibit hall. It seemed this year a lot of cosplayers were more casual and spent more time in the exhibit hall than the entrance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed watching Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2, it&amp;rsquo;s what a space adventure movie should be! What I especially love about the movie is that every character has his/her moment in the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s a great sequel to the amazing first movie.
The movie has FIVE post credit scenes, yes 5, so be sure to stay through the entire credit scroll to catch them all. This is my spoiler filled review of the movie, so read no further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched the movie yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to C2E2 over at McCormick Place. Once again I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to obtain a press pass, so I went as a civilian photographer&amp;ndash; I bought my 3-day pass. Every year I&amp;rsquo;m going to try, and every year I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to get denied!
C2E2 isn&amp;rsquo;t too big that it&amp;rsquo;s uncomfortable to go as an individual or even as a family. McCormick Place is huge and there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room to expand in case the crowd size does ever get bigger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</guid>
      <description>I liked the movie, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t love Logan. It was the best Wolverine movie Fox has made, but that bar is rather low to clear. After 17 years of playing the character, it was a good send off for Hugh Jackman. He really made the character his own over the years, despite being different from the comics-Wolverine character.
The Good What I liked about the movie is that it continues to stay true to movie-Wolverine character that Jackman has made in his solo movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Book Movies of 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote a post about Super Hero Movies of 2016. I wanted to do the same for 2017, as it looks to be another amazing year for comic fans.
2017 Rankings This is the ranking, 1-6, ranked from most looking forward to, to least.
 Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 (May 5, 2017) Wonder Woman (June 2, 2017) Thor: Ragnarok (November 3, 2017) Justice League (November 17, 2017) Spiderman: Homecoming (July 7, 2017) Logan (March 3, 2017)  Logan I cannot get excited about Fox&amp;rsquo;s Logan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Strange</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</guid>
      <description>The last MCU movie for 2016, Doctor Strange came out last week. This is my spoilery review which covers some plot points and my thoughts of it&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on the movie universe.
I really enjoyed the movie. It was an origin movie that formally introduced magic and the multiverse into Marvel&amp;rsquo;s cinematic universe. This is a big deal because it opens the door to infinite possibilities for how they wish to expand or even link universes together&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at Fox&amp;rsquo;s Deadpool/X-Men franchise here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</guid>
      <description>My quick non-spoiler-y thoughts on Suicide Squad:
I went in with low expectations, overall, the movie was just okay. I was entertained, but not blown away by anything. If you are expecting what you saw the trailers, you are probably going to be disappointed. It&amp;rsquo;s worth a watch if you want to keep up with the DC movie universe.
Disclaimer: I watched the movie for free with my T-Mobile Tuesday App, which gave me free tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/07/san-diego-comic-con-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/07/san-diego-comic-con-2016/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from San Diego Comic Con and I&amp;rsquo;m super exhausted! My sisters and I were lucky this year and we got rooms at the Manchester Grand Hyatt, just a few blocks away from the convention center. I even nabbed myself a Superman Conan FunkoPop that was being raffled away in the very same hotel we were staying at!
The weather was hot as the sun was unforgiving most of the time during the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warcraft Movie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is my review for the Warcraft movie, which is based off the video game.
I normally give a spoiler warning, but I won&amp;rsquo;t say enough about the plot of the movie to ruin anyone&amp;rsquo;s experience. But in case you are sensitive to any information and want to go in fresh, then you should stop reading now&amp;ndash; but I doubt that since you&amp;rsquo;ve read this far already.
I do have some background in playing Warcraft III, World of Warcraft (WoW), Hearthstone, and other games from Blizzard Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-Men Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>This is my spoiler filled review for the latest X-Men movie. I also talk about all the previous X-Men movies. It won&amp;rsquo;t be pretty.
I did not care for X-Men: Apocalypse.
I went in with low expectations and came out disappointed with what I saw. This is coming from someone who read some of the X-Men comics as well as watched the 1990s animated TV series.
The problem is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie where things happen, has characters from the X-Men universe, but in name only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Central 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/anime-central-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/anime-central-2016/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended Anime Central, also known as ACen. I was given a press pass and attended all three days, May 20-22nd. My main goal was to take photos of cosplayers in and out of the Donald E. Stephens Convention Center. ACen is the Midwest&amp;rsquo;s largest anime, manga, and Japanese pop culture convention. It&amp;rsquo;s the third largest anime convention, but in recent news I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it&amp;rsquo;s the second now, behind Anime Expo (AX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain America: Civil War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>This is my Captain America: Civil War review that contains spoilers, so if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the movie yet, please stop reading now! I also provide some insights and predictions on what&amp;rsquo;s to come. I also assume you&amp;rsquo;ve seen all the movies in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) to date.
I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the movie twice now and I really like it. I even enjoyed it more the second time. Not only does it complete a trilogy of the Captain America movies, it also sets up Phase 3 of the MCU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Console Wars</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Console Wars by Blake J. Harris and I really enjoyed the trip down memory lane. I grew up in the 1980s and 1990s and played on video game systems by Nintendo, Sega, Sony, and Atari. This is my reflection on this gaming era after reading this book.
Console Wars tells the story of Tom Kalinske, an American business man and CEO behind Sega of America during its meteoric rise and fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batman v Superman Dawn of Justice Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I saw Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice. In a nutshell, I thought it was okay, but not great&amp;ndash; nor does it match the hype. This post does contain SPOILERS, so don&amp;rsquo;t read any further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it yet or don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned&amp;hellip;.
I reviewed Man of Steel several years ago and gave it a generally positive review for a sci-fi Superman reimagining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to check out C2E2. It was the second year that I&amp;rsquo;ve attended the show. This year, I went all three days, unlike last year. The cosplay this year was amazing&amp;ndash; every year cosplayers keep upping their game.
Friday The main purpose of Day 1 was to pick up my lanyard, get a lay of the land, walk the exhibit hall, and determine whether I would be permitted to take photos from different positions in the main stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Hero Movies of 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year (2016), is looking to be an amazing year for comic book and superhero fans. There are so many movies coming out from both Marvel and DC that it&amp;rsquo;s a stark reminder how great it is to be a fan. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, this post is spoiler free for both the movies (since I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen them nor have they come out yet) and the source materials, the comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Willis Tower and John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago my niece visited Chicago for the first time and I took her around to see and eat some of the best my city has to offer. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve visited John Hancock Observatory before, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been up to Willis Tower (specifically the Skydeck) since it was called the Sears Tower.
The challenge with taking photos at these locations was that we went up right after it rained and there were a lot of cloud/fog surrounding Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Format your Hard Drive into exFAT</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/how-to-format-your-hard-drive-into-exfat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/how-to-format-your-hard-drive-into-exfat/</guid>
      <description>With Black Friday and Cyber Monday behind us and the upcoming holidays upon us, some of you may be getting a new external hard drive(s) for your Mac or Windows system(s). I wanted to write up a guide on how to format your drive into exFAT, the format that is well supported and ideal for many cases.
The Benefits of exFAT A few years ago, I wrote about how hard drives marketed to Apple devices are over-priced and are functionally the same as their Windows counterpart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Open House Chicago 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Sunday I went to checkout Open House Chicago and did a little photowalk of my own. I actually had no plan to go until my sister gave me her priority pass the morning of. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did as it was not only had some good photops, but was a nice steps in too since I use FitBit.
The places I visited:
 The Oriental Theatre Joffrey Ballet Aon Center Continental Illinois Bank Building The Rookery  My favorite spot was the Aon Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adams/Wabash CTA Station</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was in Chicago with hopes of getting some nice photos of Chicago henge&amp;ndash; basically the fall equinox where the sunset lines up straight with the East-West street grid. But there were some clouds in the sky which prevented any starburst from happening. However, I went early enough to do some exploring around downtown for other fun shots.
In particular I hopped on the CTA and looked for some train shots on the &amp;lsquo;L&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Apple&#39;s Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/thoughts-on-apples-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/thoughts-on-apples-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday, Apple had their livestream event (September 9, 2015) announcing a bunch of new things. As usual, I live tweeted some of my thoughts during the keynote. For the most part, my tweets are meant to poke fun at everything and shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be taken in the most serious context. I say this because some contacts I have take great personal insult whenever I poke fun of big successful companies like Apple&amp;ndash; that are named Apple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Photos in Cosplay Culture Magazine</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Halloween edition of Cosplay Culture magazine came out on newsstands. There is an article on San Diego Comic Con that features my photos in it. The article is a ten whopping page spread! This all started from a simple comment on an instagram photo.
You can find this magazine at Barnes and Noble, Target, Walmart, Ralph&amp;rsquo;s, Walgreens, CVS, and other major newsstands and comic shops. I found my copies at B&amp;amp;N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Jetbrains Toolbox is Good</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/why-jetbrains-toolbox-is-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/why-jetbrains-toolbox-is-good/</guid>
      <description>Jetbrains, a software company that creates a wealth of software IDEs for software developers recently announced that they are moving their software over to a software-as-a-service (SaaS) platform called Jetbrains Toolbox.
These are the times we live in now, and I think it&amp;rsquo;s good&amp;ndash; for the most part.
Buy or Subscribe? Traditionally, people buy a software version and own it. For many, they don&amp;rsquo;t buy an upgrade when it&amp;rsquo;s available and may only upgrade when money is available or if they feel the new features are worth it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago River from Lake Shore Drive</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</guid>
      <description>I had some spare time before dinner near Navy Pier to take some pictures of the Chicago River off Lake Shore Drive. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to take photos at this location, but never was in the area during the right time. I had about a forty minutes during sunset to grab some shots and then run off to dinner.
This was my favorite shot I took.
There were some challenges to getting this photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed reading Andy Weir&amp;rsquo;s book, The Martian. It reads mostly like a series of journal entries of the protagonist, Mark Watney who&amp;rsquo;s stuck on Mars. If you are a science buff, there&amp;rsquo;s some interesting things that occur in terms of problem solving which Mythbuster Adam Savage, has said he would love to try at his Comic Con panel.
It&amp;rsquo;s also a quick read, as you may find yourself flying through the chapters as they are a bit short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went to Trey Ratcliff&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Photowalk. I had fun walking from the Adler Planetarium toward the Bean. As usual on my many photowalks, I tend to stray from the large groups and do my own thing. I just find it difficult to get shots I want around dozens or in this case hundreds of other photographers.
This event was actually my second time that I met Trey. The first time was a few years ago at a Santa Monica Photowalk along with MySpace Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Armada</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I read Ernest Cline&amp;rsquo;s book, Ready Player One. I blogged about my love for the book and how excited I was that a movie was being made. Quick update, it&amp;rsquo;s getting a release date of December 15, 2017! However, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I liked his second book, Armada, nearly as much.
In a nutshell the book is The Last Starfigther meets Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game. It&amp;rsquo;s a coming of age story of a teenager that plays video games, struggles with his place in the world, and has pop culture knowledge of things from the 80s forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus, A Year Later</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/oneplus-a-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/oneplus-a-year-later/</guid>
      <description>I consider the OnePlus One I bought over a year ago a value phone&amp;ndash; best phone for the buck you spend. For it&amp;rsquo;s time, it was a big phone, with fantastic specs, for a low price. Even now, it&amp;rsquo;s still a good phone and is my main mobile device. The battery is good and CM12S operating system is also decent.
When I initially had CM11S running on my phone, the battery life was 2 days of regular usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Theatre</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</guid>
      <description>A couple nights ago I was in downtown Chicago for a meetup at Chicago Ruby. Since I found cheap parking via Parking Panda, I figured afterwards I would spend a little time taking some photos of the famous Chicago Theatre.
The challenge of taking the photo at this location at night was that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people and cars moving or idling on both sides of the street. On top of that, to my left was a camera crew filming what I assume to be something for either a TV show or commercial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/san-diego-comic-con-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/san-diego-comic-con-2015/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in San Diego for Comic Con. This year marks my fifth time that I&amp;rsquo;ve been to San Diego Comic Con.
This month of July also marks twenty years since I attended my first comic convention in Chicago, when it was then known as Chicago Comic Con (it was bought by Wizard World in 1997).
The Good As usual, it&amp;rsquo;s always fun to go to the biggest geek party in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in California. This past week was Anime Expo in Los Angeles, and this coming week will be San Diego Comic Con in well, San Diego.
Like previous years, I attend AX mostly to take pictures of cosplays in the South Hall. Not many people realize that the lighting from the windows and structure of the building acts like a diffuser for most of the day. In other words, it makes LA&amp;rsquo;s harsh light into something fun to work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated with Elon Musk and his companies: Tesla Motors and SpaceX. I recently read, Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future by Ashlee Vance just to learn a bit more about him.
I like to read books on some of the best entrepreneurs and companies in modern times. Everyone from Bill Gates, Michael Dell, Jeff Bezos, Tony Hsieh, Jason Fried, Larry Page, Sergey Brin, to Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LastPass Password Manager</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/lastpass-password-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/lastpass-password-manager/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week news broke that LastPass had been hacked. They released a blog post: LastPass Security Notice.
I still believe that LastPass is a great service.
I don&amp;rsquo;t hold it against them for not getting an email right away. I found out about the issue from social media&amp;ndash; basically word-of-mouth. Which to be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m fine with. I&amp;rsquo;m just glad that when there is a problem that Internet people bring it up and share it right away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</guid>
      <description>I own several copies of the book, Ready Player One, by Ernest Cline. I have it in hardcover, softcover, and digitally on Amazon Kindle. I only do this for a few books&amp;ndash; the ones I really enjoy. Off the top of my head, another is Jurassic Park by Michael Crichton.
This post is spoiler-free. Read it knowing that you can still fully enjoy the book and upcoming movie.
The Book The book paints a picture of a dystopian future, the year 2044, where people are plugged away in a virtual reality based world, OASIS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, I finished the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson and I wrote a blog post too. For the time it was released, I would say the published book collected the most information on Steve Jobs out there. Isaacson generally gives a negative review of Jobs with multiple repetitions of reality distortion field throughout the book. The book focuses a little more on the bad relationships than the good ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today&#39;s Tech TV Shows</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/todays-tech-tv-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/todays-tech-tv-shows/</guid>
      <description>There are two tech TV shows that I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying right now: Silicon Valley and Halt and Catch Fire.
They both deal with the business and culture of technology startups, but yet are pretty different from each other. They are both on their second seasons.
Silicon Valley pokes fun at the today&amp;rsquo;s tech craze in a humorous and ridiculous way. As it should be, technology is hot stuff right now and there&amp;rsquo;s so much money being thrown around as everyone thinks they are going to change the world with their product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones Epic History</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/game-of-thrones-epic-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/game-of-thrones-epic-history/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of Game of Thrones like I am? Have you checked out Comic Book Girl 19&amp;rsquo;s (CBG19) youTube videos on this book/show?
Well, you should. Her epic history videos cover all the major houses (Baratheon, Stark, Targaryen, and Lannister). She has other videos too.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the books like me, her videos helps me appreciate the TV show immensely. I previously blogged about my Top 5 YouTube Channels for Comic Geeks, and she&amp;rsquo;s listed there as being one of my favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moved from Blogger to Jekyll</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/moved-from-blogger-to-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/moved-from-blogger-to-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>I recently made the move from Blogger to Jekyll, hosted on Github Pages. It was a pretty pleasant conversion too, as Jekyll has a good amount of documenation and support.
I&amp;rsquo;ve had a blog since 1999. I&amp;rsquo;ve used just about every known blogging technology/platform out there. I&amp;rsquo;ve used perl, php, mysql, ASP, MS Access, ASP.NET, C#, MS SQL, Postgres, Ruby on Rails, Heroku, Apache Web Server, IIS, etc to write my own blogging software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 YouTube Channels for Comic Geeks</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s such an amazing time to be a comic book fan/geek. From movies to TV shows and merchandising, all the way to comic cons, there&amp;rsquo;s just so much content to consume that it can be a bit overwhelming. I don&amp;rsquo;t really watch TV anymore and just rely on my social media feed, websites, and youTube for all my news and entertainment. So there are a few YouTube channels that I absolutely love and would recommend to my friends and comic fans alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</guid>
      <description>This past Sunday I went to check out Chicago&amp;rsquo;s very own C2E2 at McCormick Place. I only went for one day unfortunately, but I had a good time walking the floor and taking pictures here and there. I really do find this con to be better than Wizard World Chicago. Not only is it bigger, with room to expand at McCormick, but the fans and cosplayers were in abundance. In short, it was way more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Map Your Mouse&#39;s Back and Forward Buttons on a Mac</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/map-your-mouses-back-and-forward-buttons-on-a-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/map-your-mouses-back-and-forward-buttons-on-a-mac/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using OS X as my main OS for almost five years now. But one thing that&amp;rsquo;s bugged me for a while was the lack of support for Logitech and other mice&amp;rsquo;s forward and back buttons. These are mouse shortcut buttons found on many gaming mice. As much as I enjoy Apple&amp;rsquo;s trackpad, I still like to use the mouse for gaming and other things.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of my mouse with the buttons that under Windows, normally maps to forward and back in the web browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott McCloud at Chicago Humanities Festival</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/02/scott-mccloud-at-chicago-humanities-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/02/scott-mccloud-at-chicago-humanities-festival/</guid>
      <description>This past Friday the Chicago Humanities Festival had Scott McCloud at the Art Institute. Not many of my friends and family know that Mr. McCloud was a big influence during my teenage and high school years.
Back in the nineties, I was a big comic book reader. Besides being a reader, I also loved doodling and drawing. But after a while, I wanted to know more about the history, art, and motivations of the comic book creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Recommend Adobe Photoshop Lightroom</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/why-i-recommend-adobe-photoshop-lightroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/why-i-recommend-adobe-photoshop-lightroom/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few years, friends have been asked me photography questions in terms of camera gear and software. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;ll write a post in the future on physical camera gear, but for this post I wanted to cover why I love using Adobe Photoshop Lightroom and why you should consider it for your photo needs.
Adobe Lightroom is essentially a trimmed down version of Photoshop (PS) with features built in for a Photography workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Photos of 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2014 was a good year for my photography. I did quite a bit of traveling and pushed myself to try some new things. Now that it&amp;rsquo;s 2015, I hope to take more photographs and try some new things out too!
Some goals:  I recently upgraded my SLR Lounge Presets to V6 and look forward to using their system in upcoming projects. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago, I hope to do some more street photos of the great city!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Road Trip From LA to Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Last week I drove from Los Angeles back to my hometown of Chicago. I&amp;rsquo;ve moved back home for personal reasons. It took my sister and I nine days to get across the US&amp;ndash; mostly just eating, driving, sleeping, and taking pictures.
The states I drove through were (in order):
 California Arizona Utah Colorado Kansas Missouri Illinois  
The first half of the trip from California to Colorado was rather scenic and interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Museum of California&#39;s SDCC Exhibit</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</guid>
      <description>The Oakland Museum of California has one of my photos from San Diego Comic Con on display in their exhibit: Sunshine and Superheroes: San Diego Comic-Con. A few days ago I had the opportunity to visit and took some photos.
The exhibit runs from May 23, 2014 to May 31, 2015.
Below is the photo I took at SDCC in 2013 that they used. It&amp;rsquo;s taken on the escalators leading up to the ticket booths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>I attended my third Comikaze Expo (CE) over the weekend, October 31st through November 2nd. I had a great time again. I say this every year&amp;ndash; Comikaze keeps getting bigger and better. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the numbers are, but the attendance on Saturday was pretty big&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;d say probably a 30% increase from last year.
I only went on Friday and Saturday. I did go on Thursday to do an early pick up of my badge&amp;ndash; which is where and when I took the shot below of the Los Angeles Convention Center with the Comikaze Expo sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Beach Comic Con 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/long-beach-comic-con-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/long-beach-comic-con-2014/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I attended Long Beach Comic Con (LBCC) with my first press pass. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve attended LBCC, two years to be exact. Back then I only went on a Sunday, but this year I attended on a Saturday to get a more full experience.
What I enjoyed about LBCC is that it&amp;rsquo;s a small con without the hassle of a big convention like San Diego Comic Con.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building my own Photography Site</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/building-my-own-photography-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 18:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/building-my-own-photography-site/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my SmugMug account expired and I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to renew it. This is where my photography website, Sunpech Photography, used to be hosted. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t fully utilizing it to make sales nor was I pushing it very much to friends, family, and even clients. So I couldn&amp;rsquo;t justify spending any money on it when I&amp;rsquo;d rather make sales on 500px and 500px Art.
Surprisingly my account was discontinued almost immediately and I whipped up a decent site in less than 24 hours along with appropriate DNS changes just so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an ugly 404 page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus One vs Nexus 5</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/oneplus-one-vs-nexus-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/oneplus-one-vs-nexus-5/</guid>
      <description>Last month in July, I purchased two Android phones: The Nexus 5 (N5) and the OnePlus One (OPO). I initially ordered the Nexus 5 because I was sick of waiting for an OnePlus invite that I signed up for in April. Up until then, I was using a Galaxy Nexus for two years and its overall performance was rather sluggish and could no longer hold a charge for half a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagram, the Better Twitter?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/instagram-the-better-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/instagram-the-better-twitter/</guid>
      <description>I like Twitter for following interesting people and entities. But lately, I&amp;rsquo;ve taken to Instagram more because it can also be interesting and more visually pleasing since each post has a picture telling a story.
I know Twitter has updated features to display images in web and mobile apps now, but most tweets do not have any picture whatsoever&amp;ndash; even though tweets with pictures have twice the amount of engagements over those that do not have a picture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Skyline</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/san-diego-skyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/san-diego-skyline/</guid>
      <description>I really like the city of San Diego. It&amp;rsquo;s a very clean city with little to no smog in the air, unlike Los Angeles.
I was there for Comic Con a few days early last week. So I put aside some time to go take pictures of the skyline from Coronado Island. I did a little research on 500px and picked a spot that had a clear shot of the skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/san-diego-comic-con-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/san-diego-comic-con-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last week I as in San Diego for Comic Con (SDCC). This visit marks my fourth visit to San Diego&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con, with next year (2015) marking twenty years since I attended my first comic con in Chicago. I cannot believe it&amp;rsquo;s been that long since I first ventured into a convention

This year I didn&amp;rsquo;t take as many pictures as I did in previous years. I think it&amp;rsquo;s mostly because I&amp;rsquo;m more interested in attending panels and enjoying myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>Day-0.jpg blogger_id: tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6841384.post-5261524371800133363 blogger_orig_url: http://www.sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html redirect_from: /2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html
headerimage: /images/headers/anime_expo.jpg This year&amp;rsquo;s Anime Expo (AX) has come and gone now. Just like the previous years, I went again to take photos of the cosplayers. For me, AX, has the best collective gatherings of cosplayers I&amp;rsquo;ve ever come across&amp;ndash; although one day I&amp;rsquo;d like to check out DragonCon, which I hear is amazing.
If you just want to see my sets of pictures see below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos of Naver Line Friends</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/photos-of-naver-line-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/photos-of-naver-line-friends/</guid>
      <description>I was in Chiang Mai, Thailand recently and found some Naver Line toys at the mall. I bought them with the intention of giving them to my sisters since we all use the Line chat app. But on the way back to the US, I had an eight hour layover at the Incheon International airport in South Korea. I happened to pack the toys in my carry-on so I took them out to have a little photo shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting Your VHS and Betamax Tapes to Digital</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/converting-your-vhs-and-betamax-tapes-to-digital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/converting-your-vhs-and-betamax-tapes-to-digital/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve started a new initiative to help my parents convert all their VHS and Betamax tapes over into the digital world. These tapes are those precious family home videos. These are mostly tapes from the 1970s, 80s, 90s, and even part of the early 2000s.
In today&amp;rsquo;s times we should all be capturing everything in digital format already. From DSLRs, HD camcorders, to even our smartphones. We just need a way to bring the past thirty plus years of our lives into the modern age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brief Appearance on Heroes of Cosplay</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</guid>
      <description>In a last week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Heroes of Cosplay, I had a brief appearance in Season 1 - Episode 7!
The episode covered part of the cosplay competition at Stan Lee&amp;rsquo;s Comikaze Expo. I was there in attendance checking out the event and taking photos of many cosplayers and panels.
I appear at about the 2:34 mark as the opening credits are still rolling.
That&amp;rsquo;s me in the Valiant t-shirt behind the DSLR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroku Postgres Maintenance Requires Manually Updating DATABASE_URL</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/heroku-postgres-maintenance-requires-manually-updating-database_url/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2014 08:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/heroku-postgres-maintenance-requires-manually-updating-database_url/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week I got an email from Heroku that one of my postgres databases required maintenance. This is the email:
bot (Heroku Support) Apr 25 14:02 Your database HEROKU_POSTGRESQL_COLOR_URL on &amp;lt;project_name&amp;gt; requires maintenance. During this period, your database credentials will become read-only. Once it has completed, your database URL will have changed, but we will update your app&#39;s config variables accordingly. This automated maintenance is a necessary part of our Starter tier plans, Dev and Basic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Different Screen Resolutions Wallpaper Project</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/different-screen-resolutions-wallpaper-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2014 17:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/04/different-screen-resolutions-wallpaper-project/</guid>
      <description>When I design websites and always wonder what the site would look like on different screen resolutions. I don&amp;rsquo;t always have all the devices to test the layout on, so I generally will prefer to resize my browser window. I once had a wallpaper that had different screen resolutions marked out, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it or google it. So I decided to make my own.
I joined Pixelapse.com and made a desktop wallpaper project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500px Art Prints</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/500px-art-prints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 12:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/500px-art-prints/</guid>
      <description>I was recently featured in a 500px blog post, Celebrating 3 Months of 500px Art! The new site launched back in December and I&amp;rsquo;ve actually bought several of my prints just to see what the quality was like.
Below are some photos from two separate orders I made. The packaging is really well done, and they consolidated two prints into one big box.
Overall they&amp;rsquo;re pretty good. 500px offers canvas, paper, aluminum, acrylic, and birchwood as print material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from 6th St Bridge</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 11:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The 6th St. bridge has a magnificent view of the Los Angeles skyline. There&amp;rsquo;s only a two problems about getting the photo at this location.
First, the area in the Arts district isn&amp;rsquo;t so good. There&amp;rsquo;s little foot traffic and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable bringing expensive equipment to set up there. Second, there are telephone wires running across in the view. I had to use Photoshop to clean that all up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Project Hearts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</guid>
      <description>One evening I took my DSLR and a bokeh kit with a heart-shaped cut out and took a walk down Miracle Mile. I started at LACMA and just walked east on Wilshire and snapped away at all the lights and traffic. I didn&amp;rsquo;t care so much about ISO as I needed to take fast shots of varying lighting situations that came up on the street&amp;ndash; so I just stayed in auto-ISO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Griffith Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</guid>
      <description>I use 500px to do research on where I want to go take pictures and what kind of shots to do. One in particular compelled me to go to Griffith Park to get a shot of the Griffith Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline.
Griffith Observatory Before Sunrise Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59933986 Griffith Observatory (After Sunrise) Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59957370 I went on a different day and night to get a night shot of the Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline (see below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing a HDD from a Western Digital Elements USB Drive</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/removing-a-hdd-from-a-western-digital-elements-usb-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/removing-a-hdd-from-a-western-digital-elements-usb-drive/</guid>
      <description>I have an old Western Digital Elements External USB HDD&amp;nbsp;(3TB)&amp;nbsp;that that mostly sits on my shelf since I&amp;rsquo;ve moved my data onto a formal network area storage (NAS). After doing some research, it turns out that these external USB hard drives actually have full 3.5&amp;rdquo; SATA hard drive inside! All you need to do is pry open the back with a knife or flathead screwdriver and remove the hard drive, and remove the USB adapter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Downtown Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Los Angeles now from traveling to cities like Toronto, San Francisco, and Chicago the past few months. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using 500px to research nice locations for these photos and it&amp;rsquo;s really paid off&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m very happy.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pushing my 500px account for my photos. I&amp;rsquo;ll have a separate blog post on that soon too, once a print I ordered arrives so I can give it a more thorough review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Adler Planetarium</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</guid>
      <description>This is my last of three posts covering the three landmarks I visited in Chicago during this past winter. My first was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s John Hancock Observatory and the other was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Bean.
The last landmark I visited was of a sunset from Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Adler Planetarium. I visited the Adler before and took pictures there&amp;ndash; but this was all when I first started to get into some HDR and photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was in Chicago for nearly three weeks during the holidays. I only planned to be there with my parents/family for about two weeks, but the snow, friends, and family all kept me from leaving&amp;ndash; so I ended up rebooking my flight TWICE.
During my extensive stay in Chicago, I visited a few landmarks to take some pictures.
I wrote a blog post covering my photos from John Hancock Observatory already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>I was up in San Francisco in late November and early December last year. It was a very last minute trip, but one I wanted to do for such a long time. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to get some shots of the iconic Golden Gate Bridge in SF&amp;ndash; without any fog. My prior visits have always been foggy and I could never see the full bridge.
Well, this trip was somewhat dedicated to visiting the bridge several times to get some shots&amp;ndash; to which I was finally able to get some shots without fog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Toronto</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-toronto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-toronto/</guid>
      <description>Last year I did some traveling in October and November. In late October, I went to Toronto for the first time. The city is beautiful there. I&amp;rsquo;ve probably been in Los Angeles too long, but I noticed how clear the skies were and was astonished to look at buildings with no haze in front. It really showcases how LA is such a polluted and dirty city.
While I was there I got a chance to see Ai Weiwei&amp;rsquo;s Forever Bicycle exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to visit the John Hancock Observatory with my sister. The last time I was there was in 2006 I think, somewhat a long time ago. I recall the views from JH being far superior to those from the Sears tower&amp;ndash; now called Willis tower. Plus I&amp;rsquo;ve seen some pictures on 500px taken from JH and wanted to try my hand at those views.
Signature Room or Observatory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlizzCon 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/blizzcon-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2013 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/blizzcon-2013/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended BlizzCon at the Anaheim Convention Center. I had a blast taking photos of cosplayers. I must say that Blizzard fans are some of the most dedicated super fans I&amp;rsquo;ve ever met. They love the games, the stories, and are really, really into the craft of cosplay. Other than at Anime Expo, these guys have the best cosplay I&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen.
This year there was some news on all fronts, minus Warcraft 3 and some other older games of course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 18:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to Comikaze Expo at the Los Angeles Convention Center. Last year I blogged about my experience and I must say that this year is a huge improvement. I want to share with everyone my thoughts and pictures I took of the convention.
But first I want to say that what Comikaze is doing is important. San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) is getting so big now that many comics/sci-fi/horror fans can&amp;rsquo;t even get tickets or housing to the huge event&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s such a hassle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink and Click LA Downtown Artwalk</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my second Drink and Click LA meetup in downtown Artwalk. Specifically we checked out The Last Bookstore, which is an amazing place to walk around and take photos if you are into books and little trinkets. Generally they ask you to check your bag at what I think is their main entrance, but the other entrance they do not in case you want to bring your camera bag in, which is what we all did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/san-diego-comic-con-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/san-diego-comic-con-2013/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in San Diego for Comic-Con. This was my third time at SDCC and I had a great time as usual. I took pictures as usual, but unlike previous years, I went to more panels than any other year.
Here are my albums on G+ (and Facebook&amp;ndash; FB):
 SDCC 2013 - Valiant Panel SDCC 2013 - Panels SDCC 2013 - General  Pictures The San Diego Convention Center from the East side Teen Titans Go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 13:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>Over the Fourth of July week I attended Anime Expo (AX) at the Los Angeles Convention Center (LACC). Last year I went and took over 1500 photos. This year I took over 1700 photos.
Full albums can be found here on G+ (and Facebook&amp;ndash; FB):  Anime Expo 2013 Day 0 Anime Expo 2013 Day 1 Anime Expo 2013 Day 2 Anime Expo 2013 Day 3 
I did not go on Day 4, on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Storage Services Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/cloud-storage-services-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 09:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/cloud-storage-services-review/</guid>
      <description>There are so many cloud storage services out there now vying for our attention and data. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my thoughts on the popular choices out there. I&amp;rsquo;m only looking at the personal or free plans. I&amp;rsquo;m leaving out anything for businesses or enterprises&amp;ndash; those are just a different beast with very different needs altogether.
Things I try to consider:
 Size of free storage (either from the start or earned through referrals) Sharing and collaboration on files Ease of use Anything else more than storage  Amazon Cloud Drive I really do not use this service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man of Steel Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</guid>
      <description>Man of Steel is the best take on Superman movie since Christopher Reeve donned the role. For me, he set the bar as to what Superman was before anything. Immediately after watching the movie, I said I liked it. But after sleeping on it and thinking about it more and more, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to like it less and less.
SPOILERS below. You have been warned.
What I liked: It&amp;rsquo;s a new take on Superman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Compatible External Hard Drives Are Over-Priced</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</guid>
      <description>Buying any technology related products online is still by far the best way to save money over buying from traditional brick and mortar stores. The likely products you would buy for your PC/Mac are keyboards, mice, external hard drive, and headphones.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the external hard drives, since they are currently priced differently between the PC and Mac market. For all intents and purposes of these drives are to backup data of a machine running either Windows or Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Drink and Click LA Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended my first Drink and Click LA event. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of the group for a while, but just never got around to attending one of their get-togethers. I really had fun talking shop with other photography enthusiasts from beginner to professionals levels. There was time to do some street photos, a little drinking, some eating, and lots of talking.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I attended a photography meetup of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y: The Last Man Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</guid>
      <description>For the past seven months I&amp;rsquo;ve jumped back into reading comics and graphic novels. I used to read them a lot when I was a teenager, but just lost interest by the mid/late 1990s. I find myself struggling to enjoy reading monthly issues and going to the comic book shop every week&amp;ndash; or even getting them online via Comixology.
The problem I have is that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reading them month to month&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s too little to read bit by bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s In My Messenger Bag</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/whats-in-my-messenger-bag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/whats-in-my-messenger-bag/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago I posted what&amp;rsquo;s in my camera bag. I thought I would follow up on what I carry in my other bag&amp;ndash; especially when I travel. Here&amp;rsquo;s what I typically have in my messenger bag.
Going from the top, left to right:  Canon 5D Mark III Apple adapters Samsung Galaxy Nexus phone Kindle Fire (version 1) Kindle Paperwhite Business cards Lens cleaner pen Pens Apple AC charger/adapter Micro USB charger Headphones 15&amp;rdquo; Macbook Pro (mid-2010) ONA &amp;ldquo;The Union Street Camera and Laptop Bag&amp;rdquo; - Ranger Tan You&amp;rsquo;re probably wondering why I have so many mobile devices/readers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laptop Warranties are Worth It</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/laptop-warranties-are-worth-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/laptop-warranties-are-worth-it/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve owned three laptops over the last nearly twelve years. Each of them, I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten some kind of warranty with. And I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did. If you don&amp;rsquo;t want to read this blog post, here is the shortened version:
Get a 2-3 year warranty for your laptop.
In 2001, I got my first laptop&amp;ndash; a Dell Latitude C600 (15&amp;rdquo; screen). Over my years using this as my main PC, the screen, hard drive, and battery all broke at some point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Considerate of Other Photographers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in the Bahamas for a friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding. The people, the scenery, and weather was beautiful up and through the wedding. The day after&amp;hellip; not so much. We had a bit of a tropical storm, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t last too long. Thank goodness the wedding day had clear skies.
Naturally, I brought my camera with me on the trip. I do have a post on what&amp;rsquo;s in my camera bag, typically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s In My Camera Bag</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/whats-in-my-camera-bag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 16:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/whats-in-my-camera-bag/</guid>
      <description>In Feedly, there&amp;rsquo;s a Flickr group that I subscribe to: What&amp;rsquo;s in your camera bag? I like to consider it photography gear porn.
So I thought I would share what I typically carry with me when I&amp;rsquo;m out and about. I consider this a light package. When I&amp;rsquo;m actually at an event I know I will take tons of pictures, there will be a bit more in my bag. But overall, this is good enough for most situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wondercon 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/wondercon-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/wondercon-2013/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend on Sunday I went to check out Wondercon down in Anaheim. I would have loved to go all three days, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t secure tickets as they sold out days in advance&amp;ndash; which I heard was a first.
The ticket for Sunday was only $10. Not bad, but they didn&amp;rsquo;t have long hours on this Easter Sunday. However, they did open the doors early for everyone. Supposedly it said 11am, but they let people in as early as 10am.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Google Reader</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/03/why-i-love-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 10:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/03/why-i-love-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday some sad news hit me with Google&amp;rsquo;s decision to close Google Reader on July 1, 2013.
Why? As The Next Web wrote, Former Google Reader product manager confirms our suspicions: Its demise is all about Google+. See Brian Shih, former Google Reader Product Manager&amp;rsquo;s answer on Quora.
This is sad for me because other than Gmail and Search itself, Google Reader (GR) is the service I use the most from Google, and is a browser tab I always have open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from UnCubed LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/02/pictures-from-uncubed-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2013 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/02/pictures-from-uncubed-la/</guid>
      <description>I went to the The UnCubed event here in Los Angeles this past Thursday. I wanted to check out what startups are here in LA and see the panels. It was good event that was extremely relaxed for a job fair. It was right by the beach&amp;ndash; LA style no doubt.
I took pictures here and there, but didn&amp;rsquo;t take any of the actual job fair. I got a chance to see what companies and technologies are at play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Stanley Kubrick Exhibit at LACMA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/the-stanley-kubrick-exhibit-at-lacma/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2013 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/the-stanley-kubrick-exhibit-at-lacma/</guid>
      <description>Today I checked out the Stanley Kubrick Exhibit at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA). To be honest, I&amp;rsquo;m not all too familiar with Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s work. There are only two of his movies that I can say I watched entirely: Eyes Wide Shut and A.I. Artificial Intelligence. The latter being more Spielberg than Kubrick anyway.
I hear that a lot of people either really like Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s films, or really dislike them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning Up Old Social Accounts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/cleaning-up-old-social-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2013 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/01/cleaning-up-old-social-accounts/</guid>
      <description>A week ago I deleted my Instagram and Path accounts.
Today I was able to delete an old Facebook account I created in 2006 when I was in graduate school. After graduating, I not only lost access to that email address, but also forgot the password and even the email address! It was one of those school accounts that auto generates an email address based on first letter of first name, followed by however many more characters of the last name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dark Knight Legend Exhibit at LA Live</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/12/dark-knight-legend-exhibit-at-la-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Dec 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/12/dark-knight-legend-exhibit-at-la-live/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend on Sunday, I went to check out the Dark Knight Legend Exhibit at LA Live. It&amp;rsquo;s a free exhibit there, located on the top of the parking structure just north of LA Live. The exhibit runs until December 14, 2012.
There&amp;rsquo;s artwork, vehicles, models, props, costumes, and behind the scene videos from all the Batman films throughout the exhibit. I really like how close I could get to the props and costumes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing an Android Error Message - Error retrieving information from server</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/fixing-an-android-error-message-error-retrieving-information-from-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/fixing-an-android-error-message-error-retrieving-information-from-server/</guid>
      <description>I have a Galaxy Nexus that recently got an over the air (OTA) update to Android 4.2 (Jelly Bean). Coming from 4.1.2 I was thrilled to see the new changes, particularly with their new panorama feature. But after the update I had issues with updating apps on the Google Play Store.
The Problem I got the following error message:
Update for &amp;ldquo;Foursquare&amp;rdquo; could not be downloaded due to an error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up Windows Phone 8 Emulator on a Virtual Machine</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/setting-up-windows-phone-8-emulator-on-a-virtual-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/setting-up-windows-phone-8-emulator-on-a-virtual-machine/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago I blogged about Installing Windows 8 Pro on Parallels Desktop 8. That of course worked for me, but when it came time to having Visual Studio 2012 (VS2012) and running an emulator for Windows Phone 8, it simply doesn&amp;rsquo;t work. I searched the Internet as to why, and came up with the following links:
 StackOverflow: Unable to create the virtual machine MSDN: Having problems running the Windows Phone 8 Emulator?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long Beach Comic Con 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/long-beach-comic-con-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/long-beach-comic-con-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I attended Long Beach Comic Con held at the Long Beach Convention Center. It&amp;rsquo;s not as big as San Diego Comic Con nor Comikaze Expo, but it definitely had a more collector&amp;rsquo;s paradise feel to it.
I actually didn&amp;rsquo;t take too many pictures myself as I was head deep in the comic book bins looking for deals on actual comic books. Normally I&amp;rsquo;m more of a trade paperback (TPB) kind of comic reader, but recently started picking up some individual titles again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Windows 8 Pro on Parallels Desktop 8</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/installing-windows-8-pro-on-parallels-desktop-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2012 17:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/11/installing-windows-8-pro-on-parallels-desktop-8/</guid>
      <description>Last week I went to a Microsoft launch event, New Era of Work, and got a free copy of Windows 8 Pro. I had already tried Windows 8 Preview as well as have Windows 7 Ultimate running as a virtual machines (VMs) through Parallels Desktop on my Macbook Pro (MBP). I didn&amp;rsquo;t like the preview edition that much, so I uninstalled it after a few days. But after attending the event, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d give it another look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upgrading my 2010 Macbook Pro to SSD</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/upgrading-my-2010-macbook-pro-to-ssd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/upgrading-my-2010-macbook-pro-to-ssd/</guid>
      <description>I recently upgraded my 15&amp;rdquo; 2010 Macbook Pro&amp;rsquo;s 500GB HDD to a 512GB SSD. The directions you find in this blog post, you should easily be able to find using a search engine. I just want to document what I did, hoping to help fill the Internet with something useful, maybe.
The didn&amp;rsquo;t have a problem with the CPU or even memory. Well, I do constantly run out of HDD space every two-three months, but I do regular backups to an external USB 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Camp LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</guid>
      <description>I picked up a free ticket to Mobile Camp LA earlier this week and decided to attend. Overall I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too impressed with the event. It may have very well been the first of it&amp;rsquo;s kind aimed at developers, designers, and business folk. Anyway, I thought the venue was a bit of a mess as many things went wrong.  Earthquake drill at 10:15am (slightly distracting, but out of their control&amp;ndash; I understand) A lot of sessions held in a one big open space separated by cloth dividers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Code Camp at USC</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended SoCal Code Camp held at University of Southern California (USC). Had a good time learning about new stuff as usual. The prizes here are pretty spectacular, but once again I won absolutely nothing. Nothing!
Like the one I went to earlier this year, this one was also a bit heavy on the .Net side of technology with little representation from Android and iOS, and nothing from Ruby/Rails/Java/etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I checked out the Comikaze Expo at the LA Convention Center (LACC). As far as I know, this was the first &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; comic con taking place in Los Angeles. The previous year&amp;rsquo;s I heard took place in a parking structure or something. But this is a comic con for LA made by fans, for fans. That&amp;rsquo;s their slogan more or less anyway.
Anyway, I had fun and took a lot of pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brazilian Day in LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/brazilian-day-in-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/brazilian-day-in-la/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I posted about my visit to Greekfest LA. The following day, Saturday I checked out Brazilian Day LA, which was during the super sunny and hot day. What I loved was that the costumes and culture were so colorful and lively. Pretty much everyone was enjoying themselves watching or dancing along to a nice big neighborhood party.
The parade was pretty awesome too. I just wish the sidewalk for it was a bit bigger and less congested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greekfest LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/greekfest-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/greekfest-la/</guid>
      <description>One of the things I love about living in Los Angeles is all the ethnic fairs that go on. Over the weekend I attended two different fairs no so far from where I live.
On Friday there was LA Greekfest. I went during the evening to avoid the crowd and heat during the day. My favorite dish was the dessert, the pastry puffs.
Full set of pictures can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 16:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</guid>
      <description>Last week I went to the San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) and had a blast. The last time I went was back in 2010, which I blogged about here. I took quite a few photos, but only post-processed a fraction of them. I may choose to post-process more of them at a later date. You can view the full album here.
I attended SDCC with a 4-day pass along with preview night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>A little over a week ago I attended Anime Expo (AX) held at the LA Convention Center. I had a four-day pass for June 29 - July 2, 2012. The last time I attended AX was in 2008, quite a long time ago. I recall being the odd one for not dressing up&amp;ndash; as so so very many people dress up in an anime costume!
So a motivation for attending this year was to take pictures of the costumed attendees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Putting CyanogenMod on the Kindle Fire</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/06/putting-cyanogenmod-on-the-kindle-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/06/putting-cyanogenmod-on-the-kindle-fire/</guid>
      <description>After seeing the Nexus 7 tablet make its debut at Google I/O yesterday, it made me realize how my Kindle Fire (KF) is kind of lame. I reviewed the Kindle Fire back in November 2011.

To be fair though, my needs have changed. When I initially purchased the KF, I didn&amp;rsquo;t want an iPad2 or a 10&amp;rdquo; tablet. I just wanted a simple reading device that could browse the web a bit and play some games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus Photographer&#39;s Conference</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-conference/</guid>
      <description>Last week I attended the Google+ Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Conference in San Francisco, May 22-23, 2012 at the Yerba Buena Center for the Arts. The day before, I attended a photowalk at Golden Gate Park which I blogged about already.
Some things I observed and learned at the conference:
 Adobe Lightroom 4, Bridge, and Photoshop seem to be the digital tools of choice of many photographers. There are just as many Nikon users as there are Canon users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus Photographer&#39;s Photowalk at Golden Gate Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was up in San Francisco May 21-23 for the Google+ Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Conference. On Monday, there was an optional photowalk at about ten locations. I attended the one led by Scott Kelby at Golden Gate Park.
The photowalk was pretty fun. It&amp;rsquo;s the third photowalk I&amp;rsquo;ve been on so far, and in general I like to stray from the group, go at my own pace, and take shots of everything I find interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muir Woods Hike Photos</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/muir-woods-hike-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/muir-woods-hike-photos/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago I was in San Francisco for the Coldplay concert in San Jose at the HP Pavillion. Part of the weekend trip was hiking near Muir Woods. I brought my camera, tripod, and backpack with me and took some photos during my hike.
I had with me my Canon 5D Mark 3 with Canon 16-35mm f/2.8 L II lens&amp;nbsp;and Canon 24-105 f/4 L lens. I brought my Dolica tripod,&amp;nbsp;Canon 480EX II Speedlite flash, jacket, and some other stuff&amp;ndash; and&amp;nbsp;packed it all in my Lowepro Photo Sport 200 AW Backpack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB May Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last evening I attended the LA MongDB May Meetup hosted at Factual. Presentations by Tony Tam (@fehguy), CTO of Wordnik and Andrew Hall, Principal Engineer of uSamp. I had a great time hearing about how mongoDB is being used by two different companies.
In N Out Burgers and fries served instead of pizza! 



Tony Tam presenting 





Andrew Hall presenting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coworking at NextSpace LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</guid>
      <description>Jelly LA held a free coworking day at NextSpace in Culver City this past Friday. I got a little tour of the place and was very impressed. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to a few coworking offices in LA already (CoLoft, BlankSpaces, and Kleverdog), and I can honestly say that this is my favorite to cowork in. One, it&amp;rsquo;s conveniently located in Culver City, where I currently live in. Two, it&amp;rsquo;s got a great amount of space, offices, and little nooks to work in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Summer Conventions</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 20:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</guid>
      <description>There are some conferences and conventions coming up soon that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about. So far I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to Anime Expo and Comic-Con, as I purchased tickets for those already. Recently announced is the G+ Photographers Conference, which includes a Photowalk on Monday, May 21st. I will most likely make my way up there for that&amp;ndash; about eighty-percent sure I&amp;rsquo;ll go.
I plan to take my photography gear to take plenty of pictures too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire in Irwindale, California. It&amp;rsquo;s been over almost fifteen years since I attended a Renaissance Fair, the last being the Bristol Renaissance Fair in the Midwest. I was a teenager then and really loved the tasty mushrooms! I also got my older sister to buy me a broad sword!
A selection of photos I took are below. Full set can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new lense and camera body</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-new-lense-and-camera-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 14:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-new-lense-and-camera-body/</guid>
      <description>Recently I made some new camera gear purchases with the help of selling some of my older, unused equipment. Say hello to the Canon 70-200mm f/2.8 L IS II lense and Canon 5D Mark III! Yes, after a few weeks after the Canon 5DM3 announcement, I decided to go ahead and make the purchase. It cost an arm and a leg, but now I no longer have to watch videos of other people unboxing and reviewing these products, I get to use them myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My HTPC Setup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-htpc-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2012 19:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-htpc-setup/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I blogged about my new purchase of the WD TV Live Streaming Media Player. I still enjoy it immensely, and a few people have inquired about what is needed.
So here&amp;rsquo;s a list of what&amp;rsquo;s in my setup:
WD TV Live Streaming Media Player This is the heart of the Home Theatre PC (HTPC).

WD Elements 3 TB USB 2.0 Desktop External Hard Drive I don&amp;rsquo;t recommend attaching more than one external hard drive via a USB hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET April Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended the LADOTNET April meetup on&amp;nbsp;Building a Rich Web Experience with jQuery, Ajax and .NET&amp;nbsp;presentation by James Johnson. Good meetup with a very decent turnout considering it was a nice day out and NCAA finals was on
For full set of pictures I&amp;rsquo;ve taken at meetups I&amp;rsquo;ve been to this year, click here.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songkran Festival in LA&#39;s Thaitown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend, on Sunday April 1, 2012, I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Thaitown to check out the Songkran (Thai New Year) celebrations along Hollywood Blvd. They closed Hollywood off from Western all the way to Normandie to have a street festival/parade. I arrived around 11am and spent about 30 minutes just trying to find parking. I ran along Hollywood just in time to catch the beginning of the parade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Chicago HDR Photography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 15:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I was in Chicago. I woke up early the morning following St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day to take some photos near the Adler Planetarium and Millennium Park. I got there with my sister just before sunrise around 6:30am.
The tools I used: Canon 60D&amp;nbsp;camera body with Canon 16-35mm L wide lens&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Canon 24-105mm L lens&amp;nbsp;along with my tripod. For post processing: Apple&amp;rsquo;s Aperture and Photomatix Pro.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Last night I attended the Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown meetup. I arrived early and walked to the Walt Disney Concert Hall to do some HDR shots. Upon arriving there, I immediately regretted not bringing my 16-35mm f/2.8 L lens. So made due with my recently purchased 24-105 f/4 L lens, which I really haven&amp;rsquo;t used that much yet.
I spent most of the evening on my own going at my own pace to take pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Photography at Baldwin Hills and LACMA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 12:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I took my camera out to take some photos here in LA.
Some HDR photos taken of the sunset near the Baldwin Hills Scenic Overlook:



 
Some photos taken at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA):
Do you know what this is? Hint, it&amp;rsquo;s a dog&amp;rsquo;s butt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon 5D Mark 3 Announced</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/canon-5d-mark-3-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/canon-5d-mark-3-announced/</guid>
      <description>The Canon 5D Mark 3 was announced yesterday.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking to get a full-frame DSLR for a while now. Last year I was thinking of getting the Canon 5D Mark 2 (M2), but settled for the Canon 60D because of price and I&amp;rsquo;d rather wait for the M3. Hopefully the M2 will drop in price slightly once the M3 officially comes out.
The price of the M3 is $3500. That&amp;rsquo;s body only, no kit lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Design of Everyday Things</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 16:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</guid>
      <description>The Design of Everyday Things comes highly recommended on Coding Horror&amp;rsquo;s recommended reading list as well as many other software developers. After giving it a read, I thought it was good, relevant today, but slightly dated with their examples.
After reading the book, I am reminded of the light switch to my bathroom in my current apartment in Los Angeles. See below.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a horrible design! The left-most button, which is red, is for off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</guid>
      <description>Over this past weekend, on Sunday, the evening of the NBA All-Star game and Academy Awards, I went to check out a Google+ LA Photowalk in Santa Monica hosted by Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson (aka mySpace Tom).
I had a great time seeing and learning how other photography enthusiasts and professionals see things. I brought my Canon 60D, Canon 16-35mm L lens, and tripod. I regret not bringing another lens with me for some more flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a Meetup Junkie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve become a Meetup Junkie. Every month I attend several meetups related to technology and food. I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get enough of following these interests with other like-minded individuals, in the real world.

I primarily use Meetup to find interesting groups by city. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it in Chicago, Bangkok, San Francisco, and now Los Angeles. It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic and addicting!
But for those who haven&amp;rsquo;t used such a service, it may be somewhat scary&amp;ndash; especially if you are an introvert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my first MongoDB meetup. They have a twitter account: @lamongodb. The meetup was hosted at Factual Inc.
Anand &amp;ldquo;Kumi&amp;rdquo; Nandakumar (@kumi360) presented MongoDB + Node.js design decisions for Jumpspoon. Nuri Halperin presented MongoDB vs. RDBMS.
Overall a good group. I look forward to attend future meetups and learn more about how mongodb is being used.
You can find the pictures I took at meetups in 2012 in this album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft&#39;s New Windows 8 Logo</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/microsofts-new-windows-8-logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 14:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/microsofts-new-windows-8-logo/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has a new logo design for their operating system (OS), Windows. I&amp;rsquo;ve been reading a few tech bloggers/writers reactions to it lately, and I felt I just had to add my two bits in.
The last time I did a blog post on logo design, was on Tropicana&amp;rsquo;s new logo design.
MG Siegler&amp;rsquo;s recent blog post on Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s new logo evolution was the first ones I read. Other writers have also written how the new logo is no longer wavy and flag-like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Web Guide Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to a Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub meetup at Kleverdog. The topic was&amp;nbsp;Kicking Web Butt: Small Business Web Guide. The presenter was Ed Wu (@edwu) from THINKademic.
The room was primarily designers, which is a nice change for me, as I generally go to developer-centric meetups and events. I hope to be more of a dev-signer (developer/designer).
Here are some of the pictures I took. As usual, you can find the album where I dump all my meetups pictures for this year here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiro Dreams of Sushi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 01:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from watching a special advanced screening of Jiro Dreams of Sushi at the Landmark. Special thanks to Aisha and Foodspotting for putting me on the list!
The documentary is wonderful! Besides the very appealing video of sushi on the big screen, there is quite a story of Jiro Ono and his sushi restaurant, Sukiyabashi Jiro. There certainly is craftsmanship and art to making sushi&amp;ndash; which Jiro has dedicated his life to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 11:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I attended the LADOTNET February meetup held at Blankspaces last night. The event topic was: Start ups, Tech and Business Trends with John Shiple. The attendance was pretty massive as this user group is getting bigger and bigger every month. I enjoyed the speaker and presentation a lot. I do notice that it&amp;rsquo;s a trend that there are a lot of startup businesses growing outside of Silicon Valley.
More speaker information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</guid>
      <description>As a foodie and photography enthusiast, I found Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots to be a good read, mostly. Although, I did find myself skimming the later chapters as they deal with post-processing using Adobe Photoshop.
The first three chapters on fundamentals, equipment, and lighting I thought were the best for foodies interested in improving their skills as a photographer. The chapter on framing and composition is good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from SoCal Code Camp</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I attended and volunteered at SoCal Code Camp at California State University Fullerton. I had an awesome time, attended quite a few sessions, learned a lot, and met quite a few good people.
Below are some of the pictures. Full set of pictures can be found here.
Pictures 

Mario Harnandez presenting CSS3 for Web Designers- Let&amp;rsquo;s Design a Visually Appealing Website and Grid Systems - Picking the Right CSS Framework for Your Website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Code Camp is tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/socal-code-camp-is-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 19:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/socal-code-camp-is-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>SoCal Code Camp is tomorrow. Sessions have been posted, as well as the schedule. It&amp;rsquo;s a two day event, January 28 and 29 (Saturday and Sunday), full of sessions on a variety of software development topics.
Did I mention that it&amp;rsquo;s FREE?!
It will be hosted at California State University Fullerton. Here is a campus map to help you.
I will be there bright and early volunteering and probably taking photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished reading: In The Plex</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/finished-reading-in-the-plex/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/finished-reading-in-the-plex/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading In The Plex: How Google Thinks, Works, and Shapes Our Lives on my Kindle Fire.
Overall it was a good book with some insight into Google, but I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say that the book was well-written. It does jump around a lot and the material wasn&amp;rsquo;t presented chronologically in story-fashion. It&amp;rsquo;s currently the most up to date book on Google as it includes recent stuff such as Android, Eric Schmidt&amp;rsquo;s stepping down as CEO in 2010, and it&amp;rsquo;s failures to enter as a social network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designer&#39;s Hub Meet and Greet</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 06:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub Meet and Greet event hosted at Kleverdog, a co-working space located in Chinatown. This was their first event. It was a very nice meetup about essentially building a community of designers. There were a lot of ideas thrown out about what the group could be about. I personally would like to have a community to turn to, in-person, for me to learn more about the tools and techniques in graphics design&amp;ndash; notably Photoshop, Lightroom, and Aperture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SOPA Blackout set for January 18 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/sopa-blackout-set-for-january-18-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2012 18:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/sopa-blackout-set-for-january-18-2012/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow, Wednesday January 18, 2012, I plan to block this website out in support of SOPA Blackout. Technically it won&amp;rsquo;t be completed blocked out, as the javascript is only a black message overlay on top of the website. Users will still be able to click through once the popup comes up.
Here is the javascript that will be used in the header:
&amp;lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src=&#34;//js.sopablackout.org/sopablackout.js&#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;On one of my other sites, spong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA Ruby/Rails January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 03:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night went to the LA Ruby/Rails Meetup hosted at AT&amp;amp;T Interactive. There were two presentations followed by three lightning talks.
Using Ruby with R by Sean Marcia
Rack Middleware as a General Purpose Abstraction by John Bender
Some of the pictures I took are posted below. You can view the picture dump from all pictures I took here.
As a reminder: LA RubyConf is coming up February 2-4, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LADOTNET January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 11:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to the LADOTNET January Meetup. The presentation was: Unit Testing/Architecting Apps for Testing with Paul Sheriff.
The turn-out for the meetup was pretty big, maybe fifty to sixty people, with a fair amount of recruiters. The LADOTNET meetup was held at Blankspaces. There is an upcoming SoCal Code Camp coming up on the weekend of January 28 and 29, 2012.
I have a new album where I will dump all pictures I take from Meetups for this upcoming year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs biography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoyed reading the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson. I bought both the hardcover and the Kindle book version. Isaacson&amp;rsquo;s writing is superb and flows very well. However, if you read articles or even watched some Steve Jobs documentaries, it covers a lot of similar ground. I am reminded of the TV movie, Pirates of Silicon Valley. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, I highly recommend it.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair for people to compare him to Thomas Edison, as Jobs was our modern day inventor and businessman&amp;ndash; a visionary if you will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Western Digital WD TV Live Streaming Media Player</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/western-digital-wd-tv-live-streaming-media-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 17:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/western-digital-wd-tv-live-streaming-media-player/</guid>
      <description>Since I moved to LA, I&amp;rsquo;ve been without my old PC that runs XBMC. For a Home Theater PC (HTPC), the PC is decent, but it&amp;rsquo;s large, loud, and not in California. So I went on Amazon and bought the Western Digital WD TV Live Streaming Media Player for $90 US. Behold, my new HTPC.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for a few days, and overall I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with it. I was able to hook up my external USB hard drives to a D-Link DUB-H7 High Speed USB 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goodbye 2011, Hello 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/goodbye-2011-hello-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 04:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/goodbye-2011-hello-2012/</guid>
      <description>The new year has come. Time to say goodbye the past year, and hello to the upcoming one. 2011 was an amazing year for me in terms of travel, photography, and trying out new things.
I spent four months living in Thailand up until the end of April. I was able to celebrate Thai new year, songkran, among other Thai/Chinese holidays. I traveled in September through November using the JetBlue Bluepass.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from SF Ruby December Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-sf-ruby-december-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-sf-ruby-december-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I drove up to San Francisco from LA to check out the SF Ruby group. The drive was long, but worth it as I got to meet some interesting people. The meetup was hosted at ZenDesk. Being from Chicago and now living in LA, I never before heard so much talk about venture capital (VCs) coming from developers. I think there really is a culture difference in SF compared to other cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA DotNet December Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 15:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in living in Los Angeles for two months now. About a month ago I finally bought a car to get around in. On Monday, December 5, 2011, I was able to attend my first the Los Angeles .Net Developer&amp;rsquo;s Group hosted at Blankspaces.
There were two presentations:
 Daniel Egan presented on Diving into Windows Phone Market: Should I make the jump? Henry Lee presented on Making Money with Windows Phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Fire Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/11/kindle-fire-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/11/kindle-fire-review/</guid>
      <description>I pre-ordered my Kindle Fire in early October. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an eReader device for a long time, ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling so much. Carrying books around is such a pain.
Like many others out there, I got my Kindle Fire on November 15, 2011. After a few weeks of using the Fire, I felt I could give it a good review. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it for playing Words With Friends, some basic browsing on Amazon, and I finished reading the Steve Jobs biography on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to have multiple remotes for you Git project</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/10/how-to-have-multiple-remotes-for-you-git-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 12:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/10/how-to-have-multiple-remotes-for-you-git-project/</guid>
      <description>When I found out that BitBucket added support for Git, I got pretty excited.
Just this past year I started to use Git as my DVCS for all my projects. More importantly, my older projects didn&amp;rsquo;t have any version control whatsoever. They were projects spread across multiple computers that only merged into a single external USB hard drive when I started to retire some computers because they were just too old (six plus years!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BlizzCon 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/10/blizzcon-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 14:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/10/blizzcon-2011/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went with my sister and friends to check out BlizzCon&amp;nbsp;at the Anaheim Convention Center. Obviously we&amp;rsquo;re all fans of the games that Blizzard Entertainment make, and it was everyone&amp;rsquo;s first time attending. We had a blast!
It was a very tiring two days (Friday and Saturday, Oct 21-22, 2011). Doors opened around 9-9:30am, and the events lasted until midnight! I went around and snapped photos as much as I could, while attending some panels and Starcraft 2 tournaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Objective-C and iOS for .NET Developers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my favorite local user group, Chicago Alt.net (@ChicagoAltNet).
Eduardo Scoz presented on Objective-C and iOS. Great talk and a very big turnout. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen this many developers show up for an Alt.net meetup here since Uncle Bob Martin did a presentation.
Here are some of the photos I took. If you are looking for a full set of photos I took from various meetups I attend, including this one, I dump them all in this Picasa album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Los Angeles Ruby/Rails Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last week I used my JetBlue BluePass to head out to Los Angeles to attend the LA Ruby Meetup (@laruby) hosted at CoLoft. I was impressed with the turnout, the speakers and presentation, and the audience participation. The format of the meetup was pretty long though. I&amp;rsquo;m used to maybe thirty minutes to one hour of a presentation. They had four presentations lasting about two hours! All very good of course, but I have to admit that it was a bit tiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wizard World Chicago Comic Con 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/wizard-world-chicago-comic-con-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 09:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/wizard-world-chicago-comic-con-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m suffering from San Diego Comic Con 2010 withdrawal still. This year I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to go as a good friend was getting married and I was his best man&amp;ndash; which turned out to be the best wedding I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to. But anyway, you can see my post and pictures from that here.
So this year I made a last minute decision to go to Wizard World&amp;rsquo;s Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Photography, Blogging, and Coding</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-photography-blogging-and-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 09:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-photography-blogging-and-coding/</guid>
      <description>It was the summer of 2010 that I decided I wanted to dust off the DSLR I bought in 2006 and put it to good use more often. So throughout that summer, I made an effort to bring my camera with me everywhere I went. I brought it to work, to my various meetups I attended, and even when I walked around Chicago. I just kept taking photos of whatever I thought was interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Alt.net: Coffeescript</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 21:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures I took from tonight&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Alt.net August 2011 meetup on Coffeescript, presented by Fawad Halim.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Traveling</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 13:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-traveling/</guid>
      <description>In July of 2010, I quit my full time job as a software developer. I wanted to break away from the nine-to-five, travel a bit, have fun, and teach myself new things in the process. I was able to visit San Diego, Los Angeles, San Francisco, Boston, New York City, Denver, Bangkok, Chiang Mai, and Pattaya.

In 2011, I kept traveling, I visited Hua Hin, Phuket, Phang Nga, Singapore, Las Vegas, and Baltimore, before returning to Chicago for a time period greater than one week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&#39;m excited about Spotify</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/why-im-excited-about-spotify/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2011 18:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/why-im-excited-about-spotify/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m so excited and I just can&#39;t hide it. - Pointer Sisters (reference)  I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Spotify now for a few weeks already. I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed it so much I upgraded to a premium account the very same day I signed up for it, so I could enjoy it on my mobile smartphone. Overall it&amp;rsquo;s been a great service that I use almost daily. For a long time I&amp;rsquo;ve been waiting for music to hit the cloud, and this year alone it&amp;rsquo;s really been a hit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting ready to Jet Blue with Blue Pass</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2011 00:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/getting-ready-to-jet-blue-with-blue-pass/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2010, I took off with JetBlue with my All-You-Can-Jet (AYCJ) pass during the month of September/October. I visited Boston, New York City, Los Angeles, San Francisco, and Denver. Five cities! Friends, food, and fun! It was such a fantastic journey!
On my plane rides, I met many other jet-setters flying around the US. I remember having interesting conversations with them, and even on one flight, sitting next to a dog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purchased a Herman Miller Aeron Chair</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I purchased a Herman Miller Aeron chair from Home and Office Solutions up in Northbrook, Illinois. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an Aeron for the longest time, but just never felt comfortable spending a thousand dollars on an office chair. My seven-year old Ikea chair was falling apart and wasn&amp;rsquo;t comfortable anymore. To be honest, it started to fall apart after two years. I really needed to get a new chair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus is for Geeks</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/google-plus-is-for-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2011 01:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/google-plus-is-for-geeks/</guid>
      <description>Google Plus (G+) is for geeks. It&amp;rsquo;s how it is now, and I think that&amp;rsquo;s how it&amp;rsquo;s going to be going forward, more or less.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using G+ now for about a month. I scored an invite early on, and a few days later invited a good chunk of people from my Gmail contacts. I went through the process of making circles, refining the circles, installing the add-ons into my Chrome browser, and so forth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading List for Summer 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/reading-list-for-summer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2011 20:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/reading-list-for-summer-2011/</guid>
      <description>I have selected the books I&amp;rsquo;d like to complete before the end of Summer/Fall season. I think it&amp;rsquo;s a nice set and variety of books.
 The 4-Hour Workweek by Timothy Ferriss Confessions of a Public Speaker by Scott Berkun Peopleware: Productive Projects and Teams by Tom DeMarco and Timothy Lister Eloquent Ruby by Russ Olsen Four Steps to Epiphany by Steven Gary Blank The Camera by Ansel Adams Joel on Software by Joel Spolsky  The Green Lantern: Blackest Night graphic novels below I already finished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Social Networks Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/the-history-of-social-networks-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/the-history-of-social-networks-part-2/</guid>
      <description>In The History of Social Networks Part 1, I covered the legacy social networks that I was once a part of. I use the term legacy to mean out-dated, unpopular, and in some cases discontinued.
Now I&amp;rsquo;m going to cover the current social networks that I am active on today. I guess you can say that these are my picks, for now.
Facebook I remember when I first heard about Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Camera Gear Purchases</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/recent-camera-gear-purchases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 15:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/recent-camera-gear-purchases/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently made some camera gear purchases.
I upgraded my Rebel XT to a Canon 60D a few weeks ago. I also got a Canon 60D battery grip with Canon EW78D Lens Hood. Overall, I&amp;rsquo;m very happy with these purchases. I love the 60D, it&amp;rsquo;s such a great step up from the Rebel XT, which I purchased 5 years ago. It feels good to use, and the pictures are also great, as expected from Canon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The History of Social Networks Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/the-history-of-social-networks-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/the-history-of-social-networks-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Paul Adams has an insightful presentation: The Real Life Social Network. It&amp;rsquo;s a great read, but it is a little long (224 slides)! Basically, he points out that the social network isn&amp;rsquo;t a fad, that it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay, and he goes through to talk about how relationships are, online/offline, behaviors, etcetera. Check it out if you have some time.
Since I started using computers, there&amp;rsquo;s always been a yearning to connect with others online&amp;ndash; through a social network in some way, shape, or form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from July&#39;s Refresh and Ignite Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to too many meetups this month, only three. Sorry, the weather&amp;rsquo;s been either really hot or super rainy. Interestingly when I condensed the meetup names in this blog title, they both hint at refreshing and igniting Chicago.
I already posted on Barcamp Chicago in a previous blog post.
The second meetup, Corey Haines presented on It&amp;rsquo;s All About the Business Value on Wednesday, July 27, 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcamp Chicago at Pumping Station One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 03:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</guid>
      <description>I went to check out Barcamp Chicago earlier this month, on July 9, 2011. It was held at Pumping Station One, a hackerspace here in Chicago. I didn&amp;rsquo;t stay too long, as it was a really nice day out.
Here are most of the pictures I took:
This is the entrance 
After the hallway entrance, this what you first see</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Tech Meetups in May and June</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</guid>
      <description>In May I came across a new group: Refresh Chicago (@refreshchi). So far, their meetups have been pretty good. From their twitter, the group is described as: Monthly meetup for the advancement of Chicagos designers and developers. Pretty cool.
So here are some pictures I took in May and June, 2011&amp;ndash; post Chicago Code Camp and Rails Conf.
David Kadavy presenting at Refresh Chicago (May 25, 2011)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Lantern Movie Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 13:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>Green Lantern was the movie I was looking forward to the most this summer. I watched it last night and wanted to share my thoughts on the movie with other fans and others that may have watched the movie already. I still recommend people to go watch the movie though, to read the comics, and/or then come talk to me.
Please note, DO NOT READ FURTHER IF YOU HAVEN&amp;rsquo;T SEEN THE MOVIE YET.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Baltimore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/trip-to-baltimore/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2011 15:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/trip-to-baltimore/</guid>
      <description>I was out in Baltimore, Maryland for RailsConf last week. The conference was great, but this was also the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Baltimore other than for a flight layover. For the most part I was there for the 4 day conference and eating.
I must say that some of the neighborhoods in the evening/night didn&amp;rsquo;t feel to safe to walk through. Also, the taxis there are so very expensive!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from RailsConf 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-railsconf-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-railsconf-2011/</guid>
      <description>I had a great time at RailsConf 2011, which took place in Baltimore, Maryland this year. Got the chance to meet and talk with a lot of Rails developers and passionate people. Always a good thing. I admit that I&amp;rsquo;m a Ruby Nuby, and quite a few of the talks were a little over my head, but in general there was a talk for everyone, no matter what skill level in Ruby/Rails.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 08:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Code Camp 2011 (CCC3) has wrapped up! I had a great time going to various sessions, learning new things, and meeting/talking with great people. I wish more of these events would take place in the Chicagoland area. I think about 300 people attended, which I think is pretty good considering the event wasn&amp;rsquo;t even in Chicago! This year, CCC3 took place at College of Lake County, in Grayslake, which is located about 50 miles from Chicago (approximately 1 hour drive).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>The schedule for Chicago Code Camp is now up! You can register for the free event here. You can follow them on twitter at: @chicagocodecamp. The twitter hash tag to follow at the event is: #ccc3
The link to actual schedule: Chicago Code Camp 2011 Schedule (this link may not work in the future&amp;ndash; beyond 2011).
This is the list of sessions I&amp;rsquo;m interested in. I may jump in/out between some sessions that are running in parallel, or pick one when the event gets closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Meetups for Spring and Summer 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 04:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago for now! Just got off the plane a few days ago. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m almost ready to get back into going to some tech meetups in the US now. A lot of great events coming up!
Chicago Ruby: Downtown - Marking Up the Web with Graffiti
Tuesday, May 3, 2011 at 6pm
To be held at ThoughtWorks.
Chicago Silverlight Users Group
Wednesday, May 4, 2011
To be held at the ITA building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Singapore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2011 16:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/trip-to-singapore/</guid>
      <description>I went to Singapore over the weekend (April 21-25) for Red Dot Ruby Conf. It was my first time to Singapore. I didn&amp;rsquo;t travel around too much, as I was in a conference for two full days (Friday and Saturday).
Some things I noticed about Singapore:
 No mosquitoes Hot and humid like Bangkok, but more pleasant Plenty of jay-walkers Seems the major things to do are shop and eat 3G is everywhere, generally very good Singlish takes some getting used to Singapore is full of folks from everywhere Super clean everywhere No traffic-- seems well managed  I ate out often at hawker centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>APN Info for Singtel&#39;s 3G in Singapore</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/apn-info-for-singtels-3g-in-singapore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 06:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/apn-info-for-singtels-3g-in-singapore/</guid>
      <description>I wanted to write a quick post on my experience with getting a SIM card in Singapore.
When I arrived to Changi Airport, I immediately went to get a SIM card from a money exchange booth. They seemed to only offer prepaid SIM cards in $50, $100, and $150 SGD if I&amp;rsquo;m not mistaken. Since I was only staying for 4 days, I chose the smallest one: $50 SGD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Red Dot Ruby Conf 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/red-dot-ruby-conf-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2011 21:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/red-dot-ruby-conf-2011/</guid>
      <description>As part of my trip back to the US, I attended Red Dot Ruby Conf 2011 on April 22-23, 2011. This event takes place in Singapore, at the Singapore Management University (SMU).
I had an awesome time. I enjoy going to these social technology events. Got a chance to talk and hang out with a lot of smart folks. I really enjoy the Ruby/Rails community
Quick summary of the talks from the two days:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow Meetup in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 20:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>On the Stackoverflow blog, it was announced that April 6, 2011 would be Worldwide Stack Overflow Meetup. They created a meetup page at: Stackoverflow Meetup.
BKK Web Meetup also hosted a meetup on IDEs and other dev tools. Presentations were given on Eclipse (by @nadam9) and Vim (by @ches). Our gracious host was, as always, Web Courses Bangkok. Afterwards, we had the usual beer/food meetup at Singha Beer Park not too far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from the March BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 03:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>The BKK Web Meetup last night was pretty awesome. It was the biggest turnout I&amp;rsquo;ve seen yet, and it was also very interactive. Plenty of discussion, questions, and even stories came from the attendees.
The topic was: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about hiring and training developers. Benjamin Scherrey was the presenter. Some bullet points that I took away:
 There are some cultural barriers to understand in hiring a Thai/Asian software developer. There are some cultural barriers dealing with Thai clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 2 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-2-of-2/</guid>
      <description>This is part 2 of 2 of my story from 2010. You can view part 1 at: My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)
So where I last left off, I was leaving Chicago, destination: Thailand. Below, the bags I packed at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.

I was flying Korea Air for the first time. On my way to Bangkok, Thailand, I had a layover at S. Korea. Some pictures I took at the airport:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Story from 2010 (Part 1 of 2)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/my-story-from-2010-part-1-of-2/</guid>
      <description>Just want to give a quick overview of my life since mid 2010 to present, early 2011. This is part 1 of 2.
For several years I was a software developer/consultant at a few companies and organizations. I mostly used .Net and Microsoft technologies as my tools for solving problems. In July of 2010, I decided to quit my 9-5 job and try new things out. I bought a Macbook Pro and decided that I wanted to get away from .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDxBKK Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, on March 3 2011, I attended TEDxBKK over at TCDC at the top floor at Emporium in Bangkok, Thailand. You can also follow them on twitter at @tedxbkk. Overall it was a good turnout, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too enthusiastic about most of the talks though. The one that stuck out the most for me was David Christian&amp;rsquo;s talk in the Knowledge Revolution session.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Is Happiness</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/food-is-happiness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/food-is-happiness/</guid>
      <description>I started a new blog/website over at foodishappiness.com. I exported all my food posts from this site as well as from bestburgerintown.blogspot.com (which I&amp;rsquo;ve abandoned) and imported them into the new site. It&amp;rsquo;s just something new I wanted to try out, to see if I could generate content from my food/eating passion. I&amp;rsquo;m still on an &amp;ldquo;eating tour&amp;rdquo; of Bangkok, Thailand so to speak.

I know many say that blogs are dead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from February 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 21:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures from last night&amp;rsquo;s BKK Web Meetup session on Ruby on Rails. The presentation was by Ches Martin. Our gracious host was Web Courses Bangkok. I like how everyone who brought a laptop, brought a Macbook, as you can see from the pictures.






Full album here.
Afterwards was the usual beer meetup at Singha Beer Park a few blocks away (towards Asok BTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Transformers 3 Set in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I just realized I never formally made a blog post on all the pictures I took of the Transformers 3 set in Chicago of Summer of 2010. Many of the photos I took weren&amp;rsquo;t that far from the office I was working at.
Here you go, enjoy the albums:  2010 Transformers 3 Set 2010 July 17 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 1 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 19 Transformers Set</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from January 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 01:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>A recent group I started to attend is BKK Web Meetup (short for Web Design, UX Design and Web Development Meetup Group in Bangkok).
Below are the pictures I took from the January Meetup: Computer Vision with Android. The presentation is by Andrea Gagliardi La Gala.







Full album here.
Some video links Andrea provided for those who couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend:  Optical recognition of ID documents with Android phone Indoor monitoring with Android phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech communities in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 13:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Thailand now for a little over two months now. Although I miss the US a lot, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot of new things, and meeting a lot of wonderful people here in Bangkok. In other words, I&amp;rsquo;m having a blast out here.
The day after I arrived, November 9 2010, I attended a Bangkok Hackerspace meetup at True Coffee (Siam Soi 2). I walked in thinking it was going to be something akin to Jelly Chicago and community building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey from Windows to Mac</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/my-journey-from-windows-to-mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 02:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/my-journey-from-windows-to-mac/</guid>
      <description>So back in May of 2010, I bought myself a Macbook Pro. I bought it for several reasons:
 I wanted a new toy/gadget to play with. I wanted to try the only other operating system (OS) I haven&#39;t really spent much time on (OS X). I wanted to get away from Microsoft technologies  Those were and are the 3 main reasons.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a little over 8 months of usage and I absolutely love it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traveling with eBags</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 09:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/12/traveling-with-ebags/</guid>
      <description>As many of you may or may not know, I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling a lot lately. From July&amp;rsquo;s trip to the San Diego Comic-Con, to September&amp;rsquo;s All-You-Can-Jet pass, to even now, Thailand! It&amp;rsquo;s been awesome, but there&amp;rsquo;s a special shout-out I need to give recognition to: eBags.com
On October 5, 2010, at the end of my All-You-Can-Jet vacationing, after hitting up 5 cities in one month, my main traveling bag: the Mother Lode eTech Junior 25 Wheeled Duffel, had ripped at the baggage claim at O&amp;rsquo;hare International Airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston University&#39;s CS lab in 2001 and 2010</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/11/boston-universitys-cs-lab-in-2001-and-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/11/boston-universitys-cs-lab-in-2001-and-2010/</guid>
      <description>In September 2010, I had the opportunity to visit Boston as part of my All-You-Can-Jet pass from JetBlue. As part of my trip out there, I visited Boston University, where I attended as an undergraduate from 1997 to 2001. While visiting the campus, I took some pictures of the undergraduate CS lab, where I worked long long ago. Different, but yet the same!
Back in 2001: Windows machines running Windows 2000 Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from October Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 21:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Alt.net on October 13, 2010 Event: SpecFlow: One Step closer to Executable Specifications
Speaker: Sergio Pereira
http://sergiopereira.com/blog
Chicago Alt.net website





Full album here.
Chicago ACM on October 18, 2010 Event: From Spider-Man to Avatar: Achieving Photoreal Digital Actors
Speaker: Paul Debevec from USC Institute for Creative Technologies www.debevec.org
Chicago ACM website



Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from September Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>There were only two events I attended last month:  Nerd Diner:NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!! Chicago Alt.net: Selenium 101.3: Practical Functional Testing Techniques 
The Nerd Dinner was at Rock Bottom and was arranged by Shankar Ramachandran. Very chill meetup, great talks with awesome .Net developers. I hope there can be more of these.










Full album for Nerd Dinnerhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from the August 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I was on a bit of a vacation in July so I forgot to post August events before the month started.
Chicago Ruby Meetup on August 3, 2010 Presentations on: Agile with Pivotal Tracker and jQuery and Rails 3.0





Full album here.
Chicago Alt.net on August 11, 2010 Fawad Halim gave a presentation on Python for .Net Developers.




Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Thai fonts onto an Android device</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/installing-thai-fonts-onto-an-android-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/installing-thai-fonts-onto-an-android-device/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve received numerous requests asking for help on how to install Thai fonts onto an Android device after my initial post on Rooting my Nexus One and installing Thai fonts. Since I do update my Android phone with the CyanogenMod ROM quite often (which wipes the Thai fonts on each install), I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share a simple shell script to help get Thai fonts onto Android.
This post does not cover how to root an Android device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Happiness by Tony Hsieh</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago, Tony Hsieh, the CEO of Zappos, offered free copies of his new book, Delivering Happiness: A Path to Profits, Passion, and Purposevia his twitter. I hopped on it right away and got myself two copies of it by using two different email addresses. I gave one away to a friend and kept the remaining copy to myself to keep and read.
I really enjoyed this book. It&amp;rsquo;s inspirational how Tony Hsieh started his company out, taking the big risks he did, despite the economic conditions of the Dot Com bubble burst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Android Photoshoot with my new Camera Lens</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/an-android-photoshoot-with-my-new-camera-lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/an-android-photoshoot-with-my-new-camera-lens/</guid>
      <description>I got my new lens in the mail yesterday. It&amp;rsquo;s a Canon EF 50mm f/1.8 II Camera Lens.

I was studying at the time, but once I got my email notification that it arrived, I rushed to pick it up and did a little photoshoot of my Android toy at the table I was studying at. I played with the aperture for most of the shoot (in AV mode). Afterwards, I used Adobe Lightroom to polish it up a bit (created a set of Black &amp;amp; White photos too).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!!
Wednesday, September 1, 2010 at 6:15 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby
Tuesday, September 7, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
There will be a meetup on Mongoid &amp;amp; Rails 3.
Chicago Alt.net
Wednesday, September 8, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM (CT)
Should be a talk about Selenium by @bwilken.
Chicago Ruby Hack Night
Thursday, September 9, 2010 from 5:30 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Chicago and the Millennium Park Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was at an event last week at the rooftop of 63 E. Lake Street and I was able to take some photos of the Millennium Park Bean and parts of Chicago.



These photos were taken with my Canon Digital Rebel XT with a Canon EF-S 55-250mm f/4.0-5.6 IS Telephoto Zoom Lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My visit to Blizzard Entertainment HQ</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/my-visit-to-blizzard-entertainment-hq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 10:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/my-visit-to-blizzard-entertainment-hq/</guid>
      <description>On my way to Los Angeles from San Diego, I had the opportunity to stop by the Blizzard Entertainment HQ in Irvine, California. I must say that they have an awesome campus with very developer/designer friendly offices. Toys and models everywhere!
Here some pictures, full set of pictures can be found here.










For more pictures, check out: Inside Blizzard Headquarters [PICS]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2010</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/san-diego-comic-con-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2010 01:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/san-diego-comic-con-2010/</guid>
      <description>Went to the San Diego Comic Con this year. First time. Awesome.
Preview Night (July 21, 2010) Arrived and checked out the exhibit hall.






SDCC 2010 Preview Night album
Day 1 (July 22, 2010) First official day of Comic Con. Attended the OneRing.net panel and the BSG/Caprica panel.









SDCC 2010 Day 1 album
Day 2 (July 23, 2010) This day was Star Wars day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from the July 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/pictures-from-the-july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 14:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/pictures-from-the-july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I made sure to take a lot of photos this month.
Tuesday July 6, 2010 Chicago Ruby had a meeting over at ThoughtWorks. Snapped a few photos there. Very cool talks. And of course, pizza. You can sign up for these meetings at: Chicago Ruby Meetup. There was a Hack Night on Thursday of the week, but I did not take any photos.
Presentations by @chrisjpowers and @blakesmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 09:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Plenty of events to attend for the month of July! This will be the first time I&amp;rsquo;m attending a Ruby event, so I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited. Sadly, things may be a bit over my head since I just started doing Ruby.
Tuesday July 6, 2010 at 6:00 PM (CT)
ChicagoRuby: Downtown- Two Talks: HTML5 WebSockets &amp;amp; Contributing to Open Source
Thursday July 8, 2010 at 5:30 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby Hack Night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2 Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 22:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to start posting pictures I take from various Tech Events I attend. One, I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I want to share visually, what the Tech community looks like. And two, because I&amp;rsquo;m picking up photography as a hobby now.
The pictures below are from Chicago Code Camp, which took place May 1st, 2010 at the Stuart Building at IIT. They were taken by me with my Google Nexus One.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 13:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>A decent amount of Tech events for the month of June here in Chicago:
Wednesday, June 02, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
MVVM with Damon Payne
The Chicago Silverlight User Group (Eventbrite link)
Tuesday, June 8, 2010 from 5:30PM - 7:30PM (CT)
Chicago Agile Project Management Meetup Group
Wednesday, June 09, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Well Behaved JavaScript With Screw.Unit
Chicago Alt.net (Eventbrite link)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>The month of May looks to be an exciting month in Chicago for Tech Events!
Saturday, May 1st 2010 from 8:00 AM - 6:00 PM (CT) Chicago Code Camp 2 will actually be held in Chicago&amp;rsquo;s IIT campus this year! Speakers, presentations, and the agenda have all been posted now.
Here is my tentative schedule that I plan to attend:
9:00 AM - 10:00 AM - Use Git Like a Boss by Kevin Gisi (Ruby)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LinkedIn Mobile Apps: No Love for Android</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/linkedin-mobile-apps-no-love-for-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 01:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/linkedin-mobile-apps-no-love-for-android/</guid>
      <description>Got this in my inbox from LinkedIn. iPhone: check. Blackberry: check. Palm: check&amp;hellip;.
No love for Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Review: Balsamiq Mockups</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/software-review-balsamiq-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/software-review-balsamiq-mockups/</guid>
      <description>I first read about Balsamiq Mockups a few weeks ago on StackOverflow.
In general I agree with what Jeff Atwood and Joel Spolsky said about the product on their podcast (IT Conversations: Episode 47). It really is a simple mockup tool that isn&amp;rsquo;t about being exact and precise, but rather sketchy and fast so you can get your idea down quickly. It makes starting something easy and fast, so you can move on to what&amp;rsquo;s next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/april-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 00:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/april-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of April 2010 Tech events in Chicago that I&amp;rsquo;m aware of. Most of them, I shall be attending.
Thursday, April 01, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM (CT) Mobile Visionary Mixer - Effective Networking at Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Hottest Brazilian Steakhouse! (Eventbrite link) I attended this event already and really enjoyed it. Meet and spoke to a lot of great people and hope to attend future events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rework by Jason Fried and David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 14:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Rework by the founders of 37Signals. I really really enjoyed the book. The chapters were concise and to the point.
Here are my favorite chapters:
 Learning from mistakes is overrated Planning is guessing No time is no excuse Outside money is Plan Z Embrace constraints Focus on won&#39;t change Interruption is the enemy of productivity Meetings are toxic Your estimates suck Underdo your competition Say no by default Emulate chefs Drug dealers get it right Do it yourself first Everybody works They&#39;re not thirteen Don&#39;t scar on the first cut  I highly recommend people to pick up a copy if you are at all interested in how a great business should be run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tech User Groups and Events for March 2010</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/chicago-tech-user-groups-and-events-for-march-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 19:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/chicago-tech-user-groups-and-events-for-march-2010/</guid>
      <description>The first two weeks this month I attended several Chicago user group meetings and events. I wanted to recap my experience with many of them since it was my first time attending several of the events.
Tuesday March 2, 2010 Chicago Agile Project Management Meetup Group I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of this meetup group for a while now. I really made an effort to attend this one since the topic was on estimating projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programmer Cartoon: Your Company App</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/02/programmer-cartoon-your-company-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 19:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/02/programmer-cartoon-your-company-app/</guid>
      <description>I was watching Joel Spolsky Tech Talk at Google about StackOverflow, and he brought up a URL on &amp;ldquo;programmer cartoon&amp;rdquo;. The link is: http://stackoverflow.com/questions/84556/whats-your-favorite-programmer-cartoon.
This may be my new favorite&amp;hellip;

Here is the original link to the comic post:http://stuffthathappens.com/blog/2008/03/05/simplicity/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coders at Work and Duct Tape Programming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 21:25:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Coders at Work! I really enjoyed the interviews with Jamie Zawinksi, Douglas Crockford, Brendan Eich, and Ken Thompson. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too interested in compilers and the much older systems some of the programmers once developed in. I must admit, I had a short attention span reading over those sections.
Anyway, the reason I picked this book up was because back in late September to early October 2009, I remember reading several blog posts on duct tape programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android SDK issue on Windows 7 x64</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/android-sdk-issue-on-windows-7-x64/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 18:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/android-sdk-issue-on-windows-7-x64/</guid>
      <description>I recently installed the Android SDK and Eclipse (32-bit) onto my Windows 7 Ultimate 64-bit machine. First thing I wanted to do was go through the Android Hello World Tutorial.
Well, I ran into the following error message:
&amp;lsquo;java&amp;rsquo; is not recognized as an internal or external command, operable program, or batch file. SWT folder &amp;ldquo; does not exist. Please set ANDROID_SWT to point to the folder containing swt.jar for your platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rooting my Nexus One and installing Thai fonts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/rooting-my-nexus-one-and-installing-thai-fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2010 00:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/rooting-my-nexus-one-and-installing-thai-fonts/</guid>
      <description>I just finished rooting my Nexus One and installed Thai fonts onto it. I had to use several websites to complete this task, but I wanted to collect them all into once nice place for any stumblers. The purpose of installing Thai fonts onto my Nexus One was to have the ability to read Thai on my Facebook app as well as some Thai websites.
Here&amp;rsquo;s how to do it:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Tech and Programming News Feeds</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/my-favorite-tech-and-programming-news-feeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 12:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/my-favorite-tech-and-programming-news-feeds/</guid>
      <description>I previously posted on my favorite tech podcasts, so I wanted to post a little snippet of my favorite tech RSS feeds from Google Reader. I read a lot more than I list here, but these are my absolute favorites.
My favorite Tech RSS Feeds:  Lifehacker RSS  Gizmodo RSS  Mashable! RSS Silicon Alley Insider RSS   My favorite Programming RSS Feeds:  Reddit Programming RSS  Hacker News RSS  Coding Horror RSS  Devlicio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My New Phone: Google&#39;s Nexus One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/my-new-phone-googles-nexus-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2010 22:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/my-new-phone-googles-nexus-one/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday Google gave a presentation on the Google Nexus One. I watched it on the Gizmodo Liveblog. Ten minutes after reading the blog and looking at the pictures, I was sold. I knew I was eventually going to get it, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t know until that moment that that was the moment I was going to get it.
I bought the phone yesterday, 1/5/2010, at 1:05pm. Overnight FedEx shipping (free). It arrived today at 1:22pm.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooked on Tech Podcasts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/12/hooked-on-tech-podcasts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2009 00:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/12/hooked-on-tech-podcasts/</guid>
      <description>Lately Ive been immersed in code at work as well as at home for a side project.&amp;#160; But I dont like to code in silence all the time, so I got myself re-hooked on to listening to podcasts, while I develop.
Here are the direct links to the current individual podcasts I subscribe to:
 .Net Rocks 37signals Podcast Alt.NET Podcast dnrTV Hanselminutes Pragmatic Podcasts Software Engineering Radio - The Podcast for Professional Software Developers The Thirsty Developer  Podcast Windows Weekly  Or if you really trust my taste, heres a single RSS feed to all the podcasts I subscribe to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I love about Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/09/what-i-love-about-microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2009 07:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/09/what-i-love-about-microsoft/</guid>
      <description>I am primarily a Microsoft software developer. But I was not always a M$FT user/developer so to speak. I used to use Windows 3.1 back in the heyday, followed a little with Windows 95&amp;frasl;98. But by then, I was a college student at Boston University. The computer labs there had primarily Unix terminals and Solaris boxes. So I naturally had to use and learn these technologies. Everything from using the command shell, pine, star office, gcc compiler, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaLa.com: A Better Alternative to iTunes</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/05/lala.com-a-better-alternative-to-itunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 11:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/05/lala.com-a-better-alternative-to-itunes/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, I tried out iTunes and really enjoyed the experience. I came from a Winamp background and really liked having a fast loading application. On top of that, I am a computer geek, so I already know where all my files are on the OS filesystem.
Anyway, after using iTunes for a little over a year and hundreds of songs purchased later, it was starting up slower and slower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Microsoft Development Tools for Students on DreamSpark</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/free-microsoft-development-tools-for-students-on-dreamspark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2009 17:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/free-microsoft-development-tools-for-students-on-dreamspark/</guid>
      <description>On Microsoft Dreamspark, they have a very nice list of Microsoft development tools that you can download for FREE. Mind you, these aren&amp;rsquo;t just the free editions of their software, these are Standard to Professional editions that individuals and companies pay a lot of money for.
The catch is that you need to be a student with a student email. (Something like student.name@myuniversity.edu).
They currently offer:
 Microsoft SQL Server 2008 Developer Edition Microsoft Visual Studio 2005 Professional Edition  Microsoft Visual Studio 2008 Professional Edition  Microsoft Expression Studio 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tropicana&#39;s New Logo Design</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/tropicanas-new-logo-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2009 18:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/tropicanas-new-logo-design/</guid>
      <description>This morning I had a peanut butter and jelly sandwich, toasted. It was delicious. Along with it I had some orange juice (OJ), but not just any OJ, Minute Maid OJ.

For years I&amp;rsquo;ve been more of a Tropicana OJ kind-of-guy, but with Tropicana&amp;rsquo;s somewhat recent logo switch on their cartons, I just felt compelled to switch.
The reason? I just don&amp;rsquo;t get why they changed their logo.
What they had before made sense (see left carton).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Web App: Google Reader</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/my-favorite-web-app-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Feb 2009 08:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/my-favorite-web-app-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>Google Reader is by far my favorite web application. I reorganized many of the labels as well as added/deleted some feeds. But I truly consider this app as my gateway to the Internet. I have it set as a tab that always opens up in any of my browsers.
What makes it my favorite is that it collects all my favorite websites/blogs into one simple screen. I don&amp;rsquo;t care about actually visiting the website unless it has an article/blog post that I&amp;rsquo;m actually interested in commenting or reading comments on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vending Machine at Work</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 22:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</guid>
      <description>This is my vending machine at work. I happen to like Reeses Peanut Butter Cups. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a sweet tooth, but it&amp;rsquo;s the only snack in the entire machine I would buy.
Can you see what&amp;rsquo;s wrong?

It&amp;rsquo;s behind a 100 Grand, one of the worst pieces of candy in the entire machine. I haven&amp;rsquo;t enjoyed a 100 Grand since I was a kid, which is probably the age of the candy since everybody knows it&amp;rsquo;s stale and gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Tech Events in Chicago for February</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 23:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Twestival! Date: Thursday, February 12, 2009
Time: 6:30 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Place: Catalyst Ranch - 656 W Randolph Dr Chicago IL
Cost: $10 donation
RSVP: http://www.chicagotwestival.eventbrite.com
Event: TECH cocktail Chicago 10 Date: Thursday, February 19, 2009
Time: 6:30pm - 9pm
Place: John Barleycorns - 3524 N Clark (where it always is)
Cost: $0 (per usual)
RSVP: http://techcocktail-chicago-10.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got  a Roomba for Christmas</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/i-got-a-roomba-for-christmas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2009 23:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/i-got-a-roomba-for-christmas/</guid>
      <description>For Christmas 2008, I got a iRobot 560 Roomba Vacuuming Robot, Black and Silveras a combined gift from my sisters and their boyfriends. I must say, that this is the best Xmas gift I&amp;rsquo;ve ever received other than the Nintendo Entertainment System (NES), around 1988-1989. Which was 20 years ago&amp;hellip; wow.

The Roomba actually does a pretty decent job of cleaning my apartment. My apartment is about 620 sq ft and mostly carpet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s next for Social Media?:  GPS-enabled applications</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/whats-next-for-social-media-gps-enabled-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2009 19:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/whats-next-for-social-media-gps-enabled-applications/</guid>
      <description>There are some really cool GPS applications out there that are about to push the boundaries of technology and social media as we know it. I remember years ago when I shared a link to Loopt with friends, pretty much everyone didn&amp;rsquo;t like the idea of sharing that much information with each other. Today, I already have a few friends jumping onto to use such an app. Google has now also released a similar application out called Google Latitude, but based on their Google login system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signed up for the 2009 Shamrock Shuffle 8k run</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 22:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</guid>
      <description>After hearing that several friends will be doing the Shamrock Shuffle this year, I decided I wanted to challenge myself to it again. I did it two years ago, in 2007. I did little to no training for that, and ran at about a 13min/mile pace. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to bring that down to a 10min/mile pace with some proper training.
I look at this as a way to start out 2009 and hopefully, the rest of my life: As a fresh start to making a better me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Combinatorial Mathematics</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/basic-combinatorial-mathematics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2009 11:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/basic-combinatorial-mathematics/</guid>
      <description>I absolutely love reading CodingHorror.com. It&amp;rsquo;s easily one of my favorite blogs to read about problem solving from the viewpoint of a programming/developer. Recently, Jeff Atwood posted a problem:
Let&#39;s say, hypothetically speaking, you met someone who told you they had two children, and one of them is a girl. What are the odds that person has a boy and a girl? I was surprised by the number of readers who responded who got it wrong, very wrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up WRT54G as a wireless bridge with DD-WRT</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/12/setting-up-wrt54g-as-a-wireless-bridge-with-dd-wrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2008 23:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/12/setting-up-wrt54g-as-a-wireless-bridge-with-dd-wrt/</guid>
      <description>My parents have a Thai TV ethernet box of some kind so they can tune in to their Thai stations, shows, and even radio on their HDTV. However, I had to run a 50 foot CAT5 cable from the upstairs to the first floor great room, which is quite messy. So for Christmas this year, I bought them a Linksys-Cisco WRT54GL Wireless-G Broadband Router.
The setup I wanted was to have the Thai TV box, which uses an ethernet port for all data, connect to the wireless router, and have the wireless router connect to the wireless router upstairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Friday is just Stupid</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/black-friday-is-just-stupid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2008 11:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/black-friday-is-just-stupid/</guid>
      <description>To my recollection, I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever participated in a Black Friday event back in 2006. And it was really really tough. In a nutshell, I went shopping at midnight, went home to nap, then went out again to shop during the day, totally 15 some hours of shopping by day&amp;rsquo;s end. It&amp;rsquo;s something that I hope to never do again in my life. (Note: I only did this because some girls wanted to do some shopping).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Firefox Add-ons</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-favorite-firefox-add-ons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2008 00:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-favorite-firefox-add-ons/</guid>
      <description>Firefox is my favorite web browser. In this day and age, I see no need to use Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s Internet Explorer (IE). Although I do like Google Chrome, it&amp;rsquo;s still not available for Linux yet. But this isn&amp;rsquo;t an entry about browsers and the pros and cons of each. (I do plan on writing about browsers and operating systems in the near future.)
This is the list of add-ons that I install on any computer I use running Firefox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Impressions of the G1 running Android</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-impressions-of-the-g1-running-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 22:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-impressions-of-the-g1-running-android/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had my G1 for a few weeks now. My overall impressions are pretty good. I like the touch screen, I like the free applications available through the market app, and I definitely enjoy the web browsing experience on the 3G network over my old Blackberry Pearl on the EDGE network.
But I do have a few complaints:
 Battery Life is too short. I can maybe go for a maximum of 2 days without a recharge if I very minimal use of the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Went to the Obama Rally in Grant Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 01:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</guid>
      <description>I witnessed history in the making last night by attending Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s Election Night in Grant Park.
How I got the ticket: Sheer Luck
It all started after I got my lunch and was heading back to the office. A lady one floor beneath mine hopped on the elevator early (she wanted to go down, I was going up, but a co-worker of hers just got off), and she mentioned to her co-worker that if got his ticket yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installed Ubuntu Linux onto my Thinkpad T60</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/installed-ubuntu-linux-onto-my-thinkpad-t60/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2008 21:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/installed-ubuntu-linux-onto-my-thinkpad-t60/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I installed Ubuntu Linux onto my Lenovo Thinkpad T60 laptop. I wanted to keep Windos XP Professional installed, so I chose to dual-boot it using GRUB. I also upgraded the 40 GB hard drive to a 250 GB hard drive using a laptop hard drive upgrade kit. I copied the files over to the new drive, and then installed Ubuntu 8.04 (Hardy Heron) in another partition. It was amazingly simple.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Blog Entry from my G1</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/my-first-blog-entry-from-my-g1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2008 08:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/my-first-blog-entry-from-my-g1/</guid>
      <description>My experience with the G1 has been pretty awesome so far. It arrived yesterday to my apartment&amp;rsquo;s front desk at 12:05pm. I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to it until about 5pm. I charged it and have been playing with it since. I&amp;rsquo;ll probably do a review of it later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>T-mobile to ship G1 early?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/t-mobile-to-ship-g1-early/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2008 18:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/t-mobile-to-ship-g1-early/</guid>
      <description>As my friend Ben pointed out, it&amp;rsquo;s possible that our pre-ordered G1 phones will arrive earlier than expected. Tomorrow, Monday, October 20, 2008 to be exact. Upon checking my order status on UPS.com, I found the following:
So it looks like my Google phone is here in Chicago, and is set to ship tomorrow!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting the G1 in one week</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/getting-the-g1-in-one-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 19:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/getting-the-g1-in-one-week/</guid>
      <description>Next week, on October 22, I should be getting my pre-ordered T-Mobile G1, in black. Sadly though, in order to pre-order this device, I had to extend my contract with T-Mobile until September 28, 2010. I found out the exact date by a letter they sent me thanking me for choosing to continue my relationship and extending my contract with them.
Let me get one thing straight, I extended the contract only to get my hand on a device running Google Android.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 9</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</guid>
      <description>Another digerati networking event coming up in November! Last time I went I had a pretty good time talking with various people in the Chicago tech community. Only wish my company would sport me with actual up-to-date business cards!

When: Thursday, November 6, 2008 - 6:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST Where: John Barleycorn Wrigleyville Tech Cocktail Chicago 9
I also recently joined the community: iam.techcocktail.com
You can see my personal blog&amp;rsquo;s previous posting on Tech Cocktail 8 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Google Docs as a Collaboration Tool</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/using-google-docs-as-a-collaboration-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2008 23:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/using-google-docs-as-a-collaboration-tool/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I visited San Francisco (SF) for the first time with my baby sister. My sister was busy with law school, so the planning was mostly up to me, and I needed recommendations on what to do there. So I started a Google Docs for myself at first and then added collaborators to help edit it. These collaborators were all friends from SF.
It then turned into a wiki-style collaboration document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Math behind TinyURL</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/09/the-math-behind-tinyurl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 00:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/09/the-math-behind-tinyurl/</guid>
      <description>TinyURLis a website that condenses a submitted URL, usually a long one, into a short readable URL on tinyurl&amp;rsquo;s website. In turn, this shorter URL then redirects to the original url. This is quite handy.
As of this writing, the text below their logo reads:
Making long URLs usable! More than 90 million of them. Over 1.5 billion hits/month. From what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen, they only use letters and numbers. So that gives us 26 possible letters, which are not case-sensitive (in other words, &amp;ldquo;A&amp;rdquo; is the same as &amp;ldquo;a&amp;rdquo;).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A C# Code Solution for FizzBuzz</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/09/c-code-solution-for-fizzbuzz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2008 22:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/09/c-code-solution-for-fizzbuzz/</guid>
      <description>I read a slashdot article earlier today which lead me to a Coding Horror article: Why Can&amp;rsquo;t Programmers.. Program?. This lead me to the FizBuzz problem, which prompted me to write my own quickie solution in C# (as a console application).
Problem: Write a program that prints the numbers from 1 to 100. But for multiples of three print &amp;ldquo;Fizz&amp;rdquo; instead of the number and for the multiples of five print &amp;ldquo;Buzz&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Free Software Recommendations for 2008</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/best-free-software-recommendations-for-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 11:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/best-free-software-recommendations-for-2008/</guid>
      <description>For almost ten years now, I still find myself fixing computers for friends. It&amp;rsquo;s not so much hardware these days as it is cleaning out viruses and installing software to handle a certain task. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind so much, but I just hope my friends learn something from what I do and explain rather than to just rely on me to fix everything for them each and every time.
Anyway, for protecting a computer running Windows, an Antivirus software is required along with receiving regular updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook to become the new AOL?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/facebook-to-become-the-new-aol/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2008 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/facebook-to-become-the-new-aol/</guid>
      <description>I used to use Prodigy as my Internet Service Provider (ISP) back in the 1990s. It was fun to post to bulletin boards and participate in various discussions. I then jumped over to use America Online (AOL) because of it&amp;rsquo;s nicer interface, live chat rooms, email, instant messaging, buddy lists, and overall better features. To be honest, back then I used the Internet for two things: to talk about wrestling and find Dragonball Z pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development Comic</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/software-development-comic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2008 13:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/software-development-comic/</guid>
      <description>I find this comic to be hilarious.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tapping into the Cloud</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/tapping-into-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2008 23:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/tapping-into-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago I envisioned a world where computers would return back to acting more like terminal PCs connected to a mainframe. A world where accessing files/applications locally would be a thing of the past. In a way, that&amp;rsquo;s what Cloud Computing seems to be about. A user can be on any computer (albeit a PC, a Mac, or a Linux box), all that is required is Internet connection and a web browser, and the user can run most of his/her computing needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Software Development</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/agile-software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/agile-software-development/</guid>
      <description>Up to this point in my consulting career, too often I&amp;rsquo;ve seen consultants (myself included) spend time writing documents describing what will be and won&amp;rsquo;t be included in the project. And pretty much every time, whatever the client committed to on paper, isn&amp;rsquo;t what the client wanted in the end. Requirements change between the start and end of a project. This is software development as it truly is.
Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong, I&amp;rsquo;m not saying documentation is bad all together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Digg Meetup Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/thoughts-on-digg-meetup-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/thoughts-on-digg-meetup-chicago/</guid>
      <description>First off, let me say that I enjoy reading some of the articles posted on Digg&amp;hellip; well, I want to emphasize some. It&amp;rsquo;s a voting system, so there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of crap stories, and just a few winners here and there. But sometimes those stories are worth it. Sometimes&amp;hellip;
Anyway, I went to the Digg Meetup event yesterday with a co-worker and I thought it was just ok. Kevin Rose spoke a little, threw out some free schwag, interacted with the crowd, typical stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Digg Meet-Up Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 01:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I published this on my other blog, but wanted to post here too. Looks like Digg is coming to Chicago!

Wednesday, July 23, 2008 6-10 pm
SmartBar
3730 N. Clark Street
Chicago, Illinois 60613</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Social Dev Camp Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 17:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I hope I can make this! From the facebook event link, I found: Chicago Interactive Design/Development Meetup Group. So interesting!
SocialDevCampChicago Saturday, August 9th 2008
8:30am-6:00pm
at Illinois Institute of Technology McCormick Tribune Center (http://www.iit.edu/mtcc/)
Facebook event: http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=20586291919
If you are developer in the midwest you might be interested in checking out the upcoming SocialDevCampChicago. SocialDevCampChicago is an unconference for people passionate about social networks, web applications, platform development, new media, and any of the exciting (but messy) topics in-between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished reading the Groundswell</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 03:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading Groundswell: Winning in a World Transformed by Social Technologies. Probably one of the best books I&amp;rsquo;ve read this year thus far.
 What Is Groundswell? It&#39;s a book by two Forrester analysts with practical, data-based strategies for companies that want to harness the power of social technologies like blogs, social networks, and YouTube. (source: Forrester) I absolutely love reading case studies in these IT Business books. I finished my MS in Information Systems 2 years ago last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 8</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about going to the Tech Cocktail Chicago 8 event this evening. I&amp;rsquo;m just so curious as to what kind of exciting tech people/companies are here in Chicago!

John Barleycorn Wrigleyville
3524 N Clark St
Upstairs
Chicago, IL 60657 Thursday, May 29, 2008 from 06:30 PM - 08:00 PM (CT)
http://tech-cocktail-chicago-8.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where is the Blogger Community?</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/where-is-the-blogger-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2008 20:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/where-is-the-blogger-community/</guid>
      <description>I recently started a new blog over at Vox.com after my older sister recommended me the site after a friend of hers recommended it to her. It&amp;rsquo;s a social blogging website that emphasizes on the concept of a neighborhood; essentially socializing with other people with common interests, etc.
Anyway, I still really like Blogger, but where the heck is the community? I&amp;rsquo;m sure I can search for it through Google, but can&amp;rsquo;t there be some kind of interface that can help users find each other?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Man Bags</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/03/my-man-bags/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2008 21:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/03/my-man-bags/</guid>
      <description>I went on an online shopping spree earlier this week and bought some Man bags for myself. I only bought 2, but from the set below, I&amp;rsquo;m showing 2 because I ordered the one on the left (the more green/olive color), but I received the one on the right (brownish/dark-green). At first I was going to send it back, but I grew attached to the color and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to go through the hassle of sending it back.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yellow Dog Linux on my PS3</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/02/yellow-dog-linux-on-my-ps3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2008 12:02:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/02/yellow-dog-linux-on-my-ps3/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend, mostly on Saturday I spent doing 2 main things:
 Tried to install Microsoft Visual Studio .Net 2008 onto my Lenovo Thinkpad T60 laptop Installed Linux onto my PS3  The development tool installation didn&amp;rsquo;t take well at all, but the Linux install went very well, a bit long to download, install, and configure everything, but overall very well. The distro I chose was Yellow Dog Linux, specifically for the PS3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belkin&#39;s Pre N Router Laggy on PS3 network</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/02/belkins-pre-n-router-laggy-on-ps3-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2008 12:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/02/belkins-pre-n-router-laggy-on-ps3-network/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the better part of this cold weekend indoors trying to configure my PS3 to work on the Playstation Network. My problem was that I would get lag when playing Puzzle Fighter 3 Turbo HD Remix. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using the Belkin Pre-N Router for the past few months for everything but gaming and have been content with it. But frankly, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t play well with my PS3! I went to portforward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PS3 and Bluray is the way to go... for now</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/ps3-and-bluray-is-the-way-to-go...-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 23:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/ps3-and-bluray-is-the-way-to-go...-for-now/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a PS3 owner, but mostly for the opposite reasons according to a co-worker. Most people own a PS3 for the games and then the blu-ray movies is a big plus. I like it for the blu-ray movie playing ability, and then the games are a plus. And with the recent announcement that Warner is going to be blu-ray exclusive too, it pretty much seals the fate of the HDDVD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Free Software of 2008 (so far)</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/best-free-software-of-2008-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2008 10:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/best-free-software-of-2008-so-far/</guid>
      <description>I find myself reinstalling software on another friend&amp;rsquo;s laptop yet again. What was the problem? Computer virii, trojan horses, adware, and spyware made the system unstable. How did it get this way? Overall, it&amp;rsquo;s because of not having a good understanding of computers, but in particular, peer-to-peer(P2P) programs such as BearShare.
Here is a list of the most common FREE programs I recommend for typical users:
 Antivirus: Avast Home Edition or AVG Free Firewall: Comodo Firewall Web Browser: Mozilla Firefox Spyware detection: Microsoft Defender Image Editing: Paint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking forward to 2008</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/looking-forward-to-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 19:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/01/looking-forward-to-2008/</guid>
      <description>As 2007 comes to a close, it marks the end of one year, and the beginning of another. So too does it bring an end more or less of my blogging on spong.org. It was a personal side project of I started 9 years ago before blogs and other free services were available. Now I&amp;rsquo;m reading to officially say that I&amp;rsquo;m stopping development on it as I have other things in my life I wish to focus on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new mp3 player: Sansa e280</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2007/11/my-new-mp3-player-sansa-e280/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2007 10:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2007/11/my-new-mp3-player-sansa-e280/</guid>
      <description>I got myself a new mp3 player, the Sansa e280. I used to have an Apple iPod mini, but the battery life on that device was just horrible after less than one year. I was thinking of getting a new Ipod, but I was sick of Apple&amp;rsquo;s proprietary music format. I love iTunes, but it&amp;rsquo;s a bit bloated. So now I use either plain old winamp or the relatively new open source, Songbird.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>