<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meetup on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/meetup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meetup on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/meetup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB May Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/la-mongodb-may-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last evening I attended the LA MongDB May Meetup hosted at Factual. Presentations by Tony Tam (@fehguy), CTO of Wordnik and Andrew Hall, Principal Engineer of uSamp. I had a great time hearing about how mongoDB is being used by two different companies.
In N Out Burgers and fries served instead of pizza! 



Tony Tam presenting 





Andrew Hall presenting</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coworking at NextSpace LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/coworking-at-nextspace-la/</guid>
      <description>Jelly LA held a free coworking day at NextSpace in Culver City this past Friday. I got a little tour of the place and was very impressed. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to a few coworking offices in LA already (CoLoft, BlankSpaces, and Kleverdog), and I can honestly say that this is my favorite to cowork in. One, it&amp;rsquo;s conveniently located in Culver City, where I currently live in. Two, it&amp;rsquo;s got a great amount of space, offices, and little nooks to work in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET April Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 21:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/ladotnet-april-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended the LADOTNET April meetup on&amp;nbsp;Building a Rich Web Experience with jQuery, Ajax and .NET&amp;nbsp;presentation by James Johnson. Good meetup with a very decent turnout considering it was a nice day out and NCAA finals was on
For full set of pictures I&amp;rsquo;ve taken at meetups I&amp;rsquo;ve been to this year, click here.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Last night I attended the Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown meetup. I arrived early and walked to the Walt Disney Concert Hall to do some HDR shots. Upon arriving there, I immediately regretted not bringing my 16-35mm f/2.8 L lens. So made due with my recently purchased 24-105 f/4 L lens, which I really haven&amp;rsquo;t used that much yet.
I spent most of the evening on my own going at my own pace to take pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</guid>
      <description>Over this past weekend, on Sunday, the evening of the NBA All-Star game and Academy Awards, I went to check out a Google+ LA Photowalk in Santa Monica hosted by Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson (aka mySpace Tom).
I had a great time seeing and learning how other photography enthusiasts and professionals see things. I brought my Canon 60D, Canon 16-35mm L lens, and tripod. I regret not bringing another lens with me for some more flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am a Meetup Junkie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2012 05:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/i-am-a-meetup-junkie/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve become a Meetup Junkie. Every month I attend several meetups related to technology and food. I can&amp;rsquo;t seem to get enough of following these interests with other like-minded individuals, in the real world.

I primarily use Meetup to find interesting groups by city. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it in Chicago, Bangkok, San Francisco, and now Los Angeles. It&amp;rsquo;s fantastic and addicting!
But for those who haven&amp;rsquo;t used such a service, it may be somewhat scary&amp;ndash; especially if you are an introvert.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA MongoDB February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-mongodb-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my first MongoDB meetup. They have a twitter account: @lamongodb. The meetup was hosted at Factual Inc.
Anand &amp;ldquo;Kumi&amp;rdquo; Nandakumar (@kumi360) presented MongoDB + Node.js design decisions for Jumpspoon. Nuri Halperin presented MongoDB vs. RDBMS.
Overall a good group. I look forward to attend future meetups and learn more about how mongodb is being used.
You can find the pictures I took at meetups in 2012 in this album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Small Business Web Guide Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/small-business-web-guide-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to a Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub meetup at Kleverdog. The topic was&amp;nbsp;Kicking Web Butt: Small Business Web Guide. The presenter was Ed Wu (@edwu) from THINKademic.
The room was primarily designers, which is a nice change for me, as I generally go to developer-centric meetups and events. I hope to be more of a dev-signer (developer/designer).
Here are some of the pictures I took. As usual, you can find the album where I dump all my meetups pictures for this year here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LADOTNET February Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2012 11:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/ladotnet-february-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I attended the LADOTNET February meetup held at Blankspaces last night. The event topic was: Start ups, Tech and Business Trends with John Shiple. The attendance was pretty massive as this user group is getting bigger and bigger every month. I enjoyed the speaker and presentation a lot. I do notice that it&amp;rsquo;s a trend that there are a lot of startup businesses growing outside of Silicon Valley.
More speaker information:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designer&#39;s Hub Meet and Greet</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2012 06:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/designers-hub-meet-and-greet/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Designer&amp;rsquo;s Hub Meet and Greet event hosted at Kleverdog, a co-working space located in Chinatown. This was their first event. It was a very nice meetup about essentially building a community of designers. There were a lot of ideas thrown out about what the group could be about. I personally would like to have a community to turn to, in-person, for me to learn more about the tools and techniques in graphics design&amp;ndash; notably Photoshop, Lightroom, and Aperture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA Ruby/Rails January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 03:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-la-ruby/rails-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night went to the LA Ruby/Rails Meetup hosted at AT&amp;amp;T Interactive. There were two presentations followed by three lightning talks.
Using Ruby with R by Sean Marcia
Rack Middleware as a General Purpose Abstraction by John Bender
Some of the pictures I took are posted below. You can view the picture dump from all pictures I took here.
As a reminder: LA RubyConf is coming up February 2-4, 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LADOTNET January Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2012 11:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-ladotnet-january-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to the LADOTNET January Meetup. The presentation was: Unit Testing/Architecting Apps for Testing with Paul Sheriff.
The turn-out for the meetup was pretty big, maybe fifty to sixty people, with a fair amount of recruiters. The LADOTNET meetup was held at Blankspaces. There is an upcoming SoCal Code Camp coming up on the weekend of January 28 and 29, 2012.
I have a new album where I will dump all pictures I take from Meetups for this upcoming year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from SF Ruby December Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-sf-ruby-december-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2011 12:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-sf-ruby-december-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I drove up to San Francisco from LA to check out the SF Ruby group. The drive was long, but worth it as I got to meet some interesting people. The meetup was hosted at ZenDesk. Being from Chicago and now living in LA, I never before heard so much talk about venture capital (VCs) coming from developers. I think there really is a culture difference in SF compared to other cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from LA DotNet December Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 15:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/12/pictures-from-la-dotnet-december-meetup/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in living in Los Angeles for two months now. About a month ago I finally bought a car to get around in. On Monday, December 5, 2011, I was able to attend my first the Los Angeles .Net Developer&amp;rsquo;s Group hosted at Blankspaces.
There were two presentations:
 Daniel Egan presented on Diving into Windows Phone Market: Should I make the jump? Henry Lee presented on Making Money with Windows Phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Objective-C and iOS for .NET Developers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my favorite local user group, Chicago Alt.net (@ChicagoAltNet).
Eduardo Scoz presented on Objective-C and iOS. Great talk and a very big turnout. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen this many developers show up for an Alt.net meetup here since Uncle Bob Martin did a presentation.
Here are some of the photos I took. If you are looking for a full set of photos I took from various meetups I attend, including this one, I dump them all in this Picasa album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Los Angeles Ruby/Rails Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-los-angeles-ruby/rails-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Last week I used my JetBlue BluePass to head out to Los Angeles to attend the LA Ruby Meetup (@laruby) hosted at CoLoft. I was impressed with the turnout, the speakers and presentation, and the audience participation. The format of the meetup was pretty long though. I&amp;rsquo;m used to maybe thirty minutes to one hour of a presentation. They had four presentations lasting about two hours! All very good of course, but I have to admit that it was a bit tiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Alt.net: Coffeescript</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 21:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures I took from tonight&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Alt.net August 2011 meetup on Coffeescript, presented by Fawad Halim.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from July&#39;s Refresh and Ignite Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to too many meetups this month, only three. Sorry, the weather&amp;rsquo;s been either really hot or super rainy. Interestingly when I condensed the meetup names in this blog title, they both hint at refreshing and igniting Chicago.
I already posted on Barcamp Chicago in a previous blog post.
The second meetup, Corey Haines presented on It&amp;rsquo;s All About the Business Value on Wednesday, July 27, 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcamp Chicago at Pumping Station One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 03:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</guid>
      <description>I went to check out Barcamp Chicago earlier this month, on July 9, 2011. It was held at Pumping Station One, a hackerspace here in Chicago. I didn&amp;rsquo;t stay too long, as it was a really nice day out.
Here are most of the pictures I took:
This is the entrance 
After the hallway entrance, this what you first see</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Tech Meetups in May and June</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</guid>
      <description>In May I came across a new group: Refresh Chicago (@refreshchi). So far, their meetups have been pretty good. From their twitter, the group is described as: Monthly meetup for the advancement of Chicago’s designers and developers. Pretty cool.
So here are some pictures I took in May and June, 2011&amp;ndash; post Chicago Code Camp and Rails Conf.
David Kadavy presenting at Refresh Chicago (May 25, 2011)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Meetups for Spring and Summer 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 04:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago for now! Just got off the plane a few days ago. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m almost ready to get back into going to some tech meetups in the US now. A lot of great events coming up!
Chicago Ruby: Downtown - Marking Up the Web with Graffiti
Tuesday, May 3, 2011 at 6pm
To be held at ThoughtWorks.
Chicago Silverlight Users Group
Wednesday, May 4, 2011
To be held at the ITA building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stack Overflow Meetup in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 20:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/04/stack-overflow-meetup-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>On the Stackoverflow blog, it was announced that April 6, 2011 would be Worldwide Stack Overflow Meetup. They created a meetup page at: Stackoverflow Meetup.
BKK Web Meetup also hosted a meetup on IDEs and other dev tools. Presentations were given on Eclipse (by @nadam9) and Vim (by @ches). Our gracious host was, as always, Web Courses Bangkok. Afterwards, we had the usual beer/food meetup at Singha Beer Park not too far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts from the March BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2011 03:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/thoughts-from-the-march-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>The BKK Web Meetup last night was pretty awesome. It was the biggest turnout I&amp;rsquo;ve seen yet, and it was also very interactive. Plenty of discussion, questions, and even stories came from the attendees.
The topic was: Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about hiring and training developers. Benjamin Scherrey was the presenter. Some bullet points that I took away:
 There are some cultural barriers to understand in hiring a Thai/Asian software developer. There are some cultural barriers dealing with Thai clients.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDxBKK Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 01:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/03/tedxbkk-pictures/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks back, on March 3 2011, I attended TEDxBKK over at TCDC at the top floor at Emporium in Bangkok, Thailand. You can also follow them on twitter at @tedxbkk. Overall it was a good turnout, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too enthusiastic about most of the talks though. The one that stuck out the most for me was David Christian&amp;rsquo;s talk in the Knowledge Revolution session.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from February 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 21:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-february-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures from last night&amp;rsquo;s BKK Web Meetup session on Ruby on Rails. The presentation was by Ches Martin. Our gracious host was Web Courses Bangkok. I like how everyone who brought a laptop, brought a Macbook, as you can see from the pictures.






Full album here.
Afterwards was the usual beer meetup at Singha Beer Park a few blocks away (towards Asok BTS).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from January 2011 BKK Web Meetup</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 01:18:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-from-january-2011-bkk-web-meetup/</guid>
      <description>A recent group I started to attend is BKK Web Meetup (short for Web Design, UX Design and Web Development Meetup Group in Bangkok).
Below are the pictures I took from the January Meetup: Computer Vision with Android. The presentation is by Andrea Gagliardi La Gala.







Full album here.
Some video links Andrea provided for those who couldn&amp;rsquo;t attend:  Optical recognition of ID documents with Android phone Indoor monitoring with Android phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech communities in Bangkok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 13:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/01/tech-communities-in-bangkok/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been in Thailand now for a little over two months now. Although I miss the US a lot, I&amp;rsquo;ve been learning a lot of new things, and meeting a lot of wonderful people here in Bangkok. In other words, I&amp;rsquo;m having a blast out here.
The day after I arrived, November 9 2010, I attended a Bangkok Hackerspace meetup at True Coffee (Siam Soi 2). I walked in thinking it was going to be something akin to Jelly Chicago and community building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from October Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 21:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Alt.net on October 13, 2010 Event: SpecFlow: One Step closer to Executable Specifications
Speaker: Sergio Pereira
http://sergiopereira.com/blog
Chicago Alt.net website





Full album here.
Chicago ACM on October 18, 2010 Event: From Spider-Man to Avatar: Achieving Photoreal Digital Actors
Speaker: Paul Debevec from USC Institute for Creative Technologies www.debevec.org
Chicago ACM website



Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from September Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>There were only two events I attended last month:  Nerd Diner:NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!! Chicago Alt.net: Selenium 101.3: Practical Functional Testing Techniques 
The Nerd Dinner was at Rock Bottom and was arranged by Shankar Ramachandran. Very chill meetup, great talks with awesome .Net developers. I hope there can be more of these.










Full album for Nerd Dinnerhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from the August 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I was on a bit of a vacation in July so I forgot to post August events before the month started.
Chicago Ruby Meetup on August 3, 2010 Presentations on: Agile with Pivotal Tracker and jQuery and Rails 3.0





Full album here.
Chicago Alt.net on August 11, 2010 Fawad Halim gave a presentation on Python for .Net Developers.




Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!!
Wednesday, September 1, 2010 at 6:15 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby
Tuesday, September 7, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
There will be a meetup on Mongoid &amp;amp; Rails 3.
Chicago Alt.net
Wednesday, September 8, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM (CT)
Should be a talk about Selenium by @bwilken.
Chicago Ruby Hack Night
Thursday, September 9, 2010 from 5:30 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 09:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Plenty of events to attend for the month of July! This will be the first time I&amp;rsquo;m attending a Ruby event, so I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited. Sadly, things may be a bit over my head since I just started doing Ruby.
Tuesday July 6, 2010 at 6:00 PM (CT)
ChicagoRuby: Downtown- Two Talks: HTML5 WebSockets &amp;amp; Contributing to Open Source
Thursday July 8, 2010 at 5:30 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby Hack Night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 13:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>A decent amount of Tech events for the month of June here in Chicago:
Wednesday, June 02, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
MVVM with Damon Payne
The Chicago Silverlight User Group (Eventbrite link)
Tuesday, June 8, 2010 from 5:30PM - 7:30PM (CT)
Chicago Agile Project Management Meetup Group
Wednesday, June 09, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Well Behaved JavaScript With Screw.Unit
Chicago Alt.net (Eventbrite link)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>The month of May looks to be an exciting month in Chicago for Tech Events!
Saturday, May 1st 2010 from 8:00 AM - 6:00 PM (CT) Chicago Code Camp 2 will actually be held in Chicago&amp;rsquo;s IIT campus this year! Speakers, presentations, and the agenda have all been posted now.
Here is my tentative schedule that I plan to attend:
9:00 AM - 10:00 AM - Use Git Like a Boss by Kevin Gisi (Ruby)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Tech Events in Chicago for February</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 23:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Twestival! Date: Thursday, February 12, 2009
Time: 6:30 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Place: Catalyst Ranch - 656 W Randolph Dr Chicago IL
Cost: $10 donation
RSVP: http://www.chicagotwestival.eventbrite.com
Event: TECH cocktail Chicago 10 Date: Thursday, February 19, 2009
Time: 6:30pm - 9pm
Place: John Barleycorn’s - 3524 N Clark (where it always is)
Cost: $0 (per usual)
RSVP: http://techcocktail-chicago-10.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 9</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</guid>
      <description>Another digerati networking event coming up in November! Last time I went I had a pretty good time talking with various people in the Chicago tech community. Only wish my company would sport me with actual up-to-date business cards!

When: Thursday, November 6, 2008 - 6:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST Where: John Barleycorn Wrigleyville Tech Cocktail Chicago 9
I also recently joined the community: iam.techcocktail.com
You can see my personal blog&amp;rsquo;s previous posting on Tech Cocktail 8 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Digg Meet-Up Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 01:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I published this on my other blog, but wanted to post here too. Looks like Digg is coming to Chicago!

Wednesday, July 23, 2008 6-10 pm
SmartBar
3730 N. Clark Street
Chicago, Illinois 60613</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Social Dev Camp Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 17:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I hope I can make this! From the facebook event link, I found: Chicago Interactive Design/Development Meetup Group. So interesting!
SocialDevCampChicago Saturday, August 9th 2008
8:30am-6:00pm
at Illinois Institute of Technology McCormick Tribune Center (http://www.iit.edu/mtcc/)
Facebook event: http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=20586291919
If you are developer in the midwest you might be interested in checking out the upcoming SocialDevCampChicago. SocialDevCampChicago is an unconference for people passionate about social networks, web applications, platform development, new media, and any of the exciting (but messy) topics in-between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 8</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about going to the Tech Cocktail Chicago 8 event this evening. I&amp;rsquo;m just so curious as to what kind of exciting tech people/companies are here in Chicago!

John Barleycorn Wrigleyville
3524 N Clark St
Upstairs
Chicago, IL 60657 Thursday, May 29, 2008 from 06:30 PM - 08:00 PM (CT)
http://tech-cocktail-chicago-8.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>