<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chicago on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/chicago/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chicago on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/chicago/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Celebration</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/04/star-wars-celebration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/04/star-wars-celebration/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to Star Wars Celebration in Chicago. This was my first Celebration event I attended so I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure what to expect. Overall, I&amp;rsquo;d say it was fun and very doable event for its size. What I mean by this is that larger cons like San Diego Comic Con is super fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also super large where it&amp;rsquo;s not possible to do all the things you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2019</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended C2E2 at Chicago&amp;rsquo;s McCormick Place once again. It&amp;rsquo;a convention I recommend to all my Chicago friends to attend as it&amp;rsquo;s very convenient to attend and is quite affordable since they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to travel far.
If you weren&amp;rsquo;t able to attend, check out SyFy Wire&amp;rsquo;s youTube channel. They have videos of most if not all the panels that happened at C2E2 as well as many other conventions across the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</guid>
      <description>This year&amp;rsquo;s C2E2 was by far the largest and busiest I&amp;rsquo;ve been to. There seemed to be a bigger space rented out for the event over at McCormick Place. I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to apply for a press pass this year and just went ahead and bought a 3-day pass. I&amp;rsquo;ve been denied 2 years in a row now and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like applying&amp;ndash; perhaps next year.
Like many other comic conventions, C2E2 offers mailing of purchased badges if they are bought before a deadline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Central 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/anime-central-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/anime-central-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was at Anime Central (ACen) which was hosted at the Donald E. Stephens Convention Center. This was my second time attending, and I was also given a press pass again.
I stuck around the main entrance hall/lobby for most of the convention hoping to catch cosplayers on their way in or out of the exhibit hall. It seemed this year a lot of cosplayers were more casual and spent more time in the exhibit hall than the entrance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to C2E2 over at McCormick Place. Once again I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to obtain a press pass, so I went as a civilian photographer&amp;ndash; I bought my 3-day pass. Every year I&amp;rsquo;m going to try, and every year I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to get denied!
C2E2 isn&amp;rsquo;t too big that it&amp;rsquo;s uncomfortable to go as an individual or even as a family. McCormick Place is huge and there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room to expand in case the crowd size does ever get bigger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Central 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/anime-central-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/anime-central-2016/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended Anime Central, also known as ACen. I was given a press pass and attended all three days, May 20-22nd. My main goal was to take photos of cosplayers in and out of the Donald E. Stephens Convention Center. ACen is the Midwest&amp;rsquo;s largest anime, manga, and Japanese pop culture convention. It&amp;rsquo;s the third largest anime convention, but in recent news I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it&amp;rsquo;s the second now, behind Anime Expo (AX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to check out C2E2. It was the second year that I&amp;rsquo;ve attended the show. This year, I went all three days, unlike last year. The cosplay this year was amazing&amp;ndash; every year cosplayers keep upping their game.
Friday The main purpose of Day 1 was to pick up my lanyard, get a lay of the land, walk the exhibit hall, and determine whether I would be permitted to take photos from different positions in the main stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Willis Tower and John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago my niece visited Chicago for the first time and I took her around to see and eat some of the best my city has to offer. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve visited John Hancock Observatory before, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been up to Willis Tower (specifically the Skydeck) since it was called the Sears Tower.
The challenge with taking photos at these locations was that we went up right after it rained and there were a lot of cloud/fog surrounding Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Open House Chicago 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Sunday I went to checkout Open House Chicago and did a little photowalk of my own. I actually had no plan to go until my sister gave me her priority pass the morning of. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did as it was not only had some good photops, but was a nice steps in too since I use FitBit.
The places I visited:
 The Oriental Theatre Joffrey Ballet Aon Center Continental Illinois Bank Building The Rookery  My favorite spot was the Aon Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adams/Wabash CTA Station</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was in Chicago with hopes of getting some nice photos of Chicago henge&amp;ndash; basically the fall equinox where the sunset lines up straight with the East-West street grid. But there were some clouds in the sky which prevented any starburst from happening. However, I went early enough to do some exploring around downtown for other fun shots.
In particular I hopped on the CTA and looked for some train shots on the &amp;lsquo;L&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago River from Lake Shore Drive</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</guid>
      <description>I had some spare time before dinner near Navy Pier to take some pictures of the Chicago River off Lake Shore Drive. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to take photos at this location, but never was in the area during the right time. I had about a forty minutes during sunset to grab some shots and then run off to dinner.
This was my favorite shot I took.
There were some challenges to getting this photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went to Trey Ratcliff&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Photowalk. I had fun walking from the Adler Planetarium toward the Bean. As usual on my many photowalks, I tend to stray from the large groups and do my own thing. I just find it difficult to get shots I want around dozens or in this case hundreds of other photographers.
This event was actually my second time that I met Trey. The first time was a few years ago at a Santa Monica Photowalk along with MySpace Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Theatre</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</guid>
      <description>A couple nights ago I was in downtown Chicago for a meetup at Chicago Ruby. Since I found cheap parking via Parking Panda, I figured afterwards I would spend a little time taking some photos of the famous Chicago Theatre.
The challenge of taking the photo at this location at night was that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people and cars moving or idling on both sides of the street. On top of that, to my left was a camera crew filming what I assume to be something for either a TV show or commercial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</guid>
      <description>This past Sunday I went to check out Chicago&amp;rsquo;s very own C2E2 at McCormick Place. I only went for one day unfortunately, but I had a good time walking the floor and taking pictures here and there. I really do find this con to be better than Wizard World Chicago. Not only is it bigger, with room to expand at McCormick, but the fans and cosplayers were in abundance. In short, it was way more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott McCloud at Chicago Humanities Festival</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/02/scott-mccloud-at-chicago-humanities-festival/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/02/scott-mccloud-at-chicago-humanities-festival/</guid>
      <description>This past Friday the Chicago Humanities Festival had Scott McCloud at the Art Institute. Not many of my friends and family know that Mr. McCloud was a big influence during my teenage and high school years.
Back in the nineties, I was a big comic book reader. Besides being a reader, I also loved doodling and drawing. But after a while, I wanted to know more about the history, art, and motivations of the comic book creators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Photos of 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2014 was a good year for my photography. I did quite a bit of traveling and pushed myself to try some new things. Now that it&amp;rsquo;s 2015, I hope to take more photographs and try some new things out too!
Some goals:  I recently upgraded my SLR Lounge Presets to V6 and look forward to using their system in upcoming projects. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago, I hope to do some more street photos of the great city!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Adler Planetarium</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</guid>
      <description>This is my last of three posts covering the three landmarks I visited in Chicago during this past winter. My first was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s John Hancock Observatory and the other was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Bean.
The last landmark I visited was of a sunset from Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Adler Planetarium. I visited the Adler before and took pictures there&amp;ndash; but this was all when I first started to get into some HDR and photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was in Chicago for nearly three weeks during the holidays. I only planned to be there with my parents/family for about two weeks, but the snow, friends, and family all kept me from leaving&amp;ndash; so I ended up rebooking my flight TWICE.
During my extensive stay in Chicago, I visited a few landmarks to take some pictures.
I wrote a blog post covering my photos from John Hancock Observatory already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to visit the John Hancock Observatory with my sister. The last time I was there was in 2006 I think, somewhat a long time ago. I recall the views from JH being far superior to those from the Sears tower&amp;ndash; now called Willis tower. Plus I&amp;rsquo;ve seen some pictures on 500px taken from JH and wanted to try my hand at those views.
Signature Room or Observatory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Summer Conventions</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 20:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</guid>
      <description>There are some conferences and conventions coming up soon that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about. So far I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to Anime Expo and Comic-Con, as I purchased tickets for those already. Recently announced is the G+ Photographers Conference, which includes a Photowalk on Monday, May 21st. I will most likely make my way up there for that&amp;ndash; about eighty-percent sure I&amp;rsquo;ll go.
I plan to take my photography gear to take plenty of pictures too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Chicago HDR Photography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 15:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I was in Chicago. I woke up early the morning following St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day to take some photos near the Adler Planetarium and Millennium Park. I got there with my sister just before sunrise around 6:30am.
The tools I used: Canon 60D&amp;nbsp;camera body with Canon 16-35mm L wide lens&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Canon 24-105mm L lens&amp;nbsp;along with my tripod. For post processing: Apple&amp;rsquo;s Aperture and Photomatix Pro.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Objective-C and iOS for .NET Developers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/09/pictures-from-objective-c-and-ios-for-.net-developers/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my favorite local user group, Chicago Alt.net (@ChicagoAltNet).
Eduardo Scoz presented on Objective-C and iOS. Great talk and a very big turnout. I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen this many developers show up for an Alt.net meetup here since Uncle Bob Martin did a presentation.
Here are some of the photos I took. If you are looking for a full set of photos I took from various meetups I attend, including this one, I dump them all in this Picasa album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wizard World Chicago Comic Con 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/wizard-world-chicago-comic-con-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2011 09:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/wizard-world-chicago-comic-con-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m suffering from San Diego Comic Con 2010 withdrawal still. This year I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to go as a good friend was getting married and I was his best man&amp;ndash; which turned out to be the best wedding I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been to. But anyway, you can see my post and pictures from that here.
So this year I made a last minute decision to go to Wizard World&amp;rsquo;s Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Comic Con.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Alt.net: Coffeescript</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2011 21:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/pictures-from-chicago-alt.net-coffeescript/</guid>
      <description>Here are the pictures I took from tonight&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Alt.net August 2011 meetup on Coffeescript, presented by Fawad Halim.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from July&#39;s Refresh and Ignite Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/pictures-from-julys-refresh-and-ignite-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I didn&amp;rsquo;t go to too many meetups this month, only three. Sorry, the weather&amp;rsquo;s been either really hot or super rainy. Interestingly when I condensed the meetup names in this blog title, they both hint at refreshing and igniting Chicago.
I already posted on Barcamp Chicago in a previous blog post.
The second meetup, Corey Haines presented on It&amp;rsquo;s All About the Business Value on Wednesday, July 27, 2011.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barcamp Chicago at Pumping Station One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2011 03:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/07/barcamp-chicago-at-pumping-station-one/</guid>
      <description>I went to check out Barcamp Chicago earlier this month, on July 9, 2011. It was held at Pumping Station One, a hackerspace here in Chicago. I didn&amp;rsquo;t stay too long, as it was a really nice day out.
Here are most of the pictures I took:
This is the entrance 
After the hallway entrance, this what you first see</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Tech Meetups in May and June</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/pictures-from-tech-meetups-in-may-and-june/</guid>
      <description>In May I came across a new group: Refresh Chicago (@refreshchi). So far, their meetups have been pretty good. From their twitter, the group is described as: Monthly meetup for the advancement of Chicago’s designers and developers. Pretty cool.
So here are some pictures I took in May and June, 2011&amp;ndash; post Chicago Code Camp and Rails Conf.
David Kadavy presenting at Refresh Chicago (May 25, 2011)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 08:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Code Camp 2011 (CCC3) has wrapped up! I had a great time going to various sessions, learning new things, and meeting/talking with great people. I wish more of these events would take place in the Chicagoland area. I think about 300 people attended, which I think is pretty good considering the event wasn&amp;rsquo;t even in Chicago! This year, CCC3 took place at College of Lake County, in Grayslake, which is located about 50 miles from Chicago (approximately 1 hour drive).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>The schedule for Chicago Code Camp is now up! You can register for the free event here. You can follow them on twitter at: @chicagocodecamp. The twitter hash tag to follow at the event is: #ccc3
The link to actual schedule: Chicago Code Camp 2011 Schedule (this link may not work in the future&amp;ndash; beyond 2011).
This is the list of sessions I&amp;rsquo;m interested in. I may jump in/out between some sessions that are running in parallel, or pick one when the event gets closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Meetups for Spring and Summer 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2011 04:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/upcoming-meetups-for-spring-and-summer-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago for now! Just got off the plane a few days ago. Anyway, I&amp;rsquo;m almost ready to get back into going to some tech meetups in the US now. A lot of great events coming up!
Chicago Ruby: Downtown - Marking Up the Web with Graffiti
Tuesday, May 3, 2011 at 6pm
To be held at ThoughtWorks.
Chicago Silverlight Users Group
Wednesday, May 4, 2011
To be held at the ITA building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Transformers 3 Set in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2011 04:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/02/pictures-of-transformers-3-set-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I just realized I never formally made a blog post on all the pictures I took of the Transformers 3 set in Chicago of Summer of 2010. Many of the photos I took weren&amp;rsquo;t that far from the office I was working at.
Here you go, enjoy the albums:  2010 Transformers 3 Set 2010 July 17 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 1 Transformers 3 Set 2010 August 19 Transformers Set</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from October Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2010 21:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-october-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Alt.net on October 13, 2010 Event: SpecFlow: One Step closer to Executable Specifications
Speaker: Sergio Pereira
http://sergiopereira.com/blog
Chicago Alt.net website





Full album here.
Chicago ACM on October 18, 2010 Event: From Spider-Man to Avatar: Achieving Photoreal Digital Actors
Speaker: Paul Debevec from USC Institute for Creative Technologies www.debevec.org
Chicago ACM website



Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from September Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 18:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/10/pictures-from-september-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>There were only two events I attended last month:  Nerd Diner:NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!! Chicago Alt.net: Selenium 101.3: Practical Functional Testing Techniques 
The Nerd Dinner was at Rock Bottom and was arranged by Shankar Ramachandran. Very chill meetup, great talks with awesome .Net developers. I hope there can be more of these.










Full album for Nerd Dinnerhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from the August 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/09/pictures-from-the-august-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I was on a bit of a vacation in July so I forgot to post August events before the month started.
Chicago Ruby Meetup on August 3, 2010 Presentations on: Agile with Pivotal Tracker and jQuery and Rails 3.0





Full album here.
Chicago Alt.net on August 11, 2010 Fawad Halim gave a presentation on Python for .Net Developers.




Full album here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>September 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/september-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>NerdDinner Chicago - .NET Enthusiasts Unite !!!!
Wednesday, September 1, 2010 at 6:15 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby
Tuesday, September 7, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
There will be a meetup on Mongoid &amp;amp; Rails 3.
Chicago Alt.net
Wednesday, September 8, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM (CT)
Should be a talk about Selenium by @bwilken.
Chicago Ruby Hack Night
Thursday, September 9, 2010 from 5:30 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Chicago and the Millennium Park Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was at an event last week at the rooftop of 63 E. Lake Street and I was able to take some photos of the Millennium Park Bean and parts of Chicago.



These photos were taken with my Canon Digital Rebel XT with a Canon EF-S 55-250mm f/4.0-5.6 IS Telephoto Zoom Lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from the July 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/pictures-from-the-july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 14:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/pictures-from-the-july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I made sure to take a lot of photos this month.
Tuesday July 6, 2010 Chicago Ruby had a meeting over at ThoughtWorks. Snapped a few photos there. Very cool talks. And of course, pizza. You can sign up for these meetings at: Chicago Ruby Meetup. There was a Hack Night on Thursday of the week, but I did not take any photos.
Presentations by @chrisjpowers and @blakesmith.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>July 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 09:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/07/july-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Plenty of events to attend for the month of July! This will be the first time I&amp;rsquo;m attending a Ruby event, so I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited. Sadly, things may be a bit over my head since I just started doing Ruby.
Tuesday July 6, 2010 at 6:00 PM (CT)
ChicagoRuby: Downtown- Two Talks: HTML5 WebSockets &amp;amp; Contributing to Open Source
Thursday July 8, 2010 at 5:30 PM (CT)
Chicago Ruby Hack Night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2 Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 22:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to start posting pictures I take from various Tech Events I attend. One, I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I want to share visually, what the Tech community looks like. And two, because I&amp;rsquo;m picking up photography as a hobby now.
The pictures below are from Chicago Code Camp, which took place May 1st, 2010 at the Stuart Building at IIT. They were taken by me with my Google Nexus One.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>June 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 13:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/june-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>A decent amount of Tech events for the month of June here in Chicago:
Wednesday, June 02, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:00 PM (CT)
MVVM with Damon Payne
The Chicago Silverlight User Group (Eventbrite link)
Tuesday, June 8, 2010 from 5:30PM - 7:30PM (CT)
Chicago Agile Project Management Meetup Group
Wednesday, June 09, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Well Behaved JavaScript With Screw.Unit
Chicago Alt.net (Eventbrite link)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>May 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 08:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/may-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>The month of May looks to be an exciting month in Chicago for Tech Events!
Saturday, May 1st 2010 from 8:00 AM - 6:00 PM (CT) Chicago Code Camp 2 will actually be held in Chicago&amp;rsquo;s IIT campus this year! Speakers, presentations, and the agenda have all been posted now.
Here is my tentative schedule that I plan to attend:
9:00 AM - 10:00 AM - Use Git Like a Boss by Kevin Gisi (Ruby)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>April 2010 Tech Events in Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/april-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2010 00:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/april-2010-tech-events-in-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of April 2010 Tech events in Chicago that I&amp;rsquo;m aware of. Most of them, I shall be attending.
Thursday, April 01, 2010 from 6:00 PM - 9:00 PM (CT) Mobile Visionary Mixer - Effective Networking at Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Hottest Brazilian Steakhouse! (Eventbrite link) I attended this event already and really enjoyed it. Meet and spoke to a lot of great people and hope to attend future events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Tech User Groups and Events for March 2010</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/chicago-tech-user-groups-and-events-for-march-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 19:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/chicago-tech-user-groups-and-events-for-march-2010/</guid>
      <description>The first two weeks this month I attended several Chicago user group meetings and events. I wanted to recap my experience with many of them since it was my first time attending several of the events.
Tuesday March 2, 2010 Chicago Agile Project Management Meetup Group I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of this meetup group for a while now. I really made an effort to attend this one since the topic was on estimating projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Vending Machine at Work</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2009 22:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/the-vending-machine-at-work/</guid>
      <description>This is my vending machine at work. I happen to like Reeses Peanut Butter Cups. I don&amp;rsquo;t have a sweet tooth, but it&amp;rsquo;s the only snack in the entire machine I would buy.
Can you see what&amp;rsquo;s wrong?

It&amp;rsquo;s behind a 100 Grand, one of the worst pieces of candy in the entire machine. I haven&amp;rsquo;t enjoyed a 100 Grand since I was a kid, which is probably the age of the candy since everybody knows it&amp;rsquo;s stale and gross.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Tech Events in Chicago for February</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2009 23:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/02/upcoming-tech-events-in-chicago-for-february/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Twestival! Date: Thursday, February 12, 2009
Time: 6:30 PM - 8:30 PM (CT)
Place: Catalyst Ranch - 656 W Randolph Dr Chicago IL
Cost: $10 donation
RSVP: http://www.chicagotwestival.eventbrite.com
Event: TECH cocktail Chicago 10 Date: Thursday, February 19, 2009
Time: 6:30pm - 9pm
Place: John Barleycorn’s - 3524 N Clark (where it always is)
Cost: $0 (per usual)
RSVP: http://techcocktail-chicago-10.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Signed up for the 2009 Shamrock Shuffle 8k run</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2009 22:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/01/signed-up-for-the-2009-shamrock-shuffle-8k-run/</guid>
      <description>After hearing that several friends will be doing the Shamrock Shuffle this year, I decided I wanted to challenge myself to it again. I did it two years ago, in 2007. I did little to no training for that, and ran at about a 13min/mile pace. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to bring that down to a 10min/mile pace with some proper training.
I look at this as a way to start out 2009 and hopefully, the rest of my life: As a fresh start to making a better me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Went to the Obama Rally in Grant Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2008 01:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/went-to-the-obama-rally-in-grant-park/</guid>
      <description>I witnessed history in the making last night by attending Barack Obama&amp;rsquo;s Election Night in Grant Park.
How I got the ticket: Sheer Luck
It all started after I got my lunch and was heading back to the office. A lady one floor beneath mine hopped on the elevator early (she wanted to go down, I was going up, but a co-worker of hers just got off), and she mentioned to her co-worker that if got his ticket yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 9</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</guid>
      <description>Another digerati networking event coming up in November! Last time I went I had a pretty good time talking with various people in the Chicago tech community. Only wish my company would sport me with actual up-to-date business cards!

When: Thursday, November 6, 2008 - 6:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST Where: John Barleycorn Wrigleyville Tech Cocktail Chicago 9
I also recently joined the community: iam.techcocktail.com
You can see my personal blog&amp;rsquo;s previous posting on Tech Cocktail 8 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Digg Meetup Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/thoughts-on-digg-meetup-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2008 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/thoughts-on-digg-meetup-chicago/</guid>
      <description>First off, let me say that I enjoy reading some of the articles posted on Digg&amp;hellip; well, I want to emphasize some. It&amp;rsquo;s a voting system, so there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of crap stories, and just a few winners here and there. But sometimes those stories are worth it. Sometimes&amp;hellip;
Anyway, I went to the Digg Meetup event yesterday with a co-worker and I thought it was just ok. Kevin Rose spoke a little, threw out some free schwag, interacted with the crowd, typical stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Digg Meet-Up Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2008 01:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-digg-meet-up-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I published this on my other blog, but wanted to post here too. Looks like Digg is coming to Chicago!

Wednesday, July 23, 2008 6-10 pm
SmartBar
3730 N. Clark Street
Chicago, Illinois 60613</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Event: Social Dev Camp Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 17:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/event-social-dev-camp-chicago/</guid>
      <description>I hope I can make this! From the facebook event link, I found: Chicago Interactive Design/Development Meetup Group. So interesting!
SocialDevCampChicago Saturday, August 9th 2008
8:30am-6:00pm
at Illinois Institute of Technology McCormick Tribune Center (http://www.iit.edu/mtcc/)
Facebook event: http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=20586291919
If you are developer in the midwest you might be interested in checking out the upcoming SocialDevCampChicago. SocialDevCampChicago is an unconference for people passionate about social networks, web applications, platform development, new media, and any of the exciting (but messy) topics in-between.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 8</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2008 08:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/05/tech-cocktail-chicago-8/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about going to the Tech Cocktail Chicago 8 event this evening. I&amp;rsquo;m just so curious as to what kind of exciting tech people/companies are here in Chicago!

John Barleycorn Wrigleyville
3524 N Clark St
Upstairs
Chicago, IL 60657 Thursday, May 29, 2008 from 06:30 PM - 08:00 PM (CT)
http://tech-cocktail-chicago-8.eventbrite.com</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>