<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>C2E2 on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/c2e2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in C2E2 on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/c2e2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2019</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2019 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2019/03/c2e2-2019/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended C2E2 at Chicago&amp;rsquo;s McCormick Place once again. It&amp;rsquo;a convention I recommend to all my Chicago friends to attend as it&amp;rsquo;s very convenient to attend and is quite affordable since they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to travel far.
If you weren&amp;rsquo;t able to attend, check out SyFy Wire&amp;rsquo;s youTube channel. They have videos of most if not all the panels that happened at C2E2 as well as many other conventions across the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/c2e2-2018/</guid>
      <description>This year&amp;rsquo;s C2E2 was by far the largest and busiest I&amp;rsquo;ve been to. There seemed to be a bigger space rented out for the event over at McCormick Place. I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to apply for a press pass this year and just went ahead and bought a 3-day pass. I&amp;rsquo;ve been denied 2 years in a row now and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like applying&amp;ndash; perhaps next year.
Like many other comic conventions, C2E2 offers mailing of purchased badges if they are bought before a deadline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/04/c2e2-2017/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to C2E2 over at McCormick Place. Once again I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to obtain a press pass, so I went as a civilian photographer&amp;ndash; I bought my 3-day pass. Every year I&amp;rsquo;m going to try, and every year I&amp;rsquo;m probably going to get denied!
C2E2 isn&amp;rsquo;t too big that it&amp;rsquo;s uncomfortable to go as an individual or even as a family. McCormick Place is huge and there&amp;rsquo;s plenty of room to expand in case the crowd size does ever get bigger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2016 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/c2e2-2016/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I went to check out C2E2. It was the second year that I&amp;rsquo;ve attended the show. This year, I went all three days, unlike last year. The cosplay this year was amazing&amp;ndash; every year cosplayers keep upping their game.
Friday The main purpose of Day 1 was to pick up my lanyard, get a lay of the land, walk the exhibit hall, and determine whether I would be permitted to take photos from different positions in the main stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C2E2 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/04/c2e2-2015/</guid>
      <description>This past Sunday I went to check out Chicago&amp;rsquo;s very own C2E2 at McCormick Place. I only went for one day unfortunately, but I had a good time walking the floor and taking pictures here and there. I really do find this con to be better than Wizard World Chicago. Not only is it bigger, with room to expand at McCormick, but the fans and cosplayers were in abundance. In short, it was way more fun.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>