<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Camp on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/code-camp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code Camp on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/code-camp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Camp LA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/mobile-camp-la/</guid>
      <description>I picked up a free ticket to Mobile Camp LA earlier this week and decided to attend. Overall I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too impressed with the event. It may have very well been the first of it&amp;rsquo;s kind aimed at developers, designers, and business folk. Anyway, I thought the venue was a bit of a mess as many things went wrong.  Earthquake drill at 10:15am (slightly distracting, but out of their control&amp;ndash; I understand) A lot of sessions held in a one big open space separated by cloth dividers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Code Camp at USC</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/10/socal-code-camp-at-usc/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I attended SoCal Code Camp held at University of Southern California (USC). Had a good time learning about new stuff as usual. The prizes here are pretty spectacular, but once again I won absolutely nothing. Nothing!
Like the one I went to earlier this year, this one was also a bit heavy on the .Net side of technology with little representation from Android and iOS, and nothing from Ruby/Rails/Java/etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Summer Conventions</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 20:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</guid>
      <description>There are some conferences and conventions coming up soon that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about. So far I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to Anime Expo and Comic-Con, as I purchased tickets for those already. Recently announced is the G+ Photographers Conference, which includes a Photowalk on Monday, May 21st. I will most likely make my way up there for that&amp;ndash; about eighty-percent sure I&amp;rsquo;ll go.
I plan to take my photography gear to take plenty of pictures too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from SoCal Code Camp</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 10:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/pictures-from-socal-code-camp/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I attended and volunteered at SoCal Code Camp at California State University Fullerton. I had an awesome time, attended quite a few sessions, learned a lot, and met quite a few good people.
Below are some of the pictures. Full set of pictures can be found here.
Pictures 

Mario Harnandez presenting CSS3 for Web Designers- Let&amp;rsquo;s Design a Visually Appealing Website and Grid Systems - Picking the Right CSS Framework for Your Website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SoCal Code Camp is tomorrow</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/socal-code-camp-is-tomorrow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2012 19:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/socal-code-camp-is-tomorrow/</guid>
      <description>SoCal Code Camp is tomorrow. Sessions have been posted, as well as the schedule. It&amp;rsquo;s a two day event, January 28 and 29 (Saturday and Sunday), full of sessions on a variety of software development topics.
Did I mention that it&amp;rsquo;s FREE?!
It will be hosted at California State University Fullerton. Here is a campus map to help you.
I will be there bright and early volunteering and probably taking photos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 May 2011 08:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/pictures-from-chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>Chicago Code Camp 2011 (CCC3) has wrapped up! I had a great time going to various sessions, learning new things, and meeting/talking with great people. I wish more of these events would take place in the Chicagoland area. I think about 300 people attended, which I think is pretty good considering the event wasn&amp;rsquo;t even in Chicago! This year, CCC3 took place at College of Lake County, in Grayslake, which is located about 50 miles from Chicago (approximately 1 hour drive).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2011</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2011 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/05/chicago-code-camp-2011/</guid>
      <description>The schedule for Chicago Code Camp is now up! You can register for the free event here. You can follow them on twitter at: @chicagocodecamp. The twitter hash tag to follow at the event is: #ccc3
The link to actual schedule: Chicago Code Camp 2011 Schedule (this link may not work in the future&amp;ndash; beyond 2011).
This is the list of sessions I&amp;rsquo;m interested in. I may jump in/out between some sessions that are running in parallel, or pick one when the event gets closer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Code Camp 2 Pictures</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2010 22:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/06/chicago-code-camp-2-pictures/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m going to start posting pictures I take from various Tech Events I attend. One, I&amp;rsquo;m doing it because I want to share visually, what the Tech community looks like. And two, because I&amp;rsquo;m picking up photography as a hobby now.
The pictures below are from Chicago Code Camp, which took place May 1st, 2010 at the Stuart Building at IIT. They were taken by me with my Google Nexus One.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>