<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Photography on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/photography/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Photography on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/photography/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Willis Tower and John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/12/photos-from-willis-tower-and-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago my niece visited Chicago for the first time and I took her around to see and eat some of the best my city has to offer. Although I&amp;rsquo;ve visited John Hancock Observatory before, I haven&amp;rsquo;t been up to Willis Tower (specifically the Skydeck) since it was called the Sears Tower.
The challenge with taking photos at these locations was that we went up right after it rained and there were a lot of cloud/fog surrounding Chicago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures from Open House Chicago 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/10/pictures-from-open-house-chicago-2015/</guid>
      <description>On Sunday I went to checkout Open House Chicago and did a little photowalk of my own. I actually had no plan to go until my sister gave me her priority pass the morning of. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I did as it was not only had some good photops, but was a nice steps in too since I use FitBit.
The places I visited:
 The Oriental Theatre Joffrey Ballet Aon Center Continental Illinois Bank Building The Rookery  My favorite spot was the Aon Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adams/Wabash CTA Station</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/adams/wabash-cta-station/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I was in Chicago with hopes of getting some nice photos of Chicago henge&amp;ndash; basically the fall equinox where the sunset lines up straight with the East-West street grid. But there were some clouds in the sky which prevented any starburst from happening. However, I went early enough to do some exploring around downtown for other fun shots.
In particular I hopped on the CTA and looked for some train shots on the &amp;lsquo;L&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Photos in Cosplay Culture Magazine</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/09/my-photos-in-cosplay-culture-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Last week, the Halloween edition of Cosplay Culture magazine came out on newsstands. There is an article on San Diego Comic Con that features my photos in it. The article is a ten whopping page spread! This all started from a simple comment on an instagram photo.
You can find this magazine at Barnes and Noble, Target, Walmart, Ralph&amp;rsquo;s, Walgreens, CVS, and other major newsstands and comic shops. I found my copies at B&amp;amp;N.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago River from Lake Shore Drive</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-river-from-lake-shore-drive/</guid>
      <description>I had some spare time before dinner near Navy Pier to take some pictures of the Chicago River off Lake Shore Drive. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to take photos at this location, but never was in the area during the right time. I had about a forty minutes during sunset to grab some shots and then run off to dinner.
This was my favorite shot I took.
There were some challenges to getting this photo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicago Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/chicago-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I went to Trey Ratcliff&amp;rsquo;s Chicago Photowalk. I had fun walking from the Adler Planetarium toward the Bean. As usual on my many photowalks, I tend to stray from the large groups and do my own thing. I just find it difficult to get shots I want around dozens or in this case hundreds of other photographers.
This event was actually my second time that I met Trey. The first time was a few years ago at a Santa Monica Photowalk along with MySpace Tom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Chicago Theatre</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-chicago-theatre/</guid>
      <description>A couple nights ago I was in downtown Chicago for a meetup at Chicago Ruby. Since I found cheap parking via Parking Panda, I figured afterwards I would spend a little time taking some photos of the famous Chicago Theatre.
The challenge of taking the photo at this location at night was that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people and cars moving or idling on both sides of the street. On top of that, to my left was a camera crew filming what I assume to be something for either a TV show or commercial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Recommend Adobe Photoshop Lightroom</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/why-i-recommend-adobe-photoshop-lightroom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2015 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/why-i-recommend-adobe-photoshop-lightroom/</guid>
      <description>Over the past few years, friends have been asked me photography questions in terms of camera gear and software. Perhaps I&amp;rsquo;ll write a post in the future on physical camera gear, but for this post I wanted to cover why I love using Adobe Photoshop Lightroom and why you should consider it for your photo needs.
Adobe Lightroom is essentially a trimmed down version of Photoshop (PS) with features built in for a Photography workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Favorite Photos of 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2015 14:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/01/my-favorite-photos-of-2014/</guid>
      <description>Last year, in 2014 was a good year for my photography. I did quite a bit of traveling and pushed myself to try some new things. Now that it&amp;rsquo;s 2015, I hope to take more photographs and try some new things out too!
Some goals:  I recently upgraded my SLR Lounge Presets to V6 and look forward to using their system in upcoming projects. Now that I&amp;rsquo;m back in Chicago, I hope to do some more street photos of the great city!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Road Trip From LA to Chicago</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/my-road-trip-from-la-to-chicago/</guid>
      <description>Last week I drove from Los Angeles back to my hometown of Chicago. I&amp;rsquo;ve moved back home for personal reasons. It took my sister and I nine days to get across the US&amp;ndash; mostly just eating, driving, sleeping, and taking pictures.
The states I drove through were (in order):
 California Arizona Utah Colorado Kansas Missouri Illinois  
The first half of the trip from California to Colorado was rather scenic and interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oakland Museum of California&#39;s SDCC Exhibit</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/oakland-museum-of-californias-sdcc-exhibit/</guid>
      <description>The Oakland Museum of California has one of my photos from San Diego Comic Con on display in their exhibit: Sunshine and Superheroes: San Diego Comic-Con. A few days ago I had the opportunity to visit and took some photos.
The exhibit runs from May 23, 2014 to May 31, 2015.
Below is the photo I took at SDCC in 2013 that they used. It&amp;rsquo;s taken on the escalators leading up to the ticket booths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building my own Photography Site</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/building-my-own-photography-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 18:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/09/building-my-own-photography-site/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago my SmugMug account expired and I didn&amp;rsquo;t bother to renew it. This is where my photography website, Sunpech Photography, used to be hosted. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t fully utilizing it to make sales nor was I pushing it very much to friends, family, and even clients. So I couldn&amp;rsquo;t justify spending any money on it when I&amp;rsquo;d rather make sales on 500px and 500px Art.
Surprisingly my account was discontinued almost immediately and I whipped up a decent site in less than 24 hours along with appropriate DNS changes just so I didn&amp;rsquo;t have an ugly 404 page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Skyline</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/san-diego-skyline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/san-diego-skyline/</guid>
      <description>I really like the city of San Diego. It&amp;rsquo;s a very clean city with little to no smog in the air, unlike Los Angeles.
I was there for Comic Con a few days early last week. So I put aside some time to go take pictures of the skyline from Coronado Island. I did a little research on 500px and picked a spot that had a clear shot of the skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos of Naver Line Friends</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/photos-of-naver-line-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/photos-of-naver-line-friends/</guid>
      <description>I was in Chiang Mai, Thailand recently and found some Naver Line toys at the mall. I bought them with the intention of giving them to my sisters since we all use the Line chat app. But on the way back to the US, I had an eight hour layover at the Incheon International airport in South Korea. I happened to pack the toys in my carry-on so I took them out to have a little photo shoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brief Appearance on Heroes of Cosplay</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</guid>
      <description>In a last week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Heroes of Cosplay, I had a brief appearance in Season 1 - Episode 7!
The episode covered part of the cosplay competition at Stan Lee&amp;rsquo;s Comikaze Expo. I was there in attendance checking out the event and taking photos of many cosplayers and panels.
I appear at about the 2:34 mark as the opening credits are still rolling.
That&amp;rsquo;s me in the Valiant t-shirt behind the DSLR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>500px Art Prints</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/500px-art-prints/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2014 12:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/500px-art-prints/</guid>
      <description>I was recently featured in a 500px blog post, Celebrating 3 Months of 500px Art! The new site launched back in December and I&amp;rsquo;ve actually bought several of my prints just to see what the quality was like.
Below are some photos from two separate orders I made. The packaging is really well done, and they consolidated two prints into one big box.
Overall they&amp;rsquo;re pretty good. 500px offers canvas, paper, aluminum, acrylic, and birchwood as print material.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from 6th St Bridge</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 11:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-6th-st-bridge/</guid>
      <description>The 6th St. bridge has a magnificent view of the Los Angeles skyline. There&amp;rsquo;s only a two problems about getting the photo at this location.
First, the area in the Arts district isn&amp;rsquo;t so good. There&amp;rsquo;s little foot traffic and I don&amp;rsquo;t feel comfortable bringing expensive equipment to set up there. Second, there are telephone wires running across in the view. I had to use Photoshop to clean that all up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Project Hearts</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-project-hearts/</guid>
      <description>One evening I took my DSLR and a bokeh kit with a heart-shaped cut out and took a walk down Miracle Mile. I started at LACMA and just walked east on Wilshire and snapped away at all the lights and traffic. I didn&amp;rsquo;t care so much about ISO as I needed to take fast shots of varying lighting situations that came up on the street&amp;ndash; so I just stayed in auto-ISO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Griffith Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/02/photos-from-griffith-observatory/</guid>
      <description>I use 500px to do research on where I want to go take pictures and what kind of shots to do. One in particular compelled me to go to Griffith Park to get a shot of the Griffith Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline.
Griffith Observatory Before Sunrise Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59933986 Griffith Observatory (After Sunrise) Buy print: http://500pxart.com/photo/59957370 I went on a different day and night to get a night shot of the Observatory as well as LA&amp;rsquo;s skyline (see below).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Downtown Los Angeles</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-downtown-los-angeles/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m back in Los Angeles now from traveling to cities like Toronto, San Francisco, and Chicago the past few months. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using 500px to research nice locations for these photos and it&amp;rsquo;s really paid off&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m very happy.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t noticed, I&amp;rsquo;ve been pushing my 500px account for my photos. I&amp;rsquo;ll have a separate blog post on that soon too, once a print I ordered arrives so I can give it a more thorough review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Adler Planetarium</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-adler-planetarium/</guid>
      <description>This is my last of three posts covering the three landmarks I visited in Chicago during this past winter. My first was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s John Hancock Observatory and the other was of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Bean.
The last landmark I visited was of a sunset from Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Adler Planetarium. I visited the Adler before and took pictures there&amp;ndash; but this was all when I first started to get into some HDR and photography.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2014 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was in Chicago for nearly three weeks during the holidays. I only planned to be there with my parents/family for about two weeks, but the snow, friends, and family all kept me from leaving&amp;ndash; so I ended up rebooking my flight TWICE.
During my extensive stay in Chicago, I visited a few landmarks to take some pictures.
I wrote a blog post covering my photos from John Hancock Observatory already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from San Francisco</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-san-francisco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-san-francisco/</guid>
      <description>I was up in San Francisco in late November and early December last year. It was a very last minute trip, but one I wanted to do for such a long time. I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to get some shots of the iconic Golden Gate Bridge in SF&amp;ndash; without any fog. My prior visits have always been foggy and I could never see the full bridge.
Well, this trip was somewhat dedicated to visiting the bridge several times to get some shots&amp;ndash; to which I was finally able to get some shots without fog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Toronto</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-toronto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-toronto/</guid>
      <description>Last year I did some traveling in October and November. In late October, I went to Toronto for the first time. The city is beautiful there. I&amp;rsquo;ve probably been in Los Angeles too long, but I noticed how clear the skies were and was astonished to look at buildings with no haze in front. It really showcases how LA is such a polluted and dirty city.
While I was there I got a chance to see Ai Weiwei&amp;rsquo;s Forever Bicycle exhibit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos from Chicago&#39;s John Hancock Observatory</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 16:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/01/photos-from-chicagos-john-hancock-observatory/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to visit the John Hancock Observatory with my sister. The last time I was there was in 2006 I think, somewhat a long time ago. I recall the views from JH being far superior to those from the Sears tower&amp;ndash; now called Willis tower. Plus I&amp;rsquo;ve seen some pictures on 500px taken from JH and wanted to try my hand at those views.
Signature Room or Observatory?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drink and Click LA Downtown Artwalk</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2013 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/09/drink-and-click-la-downtown-artwalk/</guid>
      <description>Last night I went to my second Drink and Click LA meetup in downtown Artwalk. Specifically we checked out The Last Bookstore, which is an amazing place to walk around and take photos if you are into books and little trinkets. Generally they ask you to check your bag at what I think is their main entrance, but the other entrance they do not in case you want to bring your camera bag in, which is what we all did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Drink and Click LA Event</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2013 20:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/my-first-drink-and-click-la-event/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I attended my first Drink and Click LA event. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of the group for a while, but just never got around to attending one of their get-togethers. I really had fun talking shop with other photography enthusiasts from beginner to professionals levels. There was time to do some street photos, a little drinking, some eating, and lots of talking.
It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since I attended a photography meetup of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be Considerate of Other Photographers</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 14:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/be-considerate-of-other-photographers/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was in the Bahamas for a friend&amp;rsquo;s wedding. The people, the scenery, and weather was beautiful up and through the wedding. The day after&amp;hellip; not so much. We had a bit of a tropical storm, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t last too long. Thank goodness the wedding day had clear skies.
Naturally, I brought my camera with me on the trip. I do have a post on what&amp;rsquo;s in my camera bag, typically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s In My Camera Bag</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/whats-in-my-camera-bag/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2013 16:29:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/04/whats-in-my-camera-bag/</guid>
      <description>In Feedly, there&amp;rsquo;s a Flickr group that I subscribe to: What&amp;rsquo;s in your camera bag? I like to consider it photography gear porn.
So I thought I would share what I typically carry with me when I&amp;rsquo;m out and about. I consider this a light package. When I&amp;rsquo;m actually at an event I know I will take tons of pictures, there will be a bit more in my bag. But overall, this is good enough for most situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Diego Comic Con 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2012 16:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/san-diego-comic-con-2012/</guid>
      <description>Last week I went to the San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) and had a blast. The last time I went was back in 2010, which I blogged about here. I took quite a few photos, but only post-processed a fraction of them. I may choose to post-process more of them at a later date. You can view the full album here.
I attended SDCC with a 4-day pass along with preview night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus Photographer&#39;s Conference</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-conference/</guid>
      <description>Last week I attended the Google+ Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Conference in San Francisco, May 22-23, 2012 at the Yerba Buena Center for the Arts. The day before, I attended a photowalk at Golden Gate Park which I blogged about already.
Some things I observed and learned at the conference:
 Adobe Lightroom 4, Bridge, and Photoshop seem to be the digital tools of choice of many photographers. There are just as many Nikon users as there are Canon users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Plus Photographer&#39;s Photowalk at Golden Gate Park</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/google-plus-photographers-photowalk-at-golden-gate-park/</guid>
      <description>Last week I was up in San Francisco May 21-23 for the Google+ Photographer&amp;rsquo;s Conference. On Monday, there was an optional photowalk at about ten locations. I attended the one led by Scott Kelby at Golden Gate Park.
The photowalk was pretty fun. It&amp;rsquo;s the third photowalk I&amp;rsquo;ve been on so far, and in general I like to stray from the group, go at my own pace, and take shots of everything I find interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muir Woods Hike Photos</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/muir-woods-hike-photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/05/muir-woods-hike-photos/</guid>
      <description>A few weekends ago I was in San Francisco for the Coldplay concert in San Jose at the HP Pavillion. Part of the weekend trip was hiking near Muir Woods. I brought my camera, tripod, and backpack with me and took some photos during my hike.
I had with me my Canon 5D Mark 3 with Canon 16-35mm f/2.8 L II lens&amp;nbsp;and Canon 24-105 f/4 L lens. I brought my Dolica tripod,&amp;nbsp;Canon 480EX II Speedlite flash, jacket, and some other stuff&amp;ndash; and&amp;nbsp;packed it all in my Lowepro Photo Sport 200 AW Backpack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Summer Conventions</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 20:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/upcoming-summer-conventions/</guid>
      <description>There are some conferences and conventions coming up soon that I&amp;rsquo;m pretty excited about. So far I&amp;rsquo;m definitely going to Anime Expo and Comic-Con, as I purchased tickets for those already. Recently announced is the G+ Photographers Conference, which includes a Photowalk on Monday, May 21st. I will most likely make my way up there for that&amp;ndash; about eighty-percent sure I&amp;rsquo;ll go.
I plan to take my photography gear to take plenty of pictures too!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/the-original-renaissance-pleasure-faire/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I attended The Original Renaissance Pleasure Faire in Irwindale, California. It&amp;rsquo;s been over almost fifteen years since I attended a Renaissance Fair, the last being the Bristol Renaissance Fair in the Midwest. I was a teenager then and really loved the tasty mushrooms! I also got my older sister to buy me a broad sword!
A selection of photos I took are below. Full set can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new lense and camera body</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-new-lense-and-camera-body/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2012 14:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/my-new-lense-and-camera-body/</guid>
      <description>Recently I made some new camera gear purchases with the help of selling some of my older, unused equipment. Say hello to the Canon 70-200mm f/2.8 L IS II lense and Canon 5D Mark III! Yes, after a few weeks after the Canon 5DM3 announcement, I decided to go ahead and make the purchase. It cost an arm and a leg, but now I no longer have to watch videos of other people unboxing and reviewing these products, I get to use them myself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Songkran Festival in LA&#39;s Thaitown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/04/songkran-festival-in-las-thaitown/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend, on Sunday April 1, 2012, I went to LA&amp;rsquo;s Thaitown to check out the Songkran (Thai New Year) celebrations along Hollywood Blvd. They closed Hollywood off from Western all the way to Normandie to have a street festival/parade. I arrived around 11am and spent about 30 minutes just trying to find parking. I ran along Hollywood just in time to catch the beginning of the parade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Chicago HDR Photography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2012 15:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-chicago-hdr-photography/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I was in Chicago. I woke up early the morning following St. Patrick&amp;rsquo;s Day to take some photos near the Adler Planetarium and Millennium Park. I got there with my sister just before sunrise around 6:30am.
The tools I used: Canon 60D&amp;nbsp;camera body with Canon 16-35mm L wide lens&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;Canon 24-105mm L lens&amp;nbsp;along with my tripod. For post processing: Apple&amp;rsquo;s Aperture and Photomatix Pro.
Pictures</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Mar 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/light-chasers-artwalk-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Last night I attended the Light Chasers Artwalk Downtown meetup. I arrived early and walked to the Walt Disney Concert Hall to do some HDR shots. Upon arriving there, I immediately regretted not bringing my 16-35mm f/2.8 L lens. So made due with my recently purchased 24-105 f/4 L lens, which I really haven&amp;rsquo;t used that much yet.
I spent most of the evening on my own going at my own pace to take pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekend Photography at Baldwin Hills and LACMA</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2012 12:32:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/weekend-photography-at-baldwin-hills-and-lacma/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I took my camera out to take some photos here in LA.
Some HDR photos taken of the sunset near the Baldwin Hills Scenic Overlook:



 
Some photos taken at the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA):
Do you know what this is? Hint, it&amp;rsquo;s a dog&amp;rsquo;s butt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canon 5D Mark 3 Announced</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/canon-5d-mark-3-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 17:39:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/03/canon-5d-mark-3-announced/</guid>
      <description>The Canon 5D Mark 3 was announced yesterday.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking to get a full-frame DSLR for a while now. Last year I was thinking of getting the Canon 5D Mark 2 (M2), but settled for the Canon 60D because of price and I&amp;rsquo;d rather wait for the M3. Hopefully the M2 will drop in price slightly once the M3 officially comes out.
The price of the M3 is $3500. That&amp;rsquo;s body only, no kit lens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LA Photowalk with Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/la-photowalk-with-trey-ratcliff-and-tom-anderson/</guid>
      <description>Over this past weekend, on Sunday, the evening of the NBA All-Star game and Academy Awards, I went to check out a Google+ LA Photowalk in Santa Monica hosted by Trey Ratcliff and Tom Anderson (aka mySpace Tom).
I had a great time seeing and learning how other photography enthusiasts and professionals see things. I brought my Canon 60D, Canon 16-35mm L lens, and tripod. I regret not bringing another lens with me for some more flexibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</guid>
      <description>As a foodie and photography enthusiast, I found Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots to be a good read, mostly. Although, I did find myself skimming the later chapters as they deal with post-processing using Adobe Photoshop.
The first three chapters on fundamentals, equipment, and lighting I thought were the best for foodies interested in improving their skills as a photographer. The chapter on framing and composition is good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some Thoughts on Photography, Blogging, and Coding</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-photography-blogging-and-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2011 09:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/some-thoughts-on-photography-blogging-and-coding/</guid>
      <description>It was the summer of 2010 that I decided I wanted to dust off the DSLR I bought in 2006 and put it to good use more often. So throughout that summer, I made an effort to bring my camera with me everywhere I went. I brought it to work, to my various meetups I attended, and even when I walked around Chicago. I just kept taking photos of whatever I thought was interesting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Recent Camera Gear Purchases</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/recent-camera-gear-purchases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 15:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/recent-camera-gear-purchases/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve recently made some camera gear purchases.
I upgraded my Rebel XT to a Canon 60D a few weeks ago. I also got a Canon 60D battery grip with Canon EW78D Lens Hood. Overall, I&amp;rsquo;m very happy with these purchases. I love the 60D, it&amp;rsquo;s such a great step up from the Rebel XT, which I purchased 5 years ago. It feels good to use, and the pictures are also great, as expected from Canon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Android Photoshoot with my new Camera Lens</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/an-android-photoshoot-with-my-new-camera-lens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/an-android-photoshoot-with-my-new-camera-lens/</guid>
      <description>I got my new lens in the mail yesterday. It&amp;rsquo;s a Canon EF 50mm f/1.8 II Camera Lens.

I was studying at the time, but once I got my email notification that it arrived, I rushed to pick it up and did a little photoshoot of my Android toy at the table I was studying at. I played with the aperture for most of the shoot (in AV mode). Afterwards, I used Adobe Lightroom to polish it up a bit (created a set of Black &amp;amp; White photos too).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pictures of Chicago and the Millennium Park Bean</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/pictures-of-chicago-and-the-millennium-park-bean/</guid>
      <description>I was at an event last week at the rooftop of 63 E. Lake Street and I was able to take some photos of the Millennium Park Bean and parts of Chicago.



These photos were taken with my Canon Digital Rebel XT with a Canon EF-S 55-250mm f/4.0-5.6 IS Telephoto Zoom Lens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>