<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comikaze Expo on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/comikaze-expo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comikaze Expo on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/comikaze-expo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2014 12:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/11/comikaze-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>I attended my third Comikaze Expo (CE) over the weekend, October 31st through November 2nd. I had a great time again. I say this every year&amp;ndash; Comikaze keeps getting bigger and better. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what the numbers are, but the attendance on Saturday was pretty big&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;d say probably a 30% increase from last year.
I only went on Friday and Saturday. I did go on Thursday to do an early pick up of my badge&amp;ndash; which is where and when I took the shot below of the Los Angeles Convention Center with the Comikaze Expo sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Brief Appearance on Heroes of Cosplay</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2014 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/06/my-brief-appearance-on-heroes-of-cosplay/</guid>
      <description>In a last week&amp;rsquo;s episode of Heroes of Cosplay, I had a brief appearance in Season 1 - Episode 7!
The episode covered part of the cosplay competition at Stan Lee&amp;rsquo;s Comikaze Expo. I was there in attendance checking out the event and taking photos of many cosplayers and panels.
I appear at about the 2:34 mark as the opening credits are still rolling.
That&amp;rsquo;s me in the Valiant t-shirt behind the DSLR!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2013 18:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/11/comikaze-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>This past weekend I went to Comikaze Expo at the Los Angeles Convention Center. Last year I blogged about my experience and I must say that this year is a huge improvement. I want to share with everyone my thoughts and pictures I took of the convention.
But first I want to say that what Comikaze is doing is important. San Diego Comic Con (SDCC) is getting so big now that many comics/sci-fi/horror fans can&amp;rsquo;t even get tickets or housing to the huge event&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s such a hassle!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comikaze Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/09/comikaze-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I checked out the Comikaze Expo at the LA Convention Center (LACC). As far as I know, this was the first &amp;ldquo;real&amp;rdquo; comic con taking place in Los Angeles. The previous year&amp;rsquo;s I heard took place in a parking structure or something. But this is a comic con for LA made by fans, for fans. That&amp;rsquo;s their slogan more or less anyway.
Anyway, I had fun and took a lot of pictures.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>