<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Comics on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/comics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comics on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/comics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Movies of 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/movies-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>This looks like a good year for not just comic book fans, but fans of books and other franchises because there are so many sequels coming out. This is why I dropped doing comic book only movies for my posts and opened it up to all movies.
Here are my top 8 movies that I think will be hits:
 Avengers: Infinity War Black Panther Ready Player One Incredibles 2 Ant-Man and The Wasp Deadpool 2 Alita: Battle Angel Venom  Quick Thoughts Black Panther - February 16, 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder Woman</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</guid>
      <description>I watched the Wonder Woman movie twice, didn&amp;rsquo;t like it much the first time, but enjoyed it more the second time. My initial reaction after the first viewing was rather harsh on the movie, and I think it had to do with how close I sat and how much my eyes had to travel when looking at the screen. The second time I sat further back in a sweet spot, and my eyes were more relaxed to enjoy the movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed watching Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2, it&amp;rsquo;s what a space adventure movie should be! What I especially love about the movie is that every character has his/her moment in the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s a great sequel to the amazing first movie.
The movie has FIVE post credit scenes, yes 5, so be sure to stay through the entire credit scroll to catch them all. This is my spoiler filled review of the movie, so read no further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched the movie yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</guid>
      <description>I liked the movie, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t love Logan. It was the best Wolverine movie Fox has made, but that bar is rather low to clear. After 17 years of playing the character, it was a good send off for Hugh Jackman. He really made the character his own over the years, despite being different from the comics-Wolverine character.
The Good What I liked about the movie is that it continues to stay true to movie-Wolverine character that Jackman has made in his solo movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comic Book Movies of 2017</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/01/comic-book-movies-of-2017/</guid>
      <description>Last year I wrote a post about Super Hero Movies of 2016. I wanted to do the same for 2017, as it looks to be another amazing year for comic fans.
2017 Rankings This is the ranking, 1-6, ranked from most looking forward to, to least.
 Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 (May 5, 2017) Wonder Woman (June 2, 2017) Thor: Ragnarok (November 3, 2017) Justice League (November 17, 2017) Spiderman: Homecoming (July 7, 2017) Logan (March 3, 2017)  Logan I cannot get excited about Fox&amp;rsquo;s Logan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Strange</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</guid>
      <description>The last MCU movie for 2016, Doctor Strange came out last week. This is my spoilery review which covers some plot points and my thoughts of it&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on the movie universe.
I really enjoyed the movie. It was an origin movie that formally introduced magic and the multiverse into Marvel&amp;rsquo;s cinematic universe. This is a big deal because it opens the door to infinite possibilities for how they wish to expand or even link universes together&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at Fox&amp;rsquo;s Deadpool/X-Men franchise here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</guid>
      <description>My quick non-spoiler-y thoughts on Suicide Squad:
I went in with low expectations, overall, the movie was just okay. I was entertained, but not blown away by anything. If you are expecting what you saw the trailers, you are probably going to be disappointed. It&amp;rsquo;s worth a watch if you want to keep up with the DC movie universe.
Disclaimer: I watched the movie for free with my T-Mobile Tuesday App, which gave me free tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-Men Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>This is my spoiler filled review for the latest X-Men movie. I also talk about all the previous X-Men movies. It won&amp;rsquo;t be pretty.
I did not care for X-Men: Apocalypse.
I went in with low expectations and came out disappointed with what I saw. This is coming from someone who read some of the X-Men comics as well as watched the 1990s animated TV series.
The problem is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie where things happen, has characters from the X-Men universe, but in name only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain America: Civil War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>This is my Captain America: Civil War review that contains spoilers, so if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the movie yet, please stop reading now! I also provide some insights and predictions on what&amp;rsquo;s to come. I also assume you&amp;rsquo;ve seen all the movies in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) to date.
I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the movie twice now and I really like it. I even enjoyed it more the second time. Not only does it complete a trilogy of the Captain America movies, it also sets up Phase 3 of the MCU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batman v Superman Dawn of Justice Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I saw Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice. In a nutshell, I thought it was okay, but not great&amp;ndash; nor does it match the hype. This post does contain SPOILERS, so don&amp;rsquo;t read any further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it yet or don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned&amp;hellip;.
I reviewed Man of Steel several years ago and gave it a generally positive review for a sci-fi Superman reimagining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Super Hero Movies of 2016</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/01/super-hero-movies-of-2016/</guid>
      <description>This year (2016), is looking to be an amazing year for comic book and superhero fans. There are so many movies coming out from both Marvel and DC that it&amp;rsquo;s a stark reminder how great it is to be a fan. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, this post is spoiler free for both the movies (since I haven&amp;rsquo;t seen them nor have they come out yet) and the source materials, the comics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 YouTube Channels for Comic Geeks</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/05/top-5-youtube-channels-for-comic-geeks/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s such an amazing time to be a comic book fan/geek. From movies to TV shows and merchandising, all the way to comic cons, there&amp;rsquo;s just so much content to consume that it can be a bit overwhelming. I don&amp;rsquo;t really watch TV anymore and just rely on my social media feed, websites, and youTube for all my news and entertainment. So there are a few YouTube channels that I absolutely love and would recommend to my friends and comic fans alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man of Steel Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</guid>
      <description>Man of Steel is the best take on Superman movie since Christopher Reeve donned the role. For me, he set the bar as to what Superman was before anything. Immediately after watching the movie, I said I liked it. But after sleeping on it and thinking about it more and more, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to like it less and less.
SPOILERS below. You have been warned.
What I liked: It&amp;rsquo;s a new take on Superman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y: The Last Man Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</guid>
      <description>For the past seven months I&amp;rsquo;ve jumped back into reading comics and graphic novels. I used to read them a lot when I was a teenager, but just lost interest by the mid/late 1990s. I find myself struggling to enjoy reading monthly issues and going to the comic book shop every week&amp;ndash; or even getting them online via Comixology.
The problem I have is that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reading them month to month&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s too little to read bit by bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Lantern Movie Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 13:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>Green Lantern was the movie I was looking forward to the most this summer. I watched it last night and wanted to share my thoughts on the movie with other fans and others that may have watched the movie already. I still recommend people to go watch the movie though, to read the comics, and/or then come talk to me.
Please note, DO NOT READ FURTHER IF YOU HAVEN&amp;rsquo;T SEEN THE MOVIE YET.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>