<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anime Expo on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/anime-expo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anime Expo on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/anime-expo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2018</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/07/anime-expo-2018/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend I was at Anime Expo (AX). In general it was super fun to be taking photos of cosplayers there again. But it was a crazy hot weekend. It was 100+ &amp;#176; F every day there!
It&amp;rsquo;s been three years (2015) since I was at AX. I mostly hung out inside the South hall again. I didn&amp;rsquo;t see as many cosplayers as I thought I would, and I think that may be because of the heat, and that many notable cosplayers/photographers set up near the Staples Center out West.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2015</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/07/anime-expo-2015/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently in California. This past week was Anime Expo in Los Angeles, and this coming week will be San Diego Comic Con in well, San Diego.
Like previous years, I attend AX mostly to take pictures of cosplays in the South Hall. Not many people realize that the lighting from the windows and structure of the building acts like a diffuser for most of the day. In other words, it makes LA&amp;rsquo;s harsh light into something fun to work with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2014</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2014 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014/</guid>
      <description>Day-0.jpg blogger_id: tag:blogger.com,1999:blog-6841384.post-5261524371800133363 blogger_orig_url: http://www.sunpech.com/2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html redirect_from: /2014/07/anime-expo-2014.html
headerimage: /images/headers/anime_expo.jpg This year&amp;rsquo;s Anime Expo (AX) has come and gone now. Just like the previous years, I went again to take photos of the cosplayers. For me, AX, has the best collective gatherings of cosplayers I&amp;rsquo;ve ever come across&amp;ndash; although one day I&amp;rsquo;d like to check out DragonCon, which I hear is amazing.
If you just want to see my sets of pictures see below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2013</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 13:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/07/anime-expo-2013/</guid>
      <description>Over the Fourth of July week I attended Anime Expo (AX) at the Los Angeles Convention Center (LACC). Last year I went and took over 1500 photos. This year I took over 1700 photos.
Full albums can be found here on G+ (and Facebook&amp;ndash; FB):  Anime Expo 2013 Day 0 Anime Expo 2013 Day 1 Anime Expo 2013 Day 2 Anime Expo 2013 Day 3 
I did not go on Day 4, on Sunday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anime Expo 2012</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2012 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/07/anime-expo-2012/</guid>
      <description>A little over a week ago I attended Anime Expo (AX) held at the LA Convention Center. I had a four-day pass for June 29 - July 2, 2012. The last time I attended AX was in 2008, quite a long time ago. I recall being the odd one for not dressing up&amp;ndash; as so so very many people dress up in an anime costume!
So a motivation for attending this year was to take pictures of the costumed attendees.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>