<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on sunpech.com</title>
    <link>https://sunpech.com/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on sunpech.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sunpech.com/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deadpool 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/05/deadpool-2/</guid>
      <description>I watched Deadpool 2 over the weekend and I thought the movie was just okay. The movie was done in a Deadpool way, which is both good and bad. This is my review.
Spoilers below of course.
The Good The movie is made for comic fans and those familiar with comic book pop culture. Deadpool&amp;rsquo;s character in the comics and movies is very meta in it&amp;rsquo;s commentary of comics, pop culture, current events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avengers Infinity War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/04/avengers-infinity-war/</guid>
      <description>Destiny has arrived. I watched the Avengers: Infinity War twice already and I loved it. The first time was the most emotional and suprising, the second time I caught some dialogue I missed and was more relaxed.
It&amp;rsquo;s been over three years since Kevin Feige announced the plans for MCU Phase 3, and ten years since the first movie. This is the culmination of everthing that has come before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Panther</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2018/02/black-panther/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed the Black Panther movie. The story, the characters, and especially the villain was well balanced and defined in this Marvel movie. This is my spoilery review.
The Good The characters were really solid. It&amp;rsquo;s an all-star cast!
Letitia Wright is amazing as Black Panther&amp;rsquo;s sister, Shuri. She was having fun and it really showed. She&amp;rsquo;s also starred in an episode of Black Mirror: Black Museum.
Michael B. Jordan knocked it out of the park as Erik Killmonger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars The Last Jedi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0100</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/star-wars-the-last-jedi/</guid>
      <description>I loved Star Wars The Last Jedi. The movie is brilliant. I&amp;rsquo;ve only watched it once as of this posting and I plan on watching it a few more times to catch all the little things I may have missed.
Spoilers below of course.
Empire and Return The movie has similarities to both Empire Strikes Back and Return of the Jedi.
The dark tones are similar to Empire. The failure of Luke Skywalker and the entire Jedi Order was touched upon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Justice League</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/12/justice-league/</guid>
      <description>I am pretty disappointed in the Justice League (JL) movie. I went in with low expectations since it is a Zack Snyder movie that was finished by Joss Whedon. I&amp;rsquo;ve reviewed Man of Steel and Batman vs Superman where I&amp;rsquo;ve complained about Snyder as a director. Despite Whedon&amp;rsquo;s involvement, JL suffers more of the same&amp;ndash; great visually with unappealing characters and story.
Spoilers below of course.
What I Liked Gal Gadot looks amazing as Wonder Woman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thor Ragnarok</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/11/thor-ragnarok/</guid>
      <description>I really liked Thor: Ragnarok. By far it was the best Thor movie from the MCU and maybe even the best Marvel movie of 2017. There&amp;rsquo;s not much to complain about in the movie. Spoilers ahead.
What I Liked The movie is a blend of Planet Hulk and Ragnarok story from the comics. Since Marvel can&amp;rsquo;t do Hulk movies&amp;ndash; due to movie rights sitting with Universal, they just incorporated one of his best stories in with Thor&amp;rsquo;s to make a buddy space adventure and comedy movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spider-Man Homecoming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/07/spider-man-homecoming/</guid>
      <description>Spider-Man: Homecoming is a good, coming-of-age movie aimed at younger fans and those young at heart. I liked it on a few levels, but also felt distant because I&amp;rsquo;m older and watched other Spidey and superhero films since the early 1990s.
The Good I like how Tom Holland actually looks like a teenager. I&amp;rsquo;ve always preferred the younger teen Spider-Man that makes quips in battles. Toby Maquire looked too old for high school and Andrew Garfield too handsome/hipster/cool to be Peter Parker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wonder Woman</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/06/wonder-woman/</guid>
      <description>I watched the Wonder Woman movie twice, didn&amp;rsquo;t like it much the first time, but enjoyed it more the second time. My initial reaction after the first viewing was rather harsh on the movie, and I think it had to do with how close I sat and how much my eyes had to travel when looking at the screen. The second time I sat further back in a sweet spot, and my eyes were more relaxed to enjoy the movie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/05/guardians-of-the-galaxy-vol.-2/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed watching Guardians of the Galaxy Vol 2, it&amp;rsquo;s what a space adventure movie should be! What I especially love about the movie is that every character has his/her moment in the movie. It&amp;rsquo;s a great sequel to the amazing first movie.
The movie has FIVE post credit scenes, yes 5, so be sure to stay through the entire credit scroll to catch them all. This is my spoiler filled review of the movie, so read no further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched the movie yet!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logan</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2017/03/logan/</guid>
      <description>I liked the movie, but I didn&amp;rsquo;t love Logan. It was the best Wolverine movie Fox has made, but that bar is rather low to clear. After 17 years of playing the character, it was a good send off for Hugh Jackman. He really made the character his own over the years, despite being different from the comics-Wolverine character.
The Good What I liked about the movie is that it continues to stay true to movie-Wolverine character that Jackman has made in his solo movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Strange</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/11/doctor-strange/</guid>
      <description>The last MCU movie for 2016, Doctor Strange came out last week. This is my spoilery review which covers some plot points and my thoughts of it&amp;rsquo;s potential impact on the movie universe.
I really enjoyed the movie. It was an origin movie that formally introduced magic and the multiverse into Marvel&amp;rsquo;s cinematic universe. This is a big deal because it opens the door to infinite possibilities for how they wish to expand or even link universes together&amp;ndash; I&amp;rsquo;m looking at Fox&amp;rsquo;s Deadpool/X-Men franchise here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suicide Squad</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/08/suicide-squad/</guid>
      <description>My quick non-spoiler-y thoughts on Suicide Squad:
I went in with low expectations, overall, the movie was just okay. I was entertained, but not blown away by anything. If you are expecting what you saw the trailers, you are probably going to be disappointed. It&amp;rsquo;s worth a watch if you want to keep up with the DC movie universe.
Disclaimer: I watched the movie for free with my T-Mobile Tuesday App, which gave me free tickets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Warcraft Movie</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/06/warcraft-movie/</guid>
      <description>This is my review for the Warcraft movie, which is based off the video game.
I normally give a spoiler warning, but I won&amp;rsquo;t say enough about the plot of the movie to ruin anyone&amp;rsquo;s experience. But in case you are sensitive to any information and want to go in fresh, then you should stop reading now&amp;ndash; but I doubt that since you&amp;rsquo;ve read this far already.
I do have some background in playing Warcraft III, World of Warcraft (WoW), Hearthstone, and other games from Blizzard Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>X-Men Apocalypse</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/x-men-apocalypse/</guid>
      <description>This is my spoiler filled review for the latest X-Men movie. I also talk about all the previous X-Men movies. It won&amp;rsquo;t be pretty.
I did not care for X-Men: Apocalypse.
I went in with low expectations and came out disappointed with what I saw. This is coming from someone who read some of the X-Men comics as well as watched the 1990s animated TV series.
The problem is it&amp;rsquo;s a movie where things happen, has characters from the X-Men universe, but in name only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Captain America: Civil War</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/captain-america-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>This is my Captain America: Civil War review that contains spoilers, so if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the movie yet, please stop reading now! I also provide some insights and predictions on what&amp;rsquo;s to come. I also assume you&amp;rsquo;ve seen all the movies in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) to date.
I&amp;rsquo;ve watched the movie twice now and I really like it. I even enjoyed it more the second time. Not only does it complete a trilogy of the Captain America movies, it also sets up Phase 3 of the MCU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reflecting on Console Wars</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/05/reflecting-on-console-wars/</guid>
      <description>I recently finished reading Console Wars by Blake J. Harris and I really enjoyed the trip down memory lane. I grew up in the 1980s and 1990s and played on video game systems by Nintendo, Sega, Sony, and Atari. This is my reflection on this gaming era after reading this book.
Console Wars tells the story of Tom Kalinske, an American business man and CEO behind Sega of America during its meteoric rise and fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Batman v Superman Dawn of Justice Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2016 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2016/03/batman-v-superman-dawn-of-justice-review/</guid>
      <description>Over the weekend I saw Batman v Superman: Dawn of Justice. In a nutshell, I thought it was okay, but not great&amp;ndash; nor does it match the hype. This post does contain SPOILERS, so don&amp;rsquo;t read any further if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it yet or don&amp;rsquo;t mind!
You&amp;rsquo;ve been warned&amp;hellip;.
I reviewed Man of Steel several years ago and gave it a generally positive review for a sci-fi Superman reimagining.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>I enjoyed reading Andy Weir&amp;rsquo;s book, The Martian. It reads mostly like a series of journal entries of the protagonist, Mark Watney who&amp;rsquo;s stuck on Mars. If you are a science buff, there&amp;rsquo;s some interesting things that occur in terms of problem solving which Mythbuster Adam Savage, has said he would love to try at his Comic Con panel.
It&amp;rsquo;s also a quick read, as you may find yourself flying through the chapters as they are a bit short.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Armada</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/armada/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago I read Ernest Cline&amp;rsquo;s book, Ready Player One. I blogged about my love for the book and how excited I was that a movie was being made. Quick update, it&amp;rsquo;s getting a release date of December 15, 2017! However, I can&amp;rsquo;t say that I liked his second book, Armada, nearly as much.
In a nutshell the book is The Last Starfigther meets Ender&amp;rsquo;s Game. It&amp;rsquo;s a coming of age story of a teenager that plays video games, struggles with his place in the world, and has pop culture knowledge of things from the 80s forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus, A Year Later</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/oneplus-a-year-later/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/08/oneplus-a-year-later/</guid>
      <description>I consider the OnePlus One I bought over a year ago a value phone&amp;ndash; best phone for the buck you spend. For it&amp;rsquo;s time, it was a big phone, with fantastic specs, for a low price. Even now, it&amp;rsquo;s still a good phone and is my main mobile device. The battery is good and CM12S operating system is also decent.
When I initially had CM11S running on my phone, the battery life was 2 days of regular usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/elon-musk-tesla-spacex-and-the-quest-for-a-fantastic-future/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated with Elon Musk and his companies: Tesla Motors and SpaceX. I recently read, Elon Musk: Tesla, SpaceX, and the Quest for a Fantastic Future by Ashlee Vance just to learn a bit more about him.
I like to read books on some of the best entrepreneurs and companies in modern times. Everyone from Bill Gates, Michael Dell, Jeff Bezos, Tony Hsieh, Jason Fried, Larry Page, Sergey Brin, to Steve Jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready Player One</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/ready-player-one/</guid>
      <description>I own several copies of the book, Ready Player One, by Ernest Cline. I have it in hardcover, softcover, and digitally on Amazon Kindle. I only do this for a few books&amp;ndash; the ones I really enjoy. Off the top of my head, another is Jurassic Park by Michael Crichton.
This post is spoiler-free. Read it knowing that you can still fully enjoy the book and upcoming movie.
The Book The book paints a picture of a dystopian future, the year 2044, where people are plugged away in a virtual reality based world, OASIS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/becoming-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>A few years ago, I finished the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson and I wrote a blog post too. For the time it was released, I would say the published book collected the most information on Steve Jobs out there. Isaacson generally gives a negative review of Jobs with multiple repetitions of reality distortion field throughout the book. The book focuses a little more on the bad relationships than the good ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today&#39;s Tech TV Shows</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/todays-tech-tv-shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2015/06/todays-tech-tv-shows/</guid>
      <description>There are two tech TV shows that I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying right now: Silicon Valley and Halt and Catch Fire.
They both deal with the business and culture of technology startups, but yet are pretty different from each other. They are both on their second seasons.
Silicon Valley pokes fun at the today&amp;rsquo;s tech craze in a humorous and ridiculous way. As it should be, technology is hot stuff right now and there&amp;rsquo;s so much money being thrown around as everyone thinks they are going to change the world with their product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OnePlus One vs Nexus 5</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/oneplus-one-vs-nexus-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2014/08/oneplus-one-vs-nexus-5/</guid>
      <description>Last month in July, I purchased two Android phones: The Nexus 5 (N5) and the OnePlus One (OPO). I initially ordered the Nexus 5 because I was sick of waiting for an OnePlus invite that I signed up for in April. Up until then, I was using a Galaxy Nexus for two years and its overall performance was rather sluggish and could no longer hold a charge for half a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Storage Services Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/cloud-storage-services-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2013 09:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/cloud-storage-services-review/</guid>
      <description>There are so many cloud storage services out there now vying for our attention and data. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share my thoughts on the popular choices out there. I&amp;rsquo;m only looking at the personal or free plans. I&amp;rsquo;m leaving out anything for businesses or enterprises&amp;ndash; those are just a different beast with very different needs altogether.
Things I try to consider:
 Size of free storage (either from the start or earned through referrals) Sharing and collaboration on files Ease of use Anything else more than storage  Amazon Cloud Drive I really do not use this service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man of Steel Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/man-of-steel-review/</guid>
      <description>Man of Steel is the best take on Superman movie since Christopher Reeve donned the role. For me, he set the bar as to what Superman was before anything. Immediately after watching the movie, I said I liked it. But after sleeping on it and thinking about it more and more, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to like it less and less.
SPOILERS below. You have been warned.
What I liked: It&amp;rsquo;s a new take on Superman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Compatible External Hard Drives Are Over-Priced</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2013 11:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/06/apple-compatible-external-hard-drives-are-over-priced/</guid>
      <description>Buying any technology related products online is still by far the best way to save money over buying from traditional brick and mortar stores. The likely products you would buy for your PC/Mac are keyboards, mice, external hard drive, and headphones.
I&amp;rsquo;d like to focus on the external hard drives, since they are currently priced differently between the PC and Mac market. For all intents and purposes of these drives are to backup data of a machine running either Windows or Mac.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Y: The Last Man Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/05/y-the-last-man-review/</guid>
      <description>For the past seven months I&amp;rsquo;ve jumped back into reading comics and graphic novels. I used to read them a lot when I was a teenager, but just lost interest by the mid/late 1990s. I find myself struggling to enjoy reading monthly issues and going to the comic book shop every week&amp;ndash; or even getting them online via Comixology.
The problem I have is that I don&amp;rsquo;t like reading them month to month&amp;ndash; it&amp;rsquo;s too little to read bit by bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I love Google Reader</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2013/03/why-i-love-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2013 10:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2013/03/why-i-love-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday some sad news hit me with Google&amp;rsquo;s decision to close Google Reader on July 1, 2013.
Why? As The Next Web wrote, Former Google Reader product manager confirms our suspicions: Its demise is all about Google+. See Brian Shih, former Google Reader Product Manager&amp;rsquo;s answer on Quora.
This is sad for me because other than Gmail and Search itself, Google Reader (GR) is the service I use the most from Google, and is a browser tab I always have open.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Design of Everyday Things</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Feb 2012 16:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/the-design-of-everyday-things/</guid>
      <description>The Design of Everyday Things comes highly recommended on Coding Horror&amp;rsquo;s recommended reading list as well as many other software developers. After giving it a read, I thought it was good, relevant today, but slightly dated with their examples.
After reading the book, I am reminded of the light switch to my bathroom in my current apartment in Los Angeles. See below.
It&amp;rsquo;s such a horrible design! The left-most button, which is red, is for off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jiro Dreams of Sushi</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2012 01:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/jiro-dreams-of-sushi/</guid>
      <description>Just got back from watching a special advanced screening of Jiro Dreams of Sushi at the Landmark. Special thanks to Aisha and Foodspotting for putting me on the list!
The documentary is wonderful! Besides the very appealing video of sushi on the big screen, there is quite a story of Jiro Ono and his sushi restaurant, Sukiyabashi Jiro. There certainly is craftsmanship and art to making sushi&amp;ndash; which Jiro has dedicated his life to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/02/food-photography-from-snapshots-to-great-shots/</guid>
      <description>As a foodie and photography enthusiast, I found Food Photography: From Snapshots to Great Shots to be a good read, mostly. Although, I did find myself skimming the later chapters as they deal with post-processing using Adobe Photoshop.
The first three chapters on fundamentals, equipment, and lighting I thought were the best for foodies interested in improving their skills as a photographer. The chapter on framing and composition is good too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs biography</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 11:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/steve-jobs-biography/</guid>
      <description>I really enjoyed reading the Steve Jobs biography by Walter Isaacson. I bought both the hardcover and the Kindle book version. Isaacson&amp;rsquo;s writing is superb and flows very well. However, if you read articles or even watched some Steve Jobs documentaries, it covers a lot of similar ground. I am reminded of the TV movie, Pirates of Silicon Valley. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t watched it, I highly recommend it.
I think it&amp;rsquo;s fair for people to compare him to Thomas Edison, as Jobs was our modern day inventor and businessman&amp;ndash; a visionary if you will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Western Digital WD TV Live Streaming Media Player</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/western-digital-wd-tv-live-streaming-media-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 17:36:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2012/01/western-digital-wd-tv-live-streaming-media-player/</guid>
      <description>Since I moved to LA, I&amp;rsquo;ve been without my old PC that runs XBMC. For a Home Theater PC (HTPC), the PC is decent, but it&amp;rsquo;s large, loud, and not in California. So I went on Amazon and bought the Western Digital WD TV Live Streaming Media Player for $90 US. Behold, my new HTPC.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using it for a few days, and overall I&amp;rsquo;m pretty happy with it. I was able to hook up my external USB hard drives to a D-Link DUB-H7 High Speed USB 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kindle Fire Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/11/kindle-fire-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/11/kindle-fire-review/</guid>
      <description>I pre-ordered my Kindle Fire in early October. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an eReader device for a long time, ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been traveling so much. Carrying books around is such a pain.
Like many others out there, I got my Kindle Fire on November 15, 2011. After a few weeks of using the Fire, I felt I could give it a good review. I&amp;rsquo;ve used it for playing Words With Friends, some basic browsing on Amazon, and I finished reading the Steve Jobs biography on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purchased a Herman Miller Aeron Chair</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 00:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/08/purchased-a-herman-miller-aeron-chair/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago I purchased a Herman Miller Aeron chair from Home and Office Solutions up in Northbrook, Illinois. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted an Aeron for the longest time, but just never felt comfortable spending a thousand dollars on an office chair. My seven-year old Ikea chair was falling apart and wasn&amp;rsquo;t comfortable anymore. To be honest, it started to fall apart after two years. I really needed to get a new chair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Lantern Movie Review</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 13:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2011/06/green-lantern-movie-review/</guid>
      <description>Green Lantern was the movie I was looking forward to the most this summer. I watched it last night and wanted to share my thoughts on the movie with other fans and others that may have watched the movie already. I still recommend people to go watch the movie though, to read the comics, and/or then come talk to me.
Please note, DO NOT READ FURTHER IF YOU HAVEN&amp;rsquo;T SEEN THE MOVIE YET.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Happiness by Tony Hsieh</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/08/delivering-happiness-by-tony-hsieh/</guid>
      <description>A few months ago, Tony Hsieh, the CEO of Zappos, offered free copies of his new book, Delivering Happiness: A Path to Profits, Passion, and Purposevia his twitter. I hopped on it right away and got myself two copies of it by using two different email addresses. I gave one away to a friend and kept the remaining copy to myself to keep and read.
I really enjoyed this book. It&amp;rsquo;s inspirational how Tony Hsieh started his company out, taking the big risks he did, despite the economic conditions of the Dot Com bubble burst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Review: Balsamiq Mockups</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/software-review-balsamiq-mockups/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2010 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/04/software-review-balsamiq-mockups/</guid>
      <description>I first read about Balsamiq Mockups a few weeks ago on StackOverflow.
In general I agree with what Jeff Atwood and Joel Spolsky said about the product on their podcast (IT Conversations: Episode 47). It really is a simple mockup tool that isn&amp;rsquo;t about being exact and precise, but rather sketchy and fast so you can get your idea down quickly. It makes starting something easy and fast, so you can move on to what&amp;rsquo;s next.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rework by Jason Fried and David Heinemeier Hansson</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2010 14:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/03/rework-by-jason-fried-and-david-heinemeier-hansson/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Rework by the founders of 37Signals. I really really enjoyed the book. The chapters were concise and to the point.
Here are my favorite chapters:
 Learning from mistakes is overrated Planning is guessing No time is no excuse Outside money is Plan Z Embrace constraints Focus on won&#39;t change Interruption is the enemy of productivity Meetings are toxic Your estimates suck Underdo your competition Say no by default Emulate chefs Drug dealers get it right Do it yourself first Everybody works They&#39;re not thirteen Don&#39;t scar on the first cut  I highly recommend people to pick up a copy if you are at all interested in how a great business should be run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coders at Work and Duct Tape Programming</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 21:25:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2010/01/coders-at-work-and-duct-tape-programming/</guid>
      <description>I finished reading Coders at Work! I really enjoyed the interviews with Jamie Zawinksi, Douglas Crockford, Brendan Eich, and Ken Thompson. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t too interested in compilers and the much older systems some of the programmers once developed in. I must admit, I had a short attention span reading over those sections.
Anyway, the reason I picked this book up was because back in late September to early October 2009, I remember reading several blog posts on duct tape programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LaLa.com: A Better Alternative to iTunes</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2009/05/lala.com-a-better-alternative-to-itunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2009 11:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2009/05/lala.com-a-better-alternative-to-itunes/</guid>
      <description>Several years ago, I tried out iTunes and really enjoyed the experience. I came from a Winamp background and really liked having a fast loading application. On top of that, I am a computer geek, so I already know where all my files are on the OS filesystem.
Anyway, after using iTunes for a little over a year and hundreds of songs purchased later, it was starting up slower and slower.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Impressions of the G1 running Android</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-impressions-of-the-g1-running-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2008 22:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/11/my-impressions-of-the-g1-running-android/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had my G1 for a few weeks now. My overall impressions are pretty good. I like the touch screen, I like the free applications available through the market app, and I definitely enjoy the web browsing experience on the 3G network over my old Blackberry Pearl on the EDGE network.
But I do have a few complaints:
 Battery Life is too short. I can maybe go for a maximum of 2 days without a recharge if I very minimal use of the phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Cocktail Chicago 9</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/10/tech-cocktail-chicago-9/</guid>
      <description>Another digerati networking event coming up in November! Last time I went I had a pretty good time talking with various people in the Chicago tech community. Only wish my company would sport me with actual up-to-date business cards!

When: Thursday, November 6, 2008 - 6:30 p.m. to 9:00 p.m. CST Where: John Barleycorn Wrigleyville Tech Cocktail Chicago 9
I also recently joined the community: iam.techcocktail.com
You can see my personal blog&amp;rsquo;s previous posting on Tech Cocktail 8 here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Free Software Recommendations for 2008</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/best-free-software-recommendations-for-2008/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2008 11:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/08/best-free-software-recommendations-for-2008/</guid>
      <description>For almost ten years now, I still find myself fixing computers for friends. It&amp;rsquo;s not so much hardware these days as it is cleaning out viruses and installing software to handle a certain task. I don&amp;rsquo;t mind so much, but I just hope my friends learn something from what I do and explain rather than to just rely on me to fix everything for them each and every time.
Anyway, for protecting a computer running Windows, an Antivirus software is required along with receiving regular updates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finished reading the Groundswell</title>
      <link>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2008 03:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <author>steven@sunpech.com (Steven Suwatanapongched)</author>
      <guid>https://sunpech.com/2008/07/finished-reading-the-groundswell/</guid>
      <description>I just finished reading Groundswell: Winning in a World Transformed by Social Technologies. Probably one of the best books I&amp;rsquo;ve read this year thus far.
 What Is Groundswell? It&#39;s a book by two Forrester analysts with practical, data-based strategies for companies that want to harness the power of social technologies like blogs, social networks, and YouTube. (source: Forrester) I absolutely love reading case studies in these IT Business books. I finished my MS in Information Systems 2 years ago last month.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>